[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.62,0:00:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  艾玛  欢迎乘坐塔克尔号\NOkay, Emma. All aboard the Tucker train.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.53,0:00:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备开动咯\NTucka-tucka tucka-tucka-- -
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.45,0:00:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  宝贝  今天就跟你耗上了\NLook, baby, I ain't got nowhere else to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.26,0:00:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吃我就喂你一整天\NWe can do this all day, okay? 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.41,0:00:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我投降\NOkay, I'm out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.45,0:00:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天爷  搬家真是太累人了\NOh my God, moving is exhausting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.55,0:00:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正出力搬东西的人更累\NEspecially if you're actually carrying things.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.25,0:00:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快闪开  二头肌都酸死了  \NComing through. Biceps burning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.56,0:00:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实没看起来那么壮\NNot quite as in shape as I look.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.52,0:00:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别让我猜中\NOh-hell-to-the-no.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.64,0:00:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是神马\NWhat is all of this stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.25,0:00:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-决不能让她搬来住  -别紧张  小花生\N- She is not moving in here. - Relax, peanut.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.21,0:00:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些不过是我替儿子们保留的\NThese are just a few cherished memories
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.50,0:00:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童年纪念物\Nthat I've saved from my boys' childhood.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.25,0:00:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可称之为"舍不得在车库甩卖掉的垃圾"\NAlso known as crap-she-couldn't-unload- at-the-garage-sale.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.09,0:00:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是垃圾\NNot crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.05,0:00:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西都代表着我人生的伟大成就\NThese boxes represent a lifetime of awesomeness.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.58,0:00:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都记得  你有多出色\NAnd we'd all hate to forget how awesome you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.82,0:01:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.22,0:01:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这箱子里都是丹尼的奖杯吗\NAre these all filled with Danny's trophies?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.79,0:01:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小到大也得了不少奖啊\N'Cause, you know, I accomplished a few things growing up as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.13,0:01:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做的那张假身份证显然不算\NIf only they gave awards for making fake ID's.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.45,0:01:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  我也给你留了不少东西\NI saved some of your stuff too, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.55,0:01:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.43,0:01:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我幼儿园时的涂鸦\NA picture I painted in kindergarten
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.13,0:01:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和感恩节画的手型火鸡\Nand a Thanksgiving hand turkey?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.86,0:01:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  宝贝\NI'm sorry, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.49,0:01:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不可能什么都留着\NI can't be expected to keep track of everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.14,0:01:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我大学时得的奖杯在哪儿  -楼下车里后排座\N- Where are my college trophies? - Downstairs, backseat.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些箱子都是按颜色和时间分类整理的\NThe boxes should be color-coded and dated.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.24,0:01:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  别不痛快\NMan, don't feel bad, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.13,0:01:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就没给你哥留着手型火鸡\NShe didn't save his hand turkey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.36,0:01:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊  是我的手型火鸡\NLook! My hand turkey!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.93,0:01:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边 惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.02,0:01:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲 雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions.*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.09,0:01:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不上来是哪有问题\NI can't quite put my finger on it,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.91,0:02:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这间屋确实看着不同了\Nbut something about this place feels different.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.92,0:02:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也听过吧  胜者为王\NYou've heard the expression "Winner takes all."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.91,0:02:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是王者风范\NThis is all.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.68,0:02:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  多谢你照看艾玛\NRiley,thanks for watching Emma. 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.52,0:02:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本赛季第一次练习\NFirst practice of the season.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.03,0:02:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从来没穿得这么运动\NI've never seen you look so jocky.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.05,0:02:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼又不是唯一能\NDanny's not the only one
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.15,0:02:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上运动衫  挥杆子打球的人\Nwho can put a jersey on and hit things with a stick.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.69,0:02:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是垒球  那队从未赢过\NIt's softball, and they haven't won a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.21,0:02:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水平不言自明\NDo I need to say more?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.24,0:02:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了\NFound 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.04,0:02:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都放在储藏室的圣诞灯旁\NThey were in the storage room next to the Christmas lights
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.22,0:02:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长得就像巴特夫人丢了的吉娃娃\Nand what I thought was Mrs. Bart's lost chihuahua.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.55,0:02:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实不是\NIt wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.99,0:02:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢  老兄  在斗士队比赛之前  \NThanks, man. And there will be no trash talking
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.59,0:02:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-废话少说  -抱歉\N- of the B-Bar Brawlers. - I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.81,0:02:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真想不明白  如果一点\NI just don't see the point
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.82,0:02:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢的希望都没有  还打什么比赛\Nof playing if you're not at least trying to win.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.80,0:02:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莱丽  顶我一下  -别了  \N- Back me up here, Riley. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.72,0:02:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很了解你们俩  每次说完"莱丽  顶我一下"\NI've known you both long enough to know that "Back me up, Riley"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.14,0:02:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出两秒  就得说"莱丽闭嘴吧  谁问你意见了"\Nis two seconds away from "Shut up, Riley. Who asked you?"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.06,0:02:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键是  等等\NThe point-- wait for it--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.28,0:03:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要玩得开心  这快乐都是我带给他们的\Nis to have fun, and the fun is what I bring.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.98,0:03:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然他们怎么会选我当队长\NHow do you think I got elected team captain?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.65,0:03:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我们免费啤酒和选票\NYou gave us free beer and ballots
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.49,0:03:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后说"选我吧"\Nand said "Vote for me."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.65,0:03:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  看这是什么\NOh my God, look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.29,0:03:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}兜网球:类似曲棍球的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.29,0:03:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兜网球校队合照  你是前锋  我是中锋\NVarsity lacrosse-- you and me, front and center.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.47,0:03:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后卫真不走运  风头全让我们抢了\NWhich is fairly unfortunate for all the people in the back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.80,0:03:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩在同一队\NYou two were on the same team?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.57,0:03:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"莱巨兽"可不是浪得虚名哦\NThey didn't call her Rigantor for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.92,0:03:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她动作更粗鲁  -体型也更壮\N- She was tougher... - And wider.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.49,0:03:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜过所有男队员\N...than any guy on the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.58,0:03:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想和我们打球吗  欢迎加入\NYou wanna come play? Everyone's welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.98,0:03:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在不想搞运动了\NNot really doing the sports thing anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.33,0:03:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  现在看来简直恍如隔世\NGod, this just feels like a different life.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.50,0:03:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两位运动员下午好好玩\NYou athletes enjoy your afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.92,0:03:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去冰场挥杆子了\NI've gotta get to the rink and hit stuff with a stick...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.63,0:03:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了挣钱\Nfor money.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.09,0:03:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们也走吧\NWe gotta get movin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.42,0:03:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挥杆打球是为了免费啤酒\NI need to go hit things with a stick for beer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.46,0:03:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位投手们  我想在赛前激励下士气\NAll right, Brawlers, I'd like to propose a little pre-game toast.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.97,0:03:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们记住  啤酒第一\NMay we always remember that winning isn't everything,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.45,0:03:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛第二  上场\Nbut having a full keg is. Game on!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.26,0:04:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\NHold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.47,0:04:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的替补队员来了\NI think we have a couple pinch hitters.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.64,0:04:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给大家介绍一下  这是莱丽和我女儿艾玛\NEveryone, this is Riley and my daughter Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.66,0:04:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果意外怀孕也有比赛的话  维勒我\NSo if you're keeping score that's Wheeler, 1-0
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.08,0:04:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经1比0领先了\Nin the unplanned-pregnancy game.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.46,0:04:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  我去安顿他们  你先去热身  \NTuck, you wanna try some pop-ups while I get them settled?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.91,0:04:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必了  我撑得快吐了\NI'm good. I already ate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.51,0:04:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说把这个拿走\NI meant--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.34,0:04:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真高兴你们能来\NI'm so glad you guys came down.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.04,0:04:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让艾玛看她老爸的球场英姿\NI thought it'd be nice for Emma to see her daddy play.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.34,0:04:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多打出几支全垒打  -你显然没看过我打球\N- Hit a few over the fence. - Clearly you've never seen me play,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.52,0:04:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个我可不擅长\N'cause that's not exactly what I'm known for.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.65,0:04:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.86,0:04:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑  本垒上抹胶水\NReally? Glue on home plate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.48,0:04:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是我擅长的\NThat's what I'm known for.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.15,0:04:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意  更衣室有美女出没哦\NYoo-hoo. Lady in the locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.54,0:04:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不用急着穿衣服哦\NBut don't feel any pressure to cover up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.59,0:04:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛仔你好\NHi, cowboy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.11,0:05:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈妈  你怎么来了  -丹尼\N- Mom, what are you doing?! - Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.06,0:05:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过  不要来找我\NI told you not to come see me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.83,0:05:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是来找你的  我都没注意到你也在\NAnd I'm not. I didn't even know you were here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.56,0:05:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那更要命  要是我教练再看见你\NThat's worse. If my coach sees you again--
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.33,0:05:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼  他来了  妈妈  拜托你别让我丢脸\NDamn it, there he is. Mom, please don't embarrass me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.88,0:05:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海耶斯教练  -维勒  邦妮你好\N- Coach Hayes-- - Wheeler. Hi, Bonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.68,0:05:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-汉克  -我真的很抱歉\N- Hey, Hank. - I'm really sorry about--
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.89,0:05:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邦妮  汉克\NBonnie? Hank?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.13,0:05:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒  你不介意真是太好了\NI'm glad you're cool with this, Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.15,0:05:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许多人都没法淡定\NA lot of guys wouldn't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.67,0:05:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不介意什么  -我和你妈妈约会\N- Wouldn't be what? - Me going out with your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.23,0:05:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等他反应一分钟\NIt takes him a minute...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.97,0:05:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然和我妈约会\NYou're going out with my mom?!!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.91,0:05:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他迟钝  但总能想明白\N... But he always gets there.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.01,0:05:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算亲自告诉你的\NI was going to talk to you myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.35,0:05:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但邦妮说她能处理\Nbut Bonnie said she'd handle it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.71,0:05:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的处理方式就是瞒着他\NAnd I handled it by not telling him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.52,0:05:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  绝对没让你丢脸\NSee? Absolutely nothing embarrassing whatsoever.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.80,0:05:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开心吗  好吧  不开心吗  再见  我们撤\NHappy? Okay, no. Bye-bye. We should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.59,0:05:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉我你根本不介意\NYou can't tell me you're actually okay with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.99,0:05:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不介意\NI'm actually okay with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈和你的教练约会\NYour mom dating your coach should make
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.55,0:06:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是能帮你吹吹枕边风\Nfor some interesting pillow talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.94,0:06:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  哪儿来的枕边\NWhat? No pillows.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.60,0:06:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么就扯到枕边去了\NHow did there suddenly get to be pillows?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.13,0:06:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只是出去开心一下\NThey were just going to happy hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.93,0:06:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我记得没错  上次你带女孩回来开心\NIf I recall, the last girl you took to happy hour
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.93,0:06:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩的太嗨  结果我们接到了噪音投诉\Ngot so happy we got a noise complaint.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.27,0:06:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那不一样  他们不能\NBut that's different. They wouldn't--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.24,0:06:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已为人母啊\Nshe's a mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.14,0:06:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本也为人父  也没见他闲着啊\NAnd Ben's a dad. Hasn't slowed him down.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.97,0:06:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事比带孩子复杂多了\NIt would take a lot more than a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.45,0:06:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受够了  不能再瞎想了\NThat's it-- I can't think about this anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.59,0:06:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去运动  直到脑子精疲力尽为止\NI'm going to go workout until even my brain is exhausted.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.77,0:06:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20分钟后见\NSee ya' in 20.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.17,0:06:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有进展吗\NAny progress?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.73,0:06:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她能用鼻孔吃  那进展是大大的\NIf she could eat through her nose, I'd say she's doing great.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.77,0:06:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任务完成\NMystery solved.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.98,0:06:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是听老爸的话\NShe's a Daddy's girl. 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.29,0:06:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔和队员们都在场上等着呢\NTucker and the guys are already at the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.91,0:07:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得喂完她  妈妈马上就到\NI should finish feeding her. Mom's gonna be here soon,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.37,0:07:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能帮我把装备拿到楼下吗\Ncan you run my equipment down to the field for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.13,0:07:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带上我的手套  你会玩得开心的  我保证\NAnd take my mitt. You'll have fun. I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.08,0:07:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当年我是胖妞时\NThis weighed so much less
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.27,0:07:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西轻多了\Nwhen I weighed so much more.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.84,0:07:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才看不上这满架子的奖杯呢  对吧\NYou don't care about a shelf-full of trophies, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.58,0:07:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你眼里  爸爸总是英雄  是吧\NYour daddy's still a winner in your eyes, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.13,0:07:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就当你说"是"了\NI'll take that as a "Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.90,0:07:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斗士们  抱歉我迟到了\NBrawlers. Sorry I'm so late.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.94,0:07:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们成功了  我们赢了  -赢啥了\N- We did it. We won! - At what?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.71,0:07:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垒球  第一次获胜\NSoftball. First time ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.00,0:07:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了莱丽  她真了不起\NBut it was all Riley. She was incredible.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.92,0:07:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莱丽  -本  你听见了吗\N- Riley? - Ben! Did you hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.71,0:07:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊  你说得对  太好玩了\NOh my God, you were right. This was so fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.83,0:07:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这些人都棒极了  -不  你最棒了\N- These guys are awesome. - No, you're awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.72,0:07:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三支全垒打  三支啊\NThree home runs! Three.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.59,0:07:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她都快把裁判感动哭了\NI think she even made the umpire cry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.34,0:08:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像我错过了很棒的比赛\NSounds like I missed a great game.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.89,0:08:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件小事你还不知道\NOne other minor thing you missed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.38,0:08:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们选莱丽当队长\NThe guys voted Riley team captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.04,0:08:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  他们怎么能\NWhat? How could they--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.61,0:08:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  队长应该是全票当选\Nwait. I thought the vote had to be unanimous.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.19,0:08:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时可能走神了\NI might have gotten caught up in the moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.15,0:08:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,击个掌呗\NHigh-five?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.30,0:08:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我也不知是怎么回事    \NBen, I don't know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.89,0:08:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\NI do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.33,0:08:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在我喂孩子时抢了我的队长之职\NI was feeding my baby and you took over my team.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.02,0:08:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\NI'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.75,0:08:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只记得正在捡一只手套\NOne minute I was picking up a glove
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.58,0:08:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎么  下一分钟大家就都在欢呼\Nand the next thing I knew everyone was shouting...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.72,0:08:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你真了不起"\N"You're amazing!"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.60,0:08:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  一开始喊的是"真棒"\NOkay, first it started out as "Awesome,"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.69,0:08:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来就变成"了不起"了\Nthen, you know, it went to "Amazing."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.64,0:08:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们有什么好争的\NWhy are we even having this conversation?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.51,0:08:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-反正我又不会去当这个队长  -真的吗\N- I'm obviously not going to do it. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.13,0:08:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都那么"了不起"了\N'Cause I heard you were "Amazing."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.25,0:09:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本  -不  没关系\N- Ben-- - No, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.56,0:09:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全队都很开心\NThe team seemed pretty happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.93,0:09:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许让你接手一阵是件好事\NMaybe it'd be a good thing if you took over for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.40,0:09:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗  当不当我无所谓\NAre you sure? Because I really don't care one way or the other.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.80,0:09:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  我确定  -天啊  太棒啦  谢谢你\N- Yeah, I'm sure. - Oh my God! Yes! Thank you!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.76,0:09:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会特别好玩的\NThis is going to be so much fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.39,0:09:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都忘了自己有多怀念赛场了\NI forgot how much I missed playing--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.20,0:09:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队友之谊  并肩作战  一同大喊    \Nthe camaraderie, the competition, the chanting--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.26,0:09:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"迎面痛击  废物"  我太激动了\N"In your face, suckers." I'm so excited!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.65,0:09:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候回的家  你去哪儿了\NWhen'd you get home? Where'd you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.86,0:09:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还老实吧\NHe behaved himself, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.97,0:09:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  就算是吧\NSure. Let's go with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.55,0:09:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不过是出去吃了意大利菜\NWe just went out for some Italian food.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.10,0:09:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意大利菜\NItalian food?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.40,0:09:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,含义不言自明哦\NWe all know what that means.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.08,0:09:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不明白  那是什么意思  \NNo, we don't! What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.39,0:09:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是不想面对现在这种情况\NThis is exactly what I was trying to avoid.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.72,0:09:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我想保有约会隐私\NHoney, I think I should keep this part of my life private.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.22,0:09:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-隐私  -换句话说\N- Private? - In other words,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.22,0:09:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要以为他是你的教练\Njust because he's your coach,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.87,0:09:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就该让你知道他何时把你妈给搞定了\Ndon't expect to know when he scores.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.36,0:10:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就闲得没事可做吗\NDon't you have something better to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.17,0:10:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  什么事都比不过看好戏\NNo, not better than this, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.73,0:10:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  亲爱的  我知道你不想听我说这些\NOkay, honey, I know that you don't want to hear this,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.23,0:10:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是个女人  我也有需求\Nbut I'm a woman and I have needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.35,0:10:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我列个单子  我马上满足你的需求\NSo make a list. I'll get whatever you need right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.02,0:10:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说好了吗  -我是队长啦\N- So are we good? - I'm captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.45,0:10:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本和我谈过了  -她压根儿没给我张嘴的机会\N- Ben talked me into it. - Without even opening my mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.83,0:10:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们唯一没谈拢的事就是\NThe only thing we haven't figured out yet:
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.58,0:10:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周六谁来照顾艾玛\Nwho's watching Emma on Saturday?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.19,0:10:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定不行  汉克请我吃午饭\NIt's not gonna be me. Hank invited me to lunch
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.86,0:10:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能失约\Nand I'm not canceling.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.92,0:10:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩的行程总是无法融合\NOur schedules are almost impossible to hook up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.30,0:10:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她说"融合"  -好吧\N- She said "Hook up." - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.92,0:10:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来吧\NI'll do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.94,0:10:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来照顾艾玛  我不想让  \NI'll watch Emma. I'd hate
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.38,0:10:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何人取消计划\Nfor anyone to have to cancel their plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.13,0:10:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你  丹尼  -问题解决了\N- Thank you, Danny. - Problem solved.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.97,0:10:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解决个头  不过我会搞定的\NNot yet, but it will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.06,0:11:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你没事吧\NHoney, are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.64,0:11:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事  我牙疼得像被电钻钻过  \NNo. My tooth is throbbing like a jackhammer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.98,0:11:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收到消息就尽快赶回来了\NI got here as soon as I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.18,0:11:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我的头发都烫三十分钟了\NMy hair, however, is 30 minutes away.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.11,0:11:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该找谁来照顾艾玛\NI didn't know who else to call to watch Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.21,0:11:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让我看看吧  你的牙碎了吗  -疼疼疼  \N- Can I see it? Is your tooth cracked? - Ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.77,0:11:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别碰  牙医说让我现在过去\NDon't! The dentist said he could see me right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.16,0:11:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很快完事  我保证  -好吧\N- I won't be long, I promise. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.86,0:11:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我要在一小时内去见汉克\NBecause I'm supposed to meet Hank in less than an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.84,0:11:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是今天啊  -你去吧\N- Is that today? - Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.58,0:11:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记着  别把大牙刷带回家\NAnd remember-- don't take home the giant toothbrush.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.92,0:11:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玩意是当厕所钥匙使的\NIt's the bathroom key.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.11,0:11:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  妈妈\NThanks, mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.77,0:11:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉让你约会泡汤了  汉克\NSorry about your date, Hank.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.61,0:11:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  塔克尔  我不能去比赛  \NSorry, Tuck. I can't make it to the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.48,0:11:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥  因为我在做陪审员呢  别细打听\NWhy? Jury duty. But don't ask me the details,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.72,0:11:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宣过誓的  我现在都不该跟你说话\NI took an oath. I shouldn't even be talking to you now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.47,0:11:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-丹尼  -本\N- Danny! - Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.84,0:11:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可别告诉我艾玛正在外面停车呢\NPlease tell me that Emma is outside parking the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.37,0:12:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  她  等等\NNo, she-- wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.92,0:12:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是该去打垒球吗\NAren't you supposed to be playing softball?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.79,0:12:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我得留在这里  我们被困住了  \NNo, I had to stay. We're swamped.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.90,0:12:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的孩子呢  -别担心  妈妈看着她呢\N- Where's my baby? - Relax. Mom's got her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.89,0:12:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汉克取消了约会  我不知道具体细节\NHank cancelled or something-- not real sure about the details.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.02,0:12:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我该问问汉克  那不就是他吗\NMaybe I should just ask Hank. Isn't that him?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.03,0:12:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去  掩护我\NCrap. Hide me!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.65,0:12:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在干嘛  -好吧\N- What are you doing? - Okay,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.56,0:12:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我刚跟你说的不全是实话\Nso maybe that story wasn't completely true.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.92,0:12:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但万一妈妈察觉了  他们就得逼我做牙根管填充手术了\NBut if mom asks, they had to put me under for a root canal.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.72,0:12:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难以置信\NUnbelievable.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.05,0:12:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没开玩笑  要是穿帮他们就会那么做\NNo, it's not. They'll do it if you ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.32,0:12:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我吃惊的是你\NNo. You.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.47,0:12:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能这么对妈妈  她看起来真的很开心\NHow could you do this to Mom? She seems really happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.05,0:12:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装得你好像关心别人感受似的\NLike you care about other people's happiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.60,0:12:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是莱丽发现你因为她当队长\NHow's Riley going to feel when
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.83,0:12:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而退出比赛  她会怎么想\Nshe finds out you quit because she took over?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.90,0:12:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不叫退出\NThis isn't quitting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.85,0:12:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是不去而且不想让她发现罢了 \NIt's not showing up and hoping she doesn't notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.97,0:12:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟  你本该支持她的\NDude, you're supposed to have her back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.85,0:12:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为她为什么不做女金刚了\NWhy do you think she stopped being Rigantor?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.13,0:12:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她不想被一群小飞机绕着它嗡嗡飞吗[电影"金刚"场景]\NShe got tired of all the small planes buzzing around her head?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.42,0:13:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  她是怕自己再也交不到朋友\NNo. She didn't think she'd ever have any friends,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.44,0:13:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生再也不会喜欢她\Nthat guys would never like her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.69,0:13:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说  你做了件好事  别让好事变坏事\NI'm just saying, you did a good thing. Don't screw it up now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.87,0:13:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗  结账\NCan I settle up?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.79,0:13:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本店请你了  -谢谢\N- It's on the house. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.00,0:13:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的对  我是个白痴\NYou're right. I'm being an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.91,0:13:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你也好不到哪儿去\NBut so are you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.26,0:13:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不是汉克  也可能有别人\NIf it's not Hank, it's going to be someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.64,0:13:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我来份酒水单\NCan I get a bar menu down here?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.13,0:13:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.56,0:13:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我回来了\NMom, I'm back!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.48,0:13:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练\NCoach?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.28,0:13:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-丹尼  -你怎么在这儿\N- Danny! - What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.53,0:13:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还穿我的睡袍\NIn my robe?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.65,0:13:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你看到的这样\NIt's not what it looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.92,0:13:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到那就是我的睡袍\NI'm pretty sure that's my robe.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.90,0:13:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汉克  准备好进来玩第二轮了吗  \NHank, you ready to go in for round two?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.72,0:13:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看得一点没错\NIt's exactly what it looks like!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.14,0:13:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-维勒  冷静点  -不  我没法冷静\N- Wheeler, calm down! - No, I'm not going to calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.74,0:14:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汉克  交给我处理  丹尼  冷静点\NHank, I'll handle this. Danny, calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.98,0:14:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我该穿好衣服  然后我们\NMaybe I should just get dressed and then we--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.53,0:14:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我还是走吧  -汉克  别走\N- or I could just go. - Hank, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.53,0:14:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-汉克  走吧  -说实话  维勒  听我说\N- Hank, yes. - Honestly, Wheeler, listen,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.70,0:14:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-如果你能给我两秒钟  -1  2  两秒到\N- if you would just give me two seconds-- - One two.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.44,0:14:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  什么都没发生\NDanny, nothing was going on here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.16,0:14:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话你以前说过  爸爸管那叫摔跤\NI've heard that before. I believe Dad called it wrestling.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.35,0:14:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你的牙怎么了\NWait. What happened to your tooth?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.11,0:14:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这边\NOther side.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.39,0:14:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是离谱\NYou are unbelievable!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.15,0:14:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道今天下午怎么回事吗  我们在看小孩\NDo you know what went on here this afternoon? We babysat.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.06,0:14:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅此而已  但我们喂艾玛吃香蕉泥时\NThat's it. But when we tried to feed Emma,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.51,0:14:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被她扔得满身都是\Nshe flung mashed bananas all over everything we were wearing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.75,0:14:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  她不爱吃\NYeah, she hates those.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.29,0:14:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以你们没有...  -在照顾孩子时\N- So you weren't-- - Hooking up with a guy I barely knew
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.91,0:14:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与知之甚少的男人乱搞吗  绝不可能\Nwhile I'm supposed to be babysitting? No!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.20,0:14:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  我又不是你外婆\NPlease! I'm not Grandma.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.11,0:14:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我失陪\NNow if you'll excuse me,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.48,0:14:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得清理胸罩里的香蕉泥\NI still have banana in my bra.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.09,0:14:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们真的没有...  -不  没有\N- So you really-- - No, we didn't!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.27,0:15:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一振\NStrike one!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.64,0:15:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裁判  你瞎啊\NUmp! You got cable?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.83,0:15:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不是不在同一场比赛啊\N'Cause we ain't watching the same game.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.19,0:15:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我来晚了\NSo sorry I'm late again,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.97,0:15:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我买了西瓜以表歉意\Nbut I've brought a little peace offering.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.66,0:15:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是决胜局\NIt's the top of the ninth,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.62,0:15:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没时间跟你开玩笑\NI don't really have time for a prank right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.29,0:15:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里面都是伏特加  \NIt's actually full of vodka. 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.69,0:15:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以喝完汁后把瓜打出去\NSo we drink it and then launch it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.65,0:15:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好还能击出个本垒打呢\NThere's a good chance we could clear the fence.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.62,0:15:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡事都有第一次嘛\NFirst time for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.05,0:15:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐吧  维勒  跟那队伪娘坐一起\NTake a seat, Wheeler, with the rest of the ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.88,0:15:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裁判你个猪\NUmp,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.20,0:15:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又判错了  因为你该鸣哨时不鸣哨\Nturn your ringer on because you're missing your calls!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.87,0:15:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么样了  我们赢了吗  -我们想让你回来\N- So how's it going? Are we winning? - We want you back!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.54,0:15:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你还做我们的队长吧\NPlease be our captain again.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.35,0:15:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那莱丽怎么办  -好吧  塔克尔  你上\N- What about Riley? - All right, Tuck, you're on deck.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.62,0:15:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再被三振你就等着把场地舔干净吧\NStrike out again and you'll be lickin' the lines off the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.07,0:15:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都给我精神点\NLook alive, people!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.43,0:15:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们投票一致通过  你是队长\NWe already voted. The job's yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.53,0:15:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你得先把她炒了\NBut you have to fire her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.53,0:15:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次我对莱丽说了不中听的话\NThe last time I told Riley something she didn't want to hear,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.48,0:15:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她逼我吃蜡笔\Nshe made me eat crayons.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.82,0:15:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在想起来眼前还是土黄色\NI still tear up at the sight of burnt sienna.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.01,0:16:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我罩着你  行吗\NDon't worry, I've got your back, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.26,0:16:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队友们\NTeammates.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.86,0:16:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  你今天真可爱\NRiley. Don't you look cute today?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.42,0:16:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我电话响了吧\NIs that my phone?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.16,0:16:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  没事吧\NSo what's up? Everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.56,0:16:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点事  是关于比赛的\NYeah. It's about the game.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.85,0:16:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝\NThank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.27,0:16:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不提我也要说的  -你说什么\N- I was worried I was going to have to bring it up. - Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.31,0:16:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这话不该我说\NI know it's your thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.64,0:16:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你得控制下自己的情绪了\Nbut you've gotta rein in the crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.79,0:16:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正准备控制呢\NKinda trying to do that right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.13,0:16:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你得对球队上点心\NI just think you need to take the game a little more seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.55,0:16:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样我很难向其他人交代\NYou're putting me in a really tough spot with the other guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.58,0:16:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我该让你退队\NTruth is I should've benched you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.05,0:16:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要把我赶出球队吗\NYou were going to bench me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.40,0:16:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那咱们就有话直说了\NOkay, this just got a whole lot easier.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.15,0:16:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能\NBut I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.80,0:16:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不能\NYou know I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.28,0:16:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你我才能重新打球\NYou're the reason I'm playing again
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.09,0:16:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太怀念球场了\Nand I missed it so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.98,0:17:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\NThank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.22,0:17:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要跟我说什么来着\NSo what did you want to tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.85,0:17:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说\NJust...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.99,0:17:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你今天表现真棒  -谢谢\N- That you're doing a really great job. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.90,0:17:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"好消息  莱丽走人了\N"Ding dong, Riley's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.31,0:17:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本正在炒她鱿鱼"\NBen's firing her right now."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.72,0:17:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思\NWhat is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.95,0:17:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我要说的  不过这版本更直白\NThe meaner version of what I was gonna say.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.64,0:17:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练  能和你谈谈吗\NCoach, can we talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.31,0:17:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你是要拿回睡袍是吗\NI suppose you want your robe back.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.79,0:17:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你想的那样...\NIt's not how it...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.55,0:17:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈都跟我说了\NMy mom told me about what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.47,0:17:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  我反应过激了\NI'm really sorry for overreacting like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.51,0:17:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别担心  -多谢理解\N- No hard feelings. - Thanks for understanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.52,0:17:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证下次会表现好点\NAnd I totally promise to be better next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.50,0:17:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得没有下一次了\NI really don't think there's gonna be a next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.64,0:17:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别因为我的过错而责怪她\NDon't blame her because I'm a jerk.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.04,0:17:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你的问题  维勒  说实话\NIt's not you, Wheeler. To be honest,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.94,0:18:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实没那么喜欢她  她不是我的菜\NI'm just not that into her. Turns out she's not my type.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.28,0:18:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是你的菜  -每人品位不同嘛\N- Not your type? - Just a matter of taste.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.93,0:18:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不喜欢风趣迷人\NSo you don't like funny
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.94,0:18:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你根本配不上的女人吗\Nbeautiful women who are totally out of your league?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.88,0:18:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-维勒  -别说了  你说的可是我妈妈\N- Wheeler-- - No, that's my mom you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.06,0:18:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一件事我很肯定  我妈妈是全世界\NAnd the one thing I know for sure is that no one's smarter,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.95,0:18:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最聪明  最善良  最会关心人的女人\Nnicer or more caring on this whole planet.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.95,0:18:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和她约会的男人都该感到幸运\NAnd any guy would be lucky to go out with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.32,0:18:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想约她出去\NI'll go out with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.02,0:18:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了  别做白日梦了\NYeah. In your dreams.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.76,0:18:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你站这么近不怕有危险吗\NAre sure you feel safe coming so close?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.96,0:18:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放下球棒我就安全了\NI would if you put the bat down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.05,0:18:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底哪里不好\NWhat is the matter with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.77,0:18:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你太聪明也太漂亮了\NMaybe you're just too smart and too beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.22,0:18:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额...  你还拿着球棒哈\NAgain, still holding the bat.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.37,0:18:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人外表可以任意改变\NYou can change the outside all you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.11,0:18:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但内心不容易变\Nbut the inside-- not so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.02,0:19:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到  我不能只享受乐趣\NI couldn't do it-- I couldn't just have fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.65,0:19:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢球对你来说就是乐趣\NWinning is fun for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.21,0:19:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  爱死那感觉了\NOh my God, I love it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.87,0:19:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但胜利给我带来什么\NBut what does that get me?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.44,0:19:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满满一屋子的奖杯  喜悦无人分享\NA room full of trophies and nobody to share them with?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.78,0:19:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼好像处理的不错啊\NDanny seems to have it figured out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.42,0:19:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩都不能成为你哥\NNeither of us are your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.08,0:19:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我想这话我都听了\NYeah, I think I've probably heard that one or two...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.17,0:19:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二十万遍了\N...hundred thousand times.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.79,0:19:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也不想成为像我哥那样的人\NBut he's not the brother I wanted to be like.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.61,0:19:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾编出一支傻傻的胜利之舞\NI once made up this whole goofy victory dance
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.13,0:19:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了向人们证明我也很幽默\Nso I could show people that I can be fun too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.12,0:19:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把它称为  维勒之舞\NI called it the Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.79,0:19:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后呢  -有人嘲笑我  我把它们狠揍一顿\N- What happened? - Somebody laughed and I decked them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.69,0:19:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实是  我想通过赢球能有所改变\NTruth. I was kind of looking forward to winning for a change.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.40,0:19:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前从没这样尝试过\NNever really tried it before.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.58,0:19:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你和斗士队\NI think you and the
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.39,0:19:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我也能找准方向\NBrawlers can figure out how to do it without me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.23,0:20:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧\NMaybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.91,0:20:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那有什么乐趣\NBut what fun would that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.18,0:20:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本  大家都不想我留下  -没关系  我想你留下\N- Ben, nobody wants me. - It doesn't matter. I want you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.94,0:20:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们还是跑吧  -同意  快跑\N- I think we should probably run. - Yeah, let's.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.36,0:20:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斗士队 万岁\NGo Brawlers!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.17,0:20:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们节节胜利  锐不可当\NWe're on a roll!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.61,0:20:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这多亏了我们可爱的副队长\NAll thanks to my lovely co-captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.09,0:20:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽特意去和裁判搞好关系 \NRiley even made up with the umpire.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.79,0:20:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果发现那家伙确实够眼瘸\NTurns out he really does need new glasses.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.10,0:20:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本  -妈妈  你也来为我们庆祝吗\N- Ben. - Mom. Come to help us celebrate?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.12,0:20:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  风声太紧  我来躲躲  亲爱的  你得帮我\NNo, more like hide out. Honey, you have to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.50,0:20:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-出了什么事  -妈  这个男人怎么样\N- What's wrong? - Mom, what about this guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.93,0:20:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我也说不好\NI don't know, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.32,0:20:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他眼里的恐惧会给他减分\NThe fear in his eyes is a bit of a turn off.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.19,0:20:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淘汰\NBeat it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.37,0:20:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边那个男的呢\NWhat about that guy over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.58,0:20:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你过来  别担心\NYou! Don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.09,0:20:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会找到让你幸福的男人的\NI'm gonna find a guy that makes you happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.73,0:20:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.67,0:20:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在好多了\NHe seems to be getting better.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.25,0:21:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多谢你跟他谈了  -你怎么知道\N- Thanks for talking to him. - How did you know--?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.64,0:21:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的儿子我当然了解\NI know my boy's work when I see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.29,0:21:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如我常说的  感谢上帝给了我本\NLike I always say, thank God for my Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.39,0:21:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跳维勒之舞  跳维勒之舞  -莱丽在干什么\N- Do the Wheeler, do the Wheeler... - What is Riley doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.38,0:21:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是她自己编的维勒之舞\NI believe it's called the Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.39,0:21:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  给她一美金  光看不给钱  太不厚道了\NHoney, throw her a dollar. Otherwise this is just sad.
