[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.57,0:00:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不错吧\NHuh? Amazing, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 \NYeah. 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.57,0:00:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卫生间\NBathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.74,0:00:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卧室\NBedrooms.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.97,0:00:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒\NNice.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.78,0:00:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来看别人卧室和卫生间的窗户\NViews of other bedrooms and bathrooms.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.20,0:00:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很感谢你让我在这留宿  老弟\NI really appreciate you letting me crash here, bud.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.30,0:00:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逗了  你来住算帮我们忙了\NAre you kidding? You're doing us a favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.02,0:00:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不冲厕所的托尼上周刚搬走\NNo flush Tony just moved out last week.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.32,0:00:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定这没问题吗\NYou're sure this isn't a problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.56,0:00:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  当我听说你被交易到游骑兵队时\NSeriously, the best day of my life
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.94,0:00:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真心的替你感到高兴\Nwas when I heard you got traded to the rangers.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.45,0:00:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我家人\NYou're family. 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.15,0:00:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的地盘就是你的地盘  老哥\NMy place is your place, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.34,0:00:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严格讲这是我的地盘\NTechnically, it's my place.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.48,0:00:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我再问你\NOkay, and next time I say,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"要不要帮把手的时候"\N"Hey, let me help you with that,"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.79,0:00:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请试着回答  "没关系  我自己能行"\Nlet's try "No thanks, I got it."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.53,0:00:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来像个吃货\NYou look like an eater.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.20,0:00:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我事先声明\NSo, just so we're clear,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.58,0:00:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左半边冰箱是我的\Nthe left side of the fridge is mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.65,0:00:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去开门吧  塔克尔  拜托\NI got it. Tucker, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.29,0:00:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我兄弟和我最好的哥们\NMy brother and my best friend--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.21,0:00:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再没有比这更好的了\NIt's never gonna get any better than this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.81,0:00:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们三个住一起\NThe three of us together,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何事情都不能成为阻碍\Nthere's nothing that's gonna stop us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.67,0:01:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计这个除外吧\NExcept for maybe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.45,0:01:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我门口有个婴儿\NThere's a baby on my doormat.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.98,0:01:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边  惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.03,0:01:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲  雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.57,0:01:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是打哪来的\NWhere did it come from?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.83,0:01:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\NI don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.65,0:01:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但把她放这的人应该还没走远\NBut whoever left it, they couldn't have gotten far.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.83,0:01:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实呆着  宝贝\NStay there, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.71,0:01:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好她\NMake sure she stays there!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.98,0:01:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想说\NI'm just saying,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.03,0:01:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一位刚生了宝宝的女人\Nfor a woman who just had a baby,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.62,0:01:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跑得可真够快的\Nshe moves remarkably fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.28,0:01:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么能把孩子放在这里\NHow could she just leave her here?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.53,0:01:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你需要冷静\NBen, you gotta calm down, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.97,0:01:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打保票她根本不是你的孩子\NI'm sure she's not even your baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.16,0:01:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是  这也有可能是你孩子  对吧\NExactly, you can just as easy be your baby, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.96,0:01:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计不能够吧...\NNot so much, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.57,0:01:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚来城里才一小时\NAnd I've only been in town an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.94,0:02:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的动作的确是快  但也...\NI mean, I'm fast, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.50,0:02:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可也没有这么快\NI'm not that fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.25,0:02:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我孩子\NThis is not my baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.74,0:02:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait, wait, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.85,0:02:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  有张便条\NGuys, we got a note.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.87,0:02:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫艾玛\NHer name's Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.44,0:02:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认识叫艾玛的\NI don't know any Emmas.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.32,0:02:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛是宝宝的名字\NThe baby's name is Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.84,0:02:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  艾玛\NHi, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.57,0:02:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我有没有跟你讲过\NHey, Ben. Did I ever tell you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.83,0:02:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾和一个叫艾玛的性感女服务生约会过\Nabout that hot waitress I went out with named Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.10,0:02:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  注意重点\NDanny, focus!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.65,0:02:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要知道妈妈是谁\NThe mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.59,0:02:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哦对  -谁是妈妈\N- Oh, yeah. - Who's the mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.64,0:02:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\NSorry, um,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.28,0:02:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉\NAngela.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.54,0:02:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉\NAngela!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.77,0:02:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然了  -这就对了\N- Of course. - That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.28,0:02:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉是谁\NWho is Angela?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.32,0:02:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很棒  是个女演员\NShe was nice. Actress.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.95,0:02:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩就是个疯子\NThat girl was crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.11,0:02:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说了什么其他的\NDoes it say anything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.46,0:02:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很抱歉\NUh, she's sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.21,0:02:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不知道该怎么做\NShe didn't know what else to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.46,0:02:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有她需要一点时间\NAnd she just needs a little time.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.07,0:02:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间  到底要多久\NTime? How much time?!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.16,0:02:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个时间倒还可以接受\NAnd that would be the perfect amount of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.43,0:02:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面是莱丽\NThat's Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.47,0:02:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在外面的时候我给她打了电话\NI gave her a call while you were outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.94,0:02:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽\NRiley?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.19,0:02:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是大裤衩佩林吗\NFatpants Perrin?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.39,0:03:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来干什么\NWhat's she doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.51,0:03:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有叫大裤衩的朋友吗\NYou have a friend named Fatpants?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.10,0:03:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  我可得看紧我的食物了\NOh, I'm definitely marking my food. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.97,0:03:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽现在进了法学院\NRiley's in law school now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.59,0:03:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这花了她不少功夫\NIt took her a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.77,0:03:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜入学考试可能有点难\NI guess the LSAT's kind of tricky,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.20,0:03:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是相信我  她会知道该怎么做\Nbut trust me, she will know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.40,0:03:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱巨怪\NRi-Gantor?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.74,0:03:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本大湿\NBen-wetter!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.64,0:03:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧你\NLook at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.34,0:03:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去真漂亮\NYou look amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.12,0:03:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做到的\NHow did that happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.89,0:03:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我减掉了一两磅吧\NI may have lost a pound or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是几百磅吧\NHundred.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.00,0:03:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那次骑我脑袋上\NYou sat on my head and gave me
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.34,0:03:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成我脑震荡了  记得吗\Na concussion, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.42,0:03:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  这是莱丽  莱丽  这是塔克尔\NTuck, Riley. Riley, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.10,0:03:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHi.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.13,0:03:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽从小就在我们对街长大\NRiley grew up across the street from us
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.69,0:03:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常常都能把本打得\Nand used to kick the crap out of Ben
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.98,0:03:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去意识\Nevery day of his life.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.37,0:03:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺你进了法学院\NOh, and congrats on the law school thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.02,0:03:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -不用担心  我听说很多人\N- Thanks. - Don't worry--I know a bunch
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.31,0:03:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进这个学校都很费劲\Nof people that had a hard time getting in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.29,0:03:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟他说这个干什么\NWhy did you tell him that?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.25,0:03:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也没做\NI didn't do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.90,0:04:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  小公主\NHey, it's okay, princess.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.75,0:04:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不抱抱她吗\NAren't you gonna pick her up?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.19,0:04:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗\NMe?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.02,0:04:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这帮人一看到胸\NWhat, you guys see breasts
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.10,0:04:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就马上想到妈妈吗\Nand instantly think mommy?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.05,0:04:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.01,0:04:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  小天使\NCome here, angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.42,0:04:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHi.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.84,0:04:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\NBelieve me,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.13,0:04:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道在一个陌生的地方醒来\NI know how scary it is to wake up
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.55,0:04:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一件多么惊悚的事情\Nin a strange place.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.80,0:04:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是闲聊一下罢了\NI'm just making conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.75,0:04:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你饿吗\NAre you hungry?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.85,0:04:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你肯定饿了\NI bet you're hungry, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.89,0:04:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你都有些什么\NLet's see what you got--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.05,0:04:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就带来这么点东西吗\NIs this all you brought with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.33,0:04:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  没关系\NOh, well, that's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.74,0:04:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们叫一个男生去买点必需品  同时...\NWe'll just send one of these boys out for provisions and--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.55,0:04:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我需要一个人给她换尿布\NI think somebody needs her diaper changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.70,0:04:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去买东西\NI'll go to the store.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.44,0:05:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去\NYeah, I'm going, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.42,0:05:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.16,0:05:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生们好傻  是不是\NBoys are so stupid, aren't they?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.97,0:05:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\NYes, they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.46,0:05:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们真傻\NThey're so stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.12,0:05:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真傻\NYes, they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.51,0:05:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  接下来你只要\NAll right, so then you just
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.13,0:05:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把护翼向下贴紧\Nstick the tabs down,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.65,0:05:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  这样就好了\Nand voila, she's good to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.83,0:05:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去装奶瓶  你抱一会儿没问题吧\NHold her while I get her bottle ready, would you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.46,0:05:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抱她吗\NUh, me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.00,0:05:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不怎么会带孩子\NI'm not really a baby person.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.84,0:05:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着\NHold her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.61,0:05:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺有趣不是吗\NIsn't this fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.83,0:05:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样\NThere you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.30,0:05:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是想  走过来歇下\NWant to maybe, uh, take a step over here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.01,0:05:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还好吗\NIs she okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.94,0:05:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下\NHave a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.34,0:05:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢的  放轻松\NNice and easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.63,0:06:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她开心吗\NIs she having fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.00,0:06:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.99,0:06:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩看起来都挺享受\NYou guys look comfy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.09,0:06:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是不敢相信这一切\NI can't believe this is happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.52,0:06:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没做好当父亲的准备呢\NI'm not ready to be a dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.43,0:06:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果安吉拉一直不回来怎么办\NWhat if Angela never comes back?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.94,0:06:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  尝尝这个\NOh, my God, taste this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.83,0:06:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡肉  胡萝卜  意面\NChicken, carrots, and pasta. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.26,0:06:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全在这小罐子里\NAll in this little jar.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.44,0:06:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点荒唐  但却很美味\NIt's like, gross, yet oddly delicious.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.64,0:06:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  伙计  会好起来的\NCome on, man. It's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.14,0:06:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\NHow do you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.88,0:06:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  但也只能这么说了\NI don't, but it's all I got.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.04,0:06:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问\NExcuse me,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.89,0:06:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的宝宝多大\Nhow old is your baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.56,0:06:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问得好\NOh, um... That's a good question.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.03,0:06:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在村里的派对上认识的安吉拉\NI met Angela at that party in the village...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.78,0:06:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们大概交往了六个月\Nand we dated for maybe six weeks
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.52,0:06:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到我们...  干柴烈火\Nbefore we were...intimate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.95,0:07:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她差不多就在那之后\NAnd she broke up with me
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.19,0:07:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我分手了\Npretty much right after that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.10,0:07:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢保证两件事没什么直接关系\NI'm sure there was no correlation.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.92,0:07:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是八月份\NSo, we're into August now,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.48,0:07:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀孕大概需要九个月吧\Nand they take, like, nine months once they're up and running.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.95,0:07:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是的\NI think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.22,0:07:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以宝宝现在是...\NSo...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.03,0:07:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个月大\NThree months.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.12,0:07:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个月\NThree months!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.54,0:07:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝宝有三个月大了\NMy baby's three months old.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.10,0:07:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-把这个放回去  -什么\N- Put this back. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.48,0:07:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还没长牙呢\NShe ain't got no teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.41,0:07:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放回去\NPut it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.89,0:07:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本的首要任务就是\NSo, the first thing Ben has to do
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.77,0:07:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去做个亲子鉴定\Nis take a paternity test.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.60,0:07:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说\NI mean,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.93,0:07:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很明显这孩子就是他的\Nthough it's pretty obvious she's his.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.29,0:07:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样的笑容\NSame smile,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.63,0:07:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样的耳朵\Nsame ears,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.21,0:07:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连虹膜里那闪闪的黄色小斑点也一样\Nsame little sparkly fleck of yellow in the iris.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.78,0:07:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.45,0:07:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我鼻子上有东西吗\NDo I have something in my nose?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.51,0:08:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就知道你们会觉得这很逗\NI know you guys think that's funny,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.70,0:08:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实一点也不笑好吗\Nbut it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.17,0:08:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢本\NYou like Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.14,0:08:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.34,0:08:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢  别胡说\NNo, that's insane.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.69,0:08:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪一天没折磨他呀\NI've tormented the guy every day of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.42,0:08:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我勒个去  你真的喜欢本\NHoly crap! You really do like Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.09,0:08:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回来咯\NWe're back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.17,0:08:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  真是说了你都不信\NHey. Ben, you're not gonna believe
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.65,0:08:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽刚刚...\Nwhat Riley was just--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.58,0:08:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东西都买齐了吗\NHow'd it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.20,0:08:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们走了\NYou guys left
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.04,0:08:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才想到应该给你们列张购物清单的\Nand I realized I should have given you a list.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.38,0:08:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥  我是说  地球人都知道\NWhy? I mean, everyone knows
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.80,0:08:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能给还没满四个月\Nyou're not supposed to give a baby solid food
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.75,0:08:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连坐都坐不稳的孩子吃固体食物\Nuntil it's at least four months old and sitting up on its own.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.64,0:08:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女的真是刻薄\NThat woman was mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.04,0:08:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这位应该吃饱了\NI think we're all done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.99,0:08:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOh, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.39,0:08:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再打个饱嗝  她就算完事了\NJust one good belch and she's done.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.83,0:08:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你可以搞得定接下来的了\NI think you can handle this part.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.17,0:08:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  我  现在  你确定吗\NWhat, me? Right now? Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.13,0:08:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NHey, Tucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.66,0:08:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOh, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.21,0:08:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很好  丹尼  -有事吗\N- Great. Danny? - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.46,0:08:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这里你负责  -等等\N- You're in charge. - Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.47,0:08:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是要走了吧\NYou're not leaving, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.31,0:08:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -不行  我会听话  我保证\N- Yes. - No, I'll be good. I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.84,0:08:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么弄我都已经交给你了\NI showed you how to do everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.15,0:08:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但是我根本没留心听\NYeah, but I wasn't paying attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.82,0:08:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能走\NYou can't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.87,0:08:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  让莱丽不要走\NBen, tell Riley she can't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.41,0:08:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不能走  -拜拜了\N- You can't go. - Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.59,0:08:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  哇哦  本\NOoh, wow, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.28,0:08:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还从没发现你的双眸原来这么闪亮呢\NI never noticed how sparkly your eyes are.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.26,0:09:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  莱丽\NPlease, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.33,0:09:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚要是没你在我们肯定搞不定的\NWe'll never make it through the night without you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.02,0:09:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我留下\NFine. I'll stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.04,0:09:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧见没  我想说的就是这个\NSee? That's what I'm talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.93,0:09:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  她没有吐到\NRight? Hey, she didn't spit up
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.06,0:09:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的衣服上吧\Non my shirt though, did she?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.51,0:09:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  挺好  -没  没  你挺好的\N- No, looks good. - No, no, you're great.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.62,0:09:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟新的一样  老兄\NBrand new, bud.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.87,0:09:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.51,0:09:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我五点之前应该能回来\NI should be back by five.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.67,0:09:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你要去哪里\NWait. Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.90,0:09:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去上班  轮班到我了\NUh, work. I got a shift.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.10,0:09:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你就不能找人顶你一下吗\NWait, you couldn't get anyone to cover for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.76,0:09:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确是个好主意\NOh, see, that would have been a good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.64,0:09:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过太迟了\NToo late now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.56,0:09:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  老弟\NNo, wait, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.44,0:09:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和塔克尔可不是你孩子的保姆\NTuck and I are not watching your kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.79,0:09:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  大块头说得没错\NYeah. The big guy's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.27,0:09:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说没有人...\NI mean, there is no--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.46,0:10:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  老哥  再见\NThanks, man. See you!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.72,0:10:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么悲催的总是我\NHow does this keep happening to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.93,0:10:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺有一手的嘛\NWow. Very impressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.15,0:10:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁说你身无所长来着\NAnd who said you had no discernable skills?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.51,0:10:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是你说的吧\NI think that was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.82,0:10:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  我该怎么办\NRiley, what am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.73,0:10:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在安吉拉回来之前\NWell, there's not really that much we can do
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.70,0:10:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们也做不了什么\Nuntil Angela comes back.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.93,0:10:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我觉得咱们应该谈谈\NBut I think we should probably talk about
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.36,0:10:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房里那个大麻烦了\Nthe elephant in the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.95,0:10:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算与我无关了\NWhich for once isn't me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.40,0:10:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想和这孩子扯上关系吗\NHow much do you want to be involved?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.79,0:10:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道我想不想\NI don't know what I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.66,0:10:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年  我还在当建筑工人\NLast year, I was doing construction.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.71,0:10:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前  我是做侍应生\NBefore that, I was waiting tables.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.10,0:10:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我又在这里耍瓶子\NNow I'm flipping bottles.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.96,0:10:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己的生活我都还没理清呢\NI haven't figured my life out yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.55,0:10:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你\NI'm not you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.63,0:10:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话什么意思\NWhat does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.57,0:10:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧\NOh! Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.23,0:10:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上大学\NCollege,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.33,0:10:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还考进法学院  还有这...\Nlaw school, this...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.04,0:10:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这番脱胎换骨\NTransformation.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.87,0:11:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞅准了想要的就会努力去争取\NYou see what you want and you go for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.51,0:11:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.07,0:11:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是总有勇气\NNot always.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.65,0:11:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰块掉进我的文胸里面了\NIce down my bra.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.18,0:11:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉以前我总是骑在你的头上作威作福\NI'm really sorry I sat on your head all those times.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.00,0:11:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉回来了\NAngela's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.20,0:11:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我休息一下  伙计\NI'm on break, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.30,0:11:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉我总是骑在你头上\NI'm sorry I sat on your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.43,0:11:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算说出来了  大裤衩  是啊  \NSmooth move, Fatpants. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.54,0:11:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪儿  安吉拉呢\NWhere is she? Where's Angela?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.82,0:11:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  她把孩子叫醒了\NFirst of all, she woke up the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.57,0:11:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着  她叫我把那个信封交给你\NSecond, she wanted me to give you that envelope.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.88,0:11:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然就这样让她走了\NYou let her leave?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.82,0:11:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有毛病吧\NWhat's the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.96,0:11:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\NOh, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.18,0:11:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错  因为我要忙着给你看孩子呢  \NMy bad, but I was a little preoccupied raising your child.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.76,0:11:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看那封信吧  我想你会高兴的\NRead it. I think you'll be happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.05,0:11:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是领养文件\NThey're adoption papers.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.89,0:11:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想让人领养艾玛\NShe's putting Emma up for adoption
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.17,0:11:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我放弃抚养权\Nand she needs me to relinquish my rights.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.76,0:11:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我签了这份文件  我就不是孩子她爸了\NIf I sign this, I'm not a father anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.18,0:11:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒吧\NAmazing, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.96,0:12:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧见没  我不是一个人在激动\NWell, see, I'm not the only one who's excited.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.45,0:12:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说  我签了这个  艾玛就有个新老爸了\NSo, I sign this and Emma has a new daddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.10,0:12:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\NPretty much.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.08,0:12:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信上说已经有个家庭想领养了\NThe letter says they already have a family lined up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.30,0:12:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我签了\NIf I do this,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.42,0:12:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她送走\Nif I let her go,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.71,0:12:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就再也不想听到关于她的事了\NI don't want to hear about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.91,0:12:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想这件事再被提起  明白吗\NI never want to talk about it again, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.70,0:12:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -没问题\N- Okay. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.41,0:12:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝小乖孙女在哪里\NWhere is my precious little grandbaby?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.56,0:12:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  你来这里做什么\NMom, what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.30,0:12:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当奶奶了\NI'm a grandma!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.21,0:12:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来这里做什么\NWhat is she doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.17,0:12:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你跟她说的吗\NDid you tell her?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.01,0:12:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没跟她说我在这里\NI didn't even tell her I was here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.74,0:12:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会儿再找你算账\NOh, I'll get to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.48,0:12:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真是个超级小可爱呢\NOh, she is just a big ol' pile of love.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  不过你闻到的气味就不那么可爱了\NYeah, I really don't think that's love that you're smelling.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.22,0:13:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  谁能跟我解释下\NOkay, who wants to explain to me
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.70,0:13:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥我得在修指甲的时候\Nwhy I had to hear that I was a grandma
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.81,0:13:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从别人那里得知我当奶奶了\Nwhile I was getting my nails done?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.50,0:13:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个珍妮弗·佩林[莱丽母亲]巴不得快点告诉我呢\NThat Jennifer Perrin couldn't wait to let me have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.14,0:13:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从她家的大裤衩女儿\NEver since that Fatpants daughter of hers
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.95,0:13:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进了法学院她就...\Ngot into law school she's just--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.53,0:13:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  莱丽\NHi, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.81,0:13:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没看到你在那里\NI didn't see you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.61,0:13:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在苗条极了  应该在身上系个铃铛的\NYou're so thin now, you should wear a bell.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.97,0:13:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是管道胶带吗\NIs this duct tape?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.73,0:13:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们粘不上尿布嘛\NWe were having a closure issue.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.83,0:13:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们就不能找个订书机吗\NOh, what, you couldn't find a stapler?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.43,0:13:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的\NHonestly.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.79,0:13:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在不能签那些文件\NI can't sign those papers now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.38,0:13:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会签的\NIt's not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.31,0:13:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心老妈那边\NHey, don't worry about mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.70,0:13:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要做你认为对的事情就行了\NYou gotta do what you think is right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.09,0:13:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对挺你\NI'll totally back you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.60,0:13:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么文件\NWhat papers?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.68,0:13:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你等死吧  老弟\NYou're on your own, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.33,0:13:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈\NMom...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.99,0:14:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点事要跟你说\NI have some news.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.27,0:14:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧  是你因为没什么避孕常识\NYeah. You knocked up some girl
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.85,0:14:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而搞大了某个女生肚子的事吧\Nbecause you couldn't figure out the basics of birth control.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.71,0:14:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事我已经知道了  亲爱的  好吗\NWe're past that, honey, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.44,0:14:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒太太\NMrs. Wheeler?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.09,0:14:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邦妮\NBonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.88,0:14:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-叫我啥  -维勒太太\N- Really? - Mrs. Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.35,0:14:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛的妈妈想要把她送去领养机构\NEmma's mom wants to put Emma up for adoption
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.40,0:14:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并叫本放弃孩子的抚养权\Nand for Ben to sign away his rights.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.49,0:14:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\NReally?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.60,0:14:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你想\NSo you're--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.22,0:14:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃这个小家伙的抚养权\Nyou're thinking about giving up this little girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.76,0:14:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我正在考虑\NYeah, I was thinking about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.43,0:14:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了\NOh, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.13,0:14:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  这话什么意思\NGood-- what do you mean, good?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.27,0:14:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  亲爱的\NOh, Ben, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.78,0:14:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不明白\NYou can't begin to understand
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.59,0:14:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当人爸妈要做出多大的牺牲\Nthe kind of sacrifice it takes to be a parent.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.36,0:14:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嫁给你老爸没多久\NWhen I married your father,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.60,0:14:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就生了你们两个\Nand I had you two,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.46,0:14:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我不得不把我自己的梦想放一边\NI had to put my dreams on hold.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.22,0:14:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么梦想  -做个没孩子的单身贵族\N- What dreams? - Being single and childless.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.32,0:14:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.71,0:14:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我爱你\NHoney, I love you,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.16,0:14:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你养不了这个小女孩\Nbut you can't raise this little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.26,0:14:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至都养不了自己\NYou haven't even finished raising yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.53,0:14:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会做饭\NYou can't cook,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.49,0:14:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勉强付得了账单\Nyou're barely paying your bills...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.50,0:15:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  还是我给你买的裤子\NHoney, I still buy your pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.60,0:15:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个孩子需要成年人抚养\NThis baby needs a grown-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.89,0:15:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得把文件签了\NYou gotta sign those papers.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.34,0:15:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九点\N9 am.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.80,0:15:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会准备好的\NShe'll be ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.94,0:15:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成\NDone.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.41,0:15:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领养机构的人\NSomebody from the adoption agency
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.94,0:15:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大早就来\Nwill be here first thing in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.57,0:15:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧\NYou okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.55,0:15:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  为什么不好\NYeah, why wouldn't I be?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.96,0:15:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  如果你不愿意这样做\NBen, if you don't want to do this, man--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.52,0:15:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓了\NIt doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.92,0:15:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈说的对\NMom was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.63,0:15:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使我想  我也养不了这个孩子\NI couldn't raise this baby even if I wanted to.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.12,0:15:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  没事的\NBro, it's going to be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.19,0:15:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情发生了\NIt happened,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.30,0:15:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也处理了\Nyou dealt with it,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.20,0:15:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在呢  就像你说的\Nand now, like you said,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.65,0:15:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再也不提这件事了\Nwe're never talking about this again.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.56,0:15:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本可以成为模特的\NI could have been a model.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.74,0:15:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你也见过丹尼叔叔\NBut you've seen your uncle Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.50,0:15:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.93,0:15:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生他喂他以后哪还有身材\NNo body could recover from that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.49,0:15:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那么大块头\NHe was so big,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.06,0:16:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得做剖"肚"产手术\NI had to have a "C," "D," And "E" Section.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.11,0:16:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我没有  我发誓\NNo, don't. I swear to God.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.34,0:16:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧好吧  -不  我会伤到你的\N- Okay. Okay. - No, I will hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.13,0:16:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.62,0:16:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么\NSo...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.23,0:16:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直都喜欢本吗\NDid you always like Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.33,0:16:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你太执着了吧\NOh, my God, you're obsessed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.82,0:16:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  有点吧\NI don't know. Kind of.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.40,0:16:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想着或许能有这么一天\NGuess I always thought maybe someday,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.88,0:16:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但以前我觉得\Nbut back then I just figured
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.94,0:16:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太胖  太...\NI was too fat, or too--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.65,0:16:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太吵  太多毛  太...\Nloud, or too hairy, or--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.62,0:16:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  又不是在列清单\NOkay, we're not making a list.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.95,0:16:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经出落成一个漂亮  成功的女人了\NWell, you've grown to be a beautiful and successful woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.85,0:16:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你可以安然的放下本·维勒了\NI think you can safely move on from Ben Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.09,0:16:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我干嘛要放下\NWhy would I want to do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.20,0:16:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是错过孩子那段儿了\NUh, did you miss the part in the story about the baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.82,0:16:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不愿意弃养的那个孩子吗\NThe baby he doesn't want to give up?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.63,0:16:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那样  他又为什么打那个电话呢\NIf that's true, then why did he make that call?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.71,0:16:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为家人都说他养不了\NBecause his entire family is telling him he can't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.07,0:16:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是没人相信他\NIf nobody believes in him,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.20,0:16:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他又怎么会相信自己呢\Nhow can he believe in himself?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.45,0:16:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一个人的确养不了\NHe can't do it alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.06,0:16:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能妄下定论\NYou don't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.21,0:16:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本的电话\NOh, it's Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.48,0:16:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈要走了  他就一个人看孩子了\NYour mom's about to leave him alone with the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.72,0:16:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去吗\NYou're going?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.82,0:17:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键词  "一个人"\N"Alone" is in all caps.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.77,0:17:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛掐我\NWhat was that for?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.61,0:17:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你让我聊感情了\NFor making me talk about my feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.25,0:17:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不喜欢的\NYou know I hate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.96,0:17:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你弟弟好一点  行吗\NAnd go easy on your brother, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.17,0:17:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很崇拜你\NHe looks up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.03,0:17:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他眼里  你拥有一切\NIn his eyes, you have everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.24,0:17:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非如此...\NNot everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.88,0:17:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等等\NWait, wait, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.71,0:17:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-等等  -天啊\N- Wait. - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.73,0:17:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你等我一分钟\NYou-- you gotta give me a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.00,0:17:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我现在明白为何被交易到其他队伍里了\NMaybe now I know why I was traded.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.92,0:17:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的对\NYou were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.62,0:17:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前不相信他\NI didn't believe in him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.51,0:17:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他做不了\NI didn't think he could do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.50,0:17:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么跟我说呢\NSo why are you telling me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.97,0:17:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为...\NBecause...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.29,0:17:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你走进去帮他\NIf you go in there and help him,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.60,0:17:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他永远不会相信自己了\Nhe'll never believe in himself, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.78,0:17:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  莱丽  莱丽  求你了\NRiley, Riley, Riley, Riley, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.51,0:17:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她饿了  或者渴了  或者累了\NShe's hungry, or thirsty, or tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.80,0:17:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我又不会说婴语\NI don't know, I don't speak baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.59,0:18:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.83,0:18:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\NWhat is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.01,0:18:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和瓦内萨正看电影呢\NVanessa and I were at the movies
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.28,0:18:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本打来电话\Nwhen Ben called and said
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.19,0:18:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说艾玛正在受灾受难\NEmma's having some kind of meltdown.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.78,0:18:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不是艾玛出事了\NI don't think Emma's the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.74,0:18:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  两秒钟之内你要是不回来\NTucker, I swear if you're not home in two seconds...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.12,0:18:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓我就吃光你的食物\NI'm gonna eat all your food.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.37,0:18:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTucker?!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.16,0:18:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关机啊\NTurn it off!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.43,0:18:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.99,0:18:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来只有你和我了  是吧\NSo, it looks like it's just gonna be you and me, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.34,0:18:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们真的要一起来完成这件事了\NGuess we're really gonna do this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.71,0:18:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.96,0:18:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  艾玛  嗨\NOkay, Emma, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.51,0:18:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  宝贝\NHi, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.13,0:18:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  没事的\NCome on, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.14,0:18:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你别有事啊  拜托你可别有事啊\NPlease don't break, please don't break,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.54,0:18:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了别有事啊\Nplease don't break.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.01,0:18:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.07,0:19:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  没事的\NOkay. It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.04,0:19:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.09,0:19:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.56,0:19:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  艾玛\NIt's okay, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.50,0:19:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸在呢\NDaddy's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.89,0:19:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.26,0:19:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.01,0:19:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你  不可能的事儿\NI'm telling you, there is no way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.33,0:19:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些排泄物会让他呕吐的\NBodily functions make him queasy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.60,0:19:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他能行的\NHe can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.83,0:19:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你信仰哪儿去了  哥们\NWhere's your faith, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.21,0:19:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧\NSee?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.29,0:19:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄好了\NHere you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.27,0:19:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\NThere.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.96,0:19:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.62,0:19:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛\NEmma?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.89,0:19:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你吃吧\NPlease eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.34,0:19:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  艾玛\NCome on, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.21,0:19:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊  看啊  艾玛  很好吃\NLook, look, Emma, it's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.63,0:19:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃\NIt's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.71,0:20:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睁眼说瞎话\NOh, total lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.47,0:20:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太恶心了\NIt's actually quite disgusting.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.10,0:20:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪你不想吃\NNo wonder you don't want to eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.34,0:20:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你吃吧\NPlease eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.64,0:20:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  艾玛  吃一小口  好吗\NCome on, Emma. Just a sip, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.97,0:20:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托啦\NCome on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.64,0:20:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  快吃啊\NOkay, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.36,0:20:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你得吃东西啊\NCome on, you have to eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.74,0:20:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求你了\NI'm begging you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.62,0:20:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快...\NCome--
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.83,0:20:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.33,0:20:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢吗\NYou like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.44,0:20:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看爸爸多能耐啊\NLook what daddy can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.09,0:20:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天上班我都做这个\NI do this at work every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.41,0:20:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想吃了吗\NYou want some now?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.13,0:20:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想吃吗\NYou want some?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.51,0:20:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃的来啦\NHere it comes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.74,0:20:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃的来啦  宝贝\NHere it comes, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.87,0:20:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你在吃啦\NOh, my God, you're eating.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.26,0:21:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太谢谢你了\NThank you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.36,0:21:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我擦\NHoly crap,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.61,0:21:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都哭了\Nnow I'm crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.25,0:21:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擦  不要说擦这个词\NCrap. Don't say crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.06,0:21:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说脏话\NDon't use swear words.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.89,0:21:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你在吃东西了\NOh, I can't believe you're eating.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.84,0:21:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太可爱了\NYou're so cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.86,0:21:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒\NHey, wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.11,0:21:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  你口水流我身上了\NDude, you're drooling on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.68,0:21:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧\NYou okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.13,0:21:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.65,0:21:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想抚养这个孩子\NI think I want to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.42,0:21:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能放手\NI can't let her go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.98,0:21:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱她\NI love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.96,0:21:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们听见我说什么了吗\NDid you guys hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.41,0:21:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.36,0:21:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们听见了\NYeah, we heard you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.48,0:21:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该给领养机构打电话了吧\NYou should probably call the agency.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.81,0:21:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快七点了\NIt's almost 7:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.99,0:22:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来吧  我的小宝贝\NCome on, mi amor.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.75,0:22:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来呀\NHere we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.78,0:22:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人该洗澡澡喽\NOoh, somebody could use a bath.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.08,0:22:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都该洗洗了\NOh. You both could.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.18,0:22:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去冲一瓶奶\NI'm gonna go get a bottle ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.27,0:22:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我想亲自喂她  行吗\NBut I want to give it to her, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.37,0:22:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的得制定个\NWe're really gonna have to get
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.53,0:22:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝计划了\Non some kind of schedule though.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.71,0:22:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说真的  -什么意思\N- For real. - What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.92,0:22:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在都有孩子了\NWell, we have a baby now so I mean,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.77,0:22:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意思是  我们得成熟点了\Nwe kind of have to be adults.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.07,0:22:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  购物我包了\NOkay. I'll do the shopping.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.54,0:22:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  但我们得先谈谈...\NOkay, but let's talk about...
