[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.28,0:00:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信这一天终于来了\NI can't believe this day is finally here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.96,0:00:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有不到24小时我们就要走红地毯了\NWe are walking down the aisle in less than 24 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.05,0:00:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有23小时让你记住\NWhich gives you less than 23 hours to remember
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.95,0:00:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是新娘\Nyou're not the bride.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.15,0:00:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\NI know,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.83,0:00:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但凯蒂选我做伴娘是有原因的\Nbut Katie picked me to be her maid of honor for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.22,0:00:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计是因为她没有别的朋友了\NI figured it was because she didn't have any other friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.04,0:00:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是了\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.48,0:00:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是没有多少朋友\NWell, not a lot,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.99,0:00:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她选我是知道我能把这事做好\Nbut she knew I would get the job done.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.91,0:00:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.75,0:00:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做的好好哦\NAnd you are doing such an awesome job
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.23,0:00:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那么多杏仁塞进这么女孩子气的袋袋里\Nshoving hundreds of almonds into little girly bags.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.79,0:00:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  原来是我在塞呢\NOh, wait. These are my hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.76,0:00:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特喜欢婚礼  好吧\NHey, I love a wedding, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.64,0:00:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充斥着一种很感人的东西\NThere's just something so emotional.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.25,0:00:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当女士们开始对我投怀送抱的时候\NWhen the ladies start throwing themselves at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.85,0:00:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照以往的惯例\NHey, hey. If history is any indication,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.94,0:00:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会排着队接受\Nthey will be lining up for a second helping
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.07,0:00:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自塔克尔·巴菲特的加餐\Nfrom the Tucker Buffet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.85,0:00:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂我在说什么吧\NYou know what I'm saying? Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.00,0:00:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们觉得怎么样\NWhat do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.66,0:01:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NDanny?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.72,0:01:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是干嘛呢\NWhat are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.57,0:01:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试嘛\NBreaking it in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.06,0:01:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是一股上一个穿它的人的味道\NStill kind of smells like the last guy who wore it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.66,0:01:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  不要啊\NDanny, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.79,0:01:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过让你穿得有品位一点\NI told you to get something classy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.43,0:01:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我里面还要穿衬衫呢\NDon't worry. I'm gonna wear a shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.94,0:01:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面还有花边呢\NIt's even got ruffles.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.15,0:01:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抢戏伴娘  你好\NHey, maidzilla.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.71,0:01:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都在尽力好吗\NWe're all doing the best that we can here, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.78,0:01:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  搞定\NAll right, done.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.82,0:01:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThank you!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.22,0:01:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尽力也就这样了\NOkay, actually that was my best.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.16,0:01:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁你们有空我插一个小问题\NOne other quick thing while you have a moment,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.80,0:01:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有办法把我和吉恩安排到同一桌\Nis there any way you can put me and Gene at the same table?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.94,0:01:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉恩\NGene?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.08,0:01:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女更衣室的死猪  吉恩吗\NPig in the girls' locker room Gene?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.93,0:01:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的三角绷带里放辣椒粉的吉恩吗\NChili powder in my jock strap Gene?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.38,0:01:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的秋海棠里呕吐的吉恩\NBarf in my begonias Gene?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.27,0:01:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就是那个吉恩\NYeah. That Gene.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.13,0:01:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  绝对不行  我们没邀请他\NNo, no way. He was not invited.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.20,0:01:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我也觉得挺奇怪的\NI know. I thought that was weird, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:01:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我带他去\NSo he's my plus one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.75,0:01:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你带我呢\NI thought I was your plus one?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.22,0:02:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以让丹尼带你去\NYou can be Danny's plus one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.63,0:02:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么我就要带他呢\NWhy does he have to be mine?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.78,0:02:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带牛肉和鸡肉\NI was gonna get the beef and the chicken.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.05,0:02:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  谁都不能带人去了\NAll right, listen. No one is getting a plus one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.74,0:02:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我不系这些粉色蝴蝶结了\NOh, well then I am done tying these little pink bows.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.59,0:02:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会找个时机带着我的小惊悚现身的\NI will come up with something a little more threatening in a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.24,0:02:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以来\NYou can come.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.30,0:02:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是吉恩没戏\NBut Gene cannot.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.94,0:02:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我们打算把婚礼搞得气派高档一点\NBen, this is supposed to be a dignified and classy affair.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.81,0:02:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\NAll right, there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.24,0:02:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来人啊  新娘摔倒了\NBride down, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.42,0:02:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新娘摔倒了\NBride down.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.88,0:02:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚礼会很高档的\NAnd it will be classy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.19,0:02:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中以后吉恩就改变了\NGene's changed a lot since high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.32,0:02:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都变了\NWe all have.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.05,0:02:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他个机会吧  求你了\NGive him a chance, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.55,0:02:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NUgh. Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.79,0:02:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是丑话说在前面  如果他\NBut I am warning you, if that guy even--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.18,0:02:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我是莱丽\NHello? Hi, this is Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.44,0:02:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.58,0:02:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能这么做\NNo, you can't!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.34,0:02:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就是婚礼的大日子了\NBut the wedding is tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.88,0:02:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  这是办婚宴的人\NOh my God, it's the caterer.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.26,0:02:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要取消服务\NThey're canceling.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.68,0:02:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\NUh, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.20,0:02:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上  我是个律师\NI am practically a lawyer,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.99,0:02:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果明天你不来\Nand if you are not there tomorrow
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.13,0:03:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且带着500个三文鱼丸  我就告你\Nwith 500 salmon croquettes, I will sue--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.85,0:03:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  告我吗\NWhat? Sue me?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.67,0:03:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉恩\NGene.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.61,0:03:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗到你啦\NGotcha!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.28,0:03:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我恨死他了\NGod, I hate that guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.58,0:03:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边 惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.09,0:03:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲 雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions*
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.05,0:03:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仍然不敢相信你竟然邀请吉恩参加婚礼\NI still can't believe you invited Gene to the wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.95,0:03:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想什么呢\NWhat were you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.22,0:03:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那样会有意思得多\NI was thinking it would be fun
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.72,0:03:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邀请一个本身就很\Nto invite somebody who was actually...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.94,0:03:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣的人\NFun.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.08,0:03:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我你已经为今晚的彩排晚餐\NJust please tell me you have everything all set up
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.05,0:03:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做足了准备\Nfor tonight's rehearsal dinner?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.45,0:03:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切就绪  我再拿点冰就行了\NWe're good. I just need to get some ice.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.57,0:03:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来点酒水\NAnd some liquor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.02,0:03:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差几个杯子\NAnd maybe some cups.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.29,0:03:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你怎么啦\NBen, ugh. What is your problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.36,0:03:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道  真抱歉\NI don't know, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.44,0:03:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉他们进展得太快了\NIt just feels like they're rushing into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.84,0:03:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从11岁就开始约会了\NThey've been dating since they were 11.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.49,0:03:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得这很吓人吗\NDoesn't that freak you out a little?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.67,0:03:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都一样大\NWe're the same age.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.10,0:03:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道你有多传统了\NOh, well, we all know how traditional you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.26,0:03:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝宝怎么样啊\NHey, how's your baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.65,0:04:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽啊\NSo, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.47,0:04:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中毕业以后你才变热辣  可惜了啊\NToo bad you waited until after high school to get hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.67,0:04:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不然的话  咱俩就好了\NOtherwise, it would have been you and me
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.07,0:04:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪轮得到你和本啊\Ninstead of you and my boy Ben here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.43,0:04:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和莱丽\NOh, me and Riley?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.53,0:04:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不是  我们只是普通朋友\NNo, no, no, no. We're just friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.92,0:04:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和本在一起\NYeah, me and Ben together?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.67,0:04:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太疯狂了\NThat would be crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.18,0:04:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说你还单着呢\NOh, so you're available?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.62,0:04:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次声明  我会出现在婚礼上的\NAnd once again, I've shown up to the party
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.98,0:04:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要多及时有多及时\Njust in time.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.84,0:04:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也再次声明  没人邀请你\NAnd once again, you are not invited.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.26,0:04:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒\NSo, Wheeler...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.03,0:04:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们编个什么故事忽悠今晚来的女士们啊\NWhat's our back-story for the ladies tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.92,0:04:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,华尔街巨子还是脑外科医生\NWe Wall Street moguls or brain surgeons?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.92,0:04:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样如何\NWhat about this--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.88,0:04:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是脑外科医生\NI'm a brain surgeon,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.04,0:04:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我救的一个华尔街巨子\Nand you're a Wall Street mogul whose life I just saved.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.11,0:04:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你医生\NThank you, doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.59,0:04:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将永远感激你\NI'm eternally grateful.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.40,0:04:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能相信吗\NCan you believe it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.72,0:04:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的要结婚啦\NAah! I am actually getting married.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.09,0:04:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂的\NI know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.07,0:04:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能不能占用你几分钟\NBut if I could just get a few minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.68,0:04:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你全神贯注地过一遍\Nof your undivided attention
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.82,0:04:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终确定的细节\Nto go over some of these last minute details--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.21,0:04:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-任凭你差遣  -太好了\N- I am all yours. - Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.96,0:04:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  我们要\N So, first off, we have-- -
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.71,0:05:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫给我发的信息\NIt's from Dave!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.68,0:05:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想我  笑脸  笑脸  桃心\NHe misses me. Smiley face, smiley face, heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.39,0:05:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羡煞旁人了  凯蒂\NAww. That's adorable, Katie.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是就在那里吗\NBut he's right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.69,0:05:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买咖啡呢\NGetting his coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.10,0:05:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是不是世界上最贴心的人\NIsn't he just the sweetest?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.60,0:05:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱死他了\NOh, I just love him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.60,0:05:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  谁不是呢\NYeah. Don't we all.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.10,0:05:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  正如我刚才所说\NSo, anyway, as I was saying--
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.60,0:05:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道今天是我们在一起的第4643天吗\NDid you know that today is our 4,643rd day as a couple?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.39,0:05:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从未分开过\NWe've never been apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.06,0:05:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我还记得那些奇怪又无趣的派对\NYeah. I remember some very awkward slumber parties.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.66,0:05:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次我想起我们相识的那天\NEvery time I think about the day we met,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.15,0:05:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就起一身鸡皮疙瘩\NI just get goosebumps all over again.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.20,0:05:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧\NOh, look!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.97,0:05:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们反正是没法讨论这个了  是吧\NWe're just never gonna get through this, are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.13,0:05:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻  婚礼最重要的环节\NAnd now, the most important part of a wedding,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.47,0:05:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录像部分\Nthe video.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.81,0:05:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂让我负责  莱丽你弱爆了\NWhich Katie asked me to do, so suck it, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.01,0:05:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  凯蒂\NHi, Katie.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.10,0:05:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  快来  你是不是想让我们\NHey, Mom. Come on, I thought you wanted to get us
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.93,0:05:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把蛋糕搬进来啊\Ncarrying the cake in.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.15,0:05:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你一定要拍我好看的那一边\NYeah, and make sure you get my good side.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.24,0:05:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这应该挺容易的\NWell, actually that should be easy
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.63,0:05:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  我两边都挺上镜的\Nbecause, you know, both of my sides are good.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.21,0:06:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西怎么聚焦啊\NWhere is the focus on this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.67,0:06:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从你爸和我想要拍个性爱录影以来\NYou know, I haven't used this camera
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.90,0:06:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没用过这相机呢\Nsince your father and I tried to make a sex tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.24,0:06:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  怎么扯这上面去了\NMom! Where are we going with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.17,0:06:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是想加些情趣进去\NWell, we were just trying to spice things up a little.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.17,0:06:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  老妈  我是说蛋糕\NNo, Mom. The cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.54,0:06:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好  好的\NOh, okay, okay, okay. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.12,0:06:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我指挥你们进来\NAll right, I will guide you in,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.32,0:06:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -小心下面\N- all right? - Watch the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.79,0:06:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -小心凳子\N- All right. - Watch the ottoman.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.88,0:06:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差几步\NJust another couple of feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.39,0:06:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到了  我们搞得定\NAlmost there, we got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.17,0:06:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的二头肌看起来超棒  -好了\N- My biceps are gonna look great. - All right, here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.96,0:06:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去太棒了\NOh, this looks so great.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.08,0:06:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二\NOne, two...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.85,0:06:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们太棒了  -好的\N- You're good. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.98,0:06:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这玩意的洞察力也太差了\NThe depth perception in this thing is horrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.98,0:06:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给孙女的礼物多么温暖可爱啊\NWhat a warm and loving tribute to your granddaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.08,0:06:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她必定相当感动\NShe will be so touched.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.52,0:06:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我刚才开机可能会更感动的\NProbably more touched if I'd touched the on button.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.50,0:06:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是塔克尔\NHey, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.11,0:06:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来这两个疯狂的小孩\NSo, it looks like these two crazy kids
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.37,0:06:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于要结婚了\Nare really gonna do it, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.55,0:07:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我感到十分的\NYou know, it just makes me feel all...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.99,0:07:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤感\NVulnerable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.99,0:07:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是新娘\NI'm the bride.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.02,0:07:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说我跟这浪费时间呢\NSo I'm probably wasting my time here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.63,0:07:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有没有一个伴娘休息区啊\NThere's not a bridesmaids holding area, is there?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.01,0:07:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很可爱\NYou look cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.90,0:07:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NHey, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.94,0:07:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过来看看\NI just came to check on--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.62,0:07:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋糕呢\Nwhere's the cake?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.90,0:07:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋糕啊\NThe cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.44,0:07:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在楼下酒吧的冰箱里呢\NIt's in the walk-in fridge down at the bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.46,0:07:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意啊\NWow. That was a really good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.46,0:07:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  这原本可以是个好主意\NActually, that would have been a really good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.84,0:07:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西怎么在这里\NWhat is this doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.00,0:07:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛想玩来着\NOh, Emma wanted to play with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.80,0:07:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它摆在蛋糕上太完美了\NThey always look so perfect together on top of the cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.15,0:07:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天你也会成为一个漂亮的新娘\NYou're gonna be a beautiful bride someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.68,0:07:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.82,0:08:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在幻想你和本站在教堂的圣殿上吗\NStill imagining yourself up at the altar with Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.88,0:08:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.27,0:08:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  不这么想了\NNo, I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.47,0:08:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是一时的小迷恋\NThat was just a crush.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.47,0:08:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天你会找到一个真心珍惜你的人\NWell, someday you'll find a guy who truly appreciates you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.23,0:08:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个懂看穿你的心思\NA guy who can look into your heart
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.29,0:08:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道你在想什么的人\Nand know what you're thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.61,0:08:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  好的\NYeah, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.13,0:08:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就太好了\NThat would be nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.39,0:08:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天  我的心\NSomeday, my heart
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.01,0:08:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概应该回到楼上去  开派对呢\Nshould probably get back upstairs. You know, party.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.91,0:08:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上来吗\NAre you gonna come up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.00,0:08:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上去  马上来\NYeah, in a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.49,0:08:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.42,0:08:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂  现在想换其他口味也不算太晚\NYou know, Katie, it's still not too late to shop around.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.65,0:08:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让吉恩牌带你去兜兜风怎么样\NHow would you like to take a ride on the Gene machine?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.76,0:08:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边才是约会区\NAnd that's the dating pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.31,0:08:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出现的真及时\NYou got out just in time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.54,0:08:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NAll right, woo!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.80,0:08:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有两分钟就到午夜了\NTwo minutes to midnight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:09:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫  婚礼的大日子怎么没见新娘啊\NDave, no seeing the bride on the wedding day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.08,0:09:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  行动起来\NAll right, let's move.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.10,0:09:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你  凯蒂猫眯\NI love you, Katie cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.51,0:09:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更爱你  大卫小熊\NI love you more, Davey bear.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.13,0:09:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你们有一整晚的时间\NAw, now you have a whole night apart
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.84,0:09:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去给对方想个新昵称了\Nto think of new nicknames!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.65,0:09:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  维勒\NOkay, Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.00,0:09:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先安排几个小时的酒吧时光\NAfter hours bar,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.09,0:09:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再去脱衣舞俱乐部\Nstrip club,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.36,0:09:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是去脱衣舞俱乐部先消磨几个小时啊\Nor after hours strip club?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.70,0:09:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们干嘛给自己设限呢  -我不知道\N- Why limit ourselves? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.59,0:09:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  安排婚礼的优先事项呢\NBen? Wedding priorities?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.07,0:09:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天是个大日子\NTomorrow's a big day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.48,0:09:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁这么大惊小怪啊\NWho opened a bag of "Wah."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.16,0:09:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你至少要确定\NCan you please at least make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.79,0:09:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有车送凯蒂回酒店\NKatie gets a cab back to her hotel?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.60,0:09:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我保证新娘安全到家\NYes, I'll make sure the bride gets home safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.02,0:09:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松点\NAnd relax,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.95,0:09:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能把持好自己\NI think I can handle myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.27,0:09:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的头啊\NOh, my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.45,0:10:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫熊熊\NMmm... Davey bear
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.38,0:10:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你不想和凯蒂小猫咪依偎在一起吗\Ndon't you want to snuggle with your Katie cat?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.32,0:10:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我是你的本\NIt's actually your Ben...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.08,0:10:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔兔\NBunny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.48,0:10:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你在我床上做什么\NBen, what are you doing in my bed?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.74,0:10:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在我床上干什么\NWondering what you're doing in my bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.26,0:10:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会  等等  我们有没有\NBut how did I-- wait, did we--?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.17,0:10:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  发生什么事情了\NWait, what happened?!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.58,0:10:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还盼着你能想起来呢\NI was hoping you could fill in some of those details.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.38,0:10:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办\NWhat am I gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.12,0:10:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这本应该是我一生中最幸福的一天\NThis is supposed to be the happiest day of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.14,0:10:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深呼吸  深长安静地呼吸\NDeep breath. Deep quiet breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.11,0:10:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带你出去\NOkay, we'll get you out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.80,0:10:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的秘密  谁也不会知道\NIt'll be our secret. No one else will ever know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.03,0:10:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\NMorning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.16,0:10:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  不要啊\NOh, God, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.24,0:10:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许就三个人会知道\NOkay, maybe just one other person will know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.39,0:10:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么回事\NWhat is the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.75,0:10:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个不敲门的老妈\NI don't have a mother who knocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.56,0:10:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她三个小时内就结婚了\NShe is getting married in three hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.85,0:10:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  你得帮我把她弄出来\NI know. You have to help me get her out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.99,0:10:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\NFine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.11,0:10:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我不是为了你\NBut I'm not doing this for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.81,0:10:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了亲爱的  甜美可爱无辜的凯蒂\NI'm doing this for dear, sweet, lovable, innocent Katie,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.71,0:11:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在就只是凯蒂了\Nwho will now just be known as Katie.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.52,0:11:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两分钟之内准备走\NBe ready to move in two.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.90,0:11:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟据这个散落图样\NJudging from this splatter pattern,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.55,0:11:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我判断这是底层\NI detect that this is the bottom layer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.10,0:11:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  神探南茜\NHey, Nancy Drew...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.55,0:11:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划有变\NChange of plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.71,0:11:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得走了  马上\NYou've got to get out of here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.38,0:11:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不可能\NOh, no. Not happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.58,0:11:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得复建蛋糕  穿燕尾服\NI've got a cake to build, a tuxedo to wear,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.51,0:11:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为舞池主角\Nand a dance floor to dominate.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.63,0:11:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.17,0:11:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  顶层在哪儿\NOkay, now where is that top tier?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.60,0:11:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有可能是那个\NAny chance that's it?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.52,0:11:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.19,0:11:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  就是这个  你怎么搞的啊\NYes, that's it. What is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.44,0:11:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我饿了\NI was hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.07,0:11:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱吃蛋糕\NAnd I like cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.80,0:11:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我待会不吃就是了\NI just won't have a piece later.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.26,0:11:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  现在吗\NWhat?! Right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.09,0:11:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都到大厅了啊\NYou're in the lobby?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.74,0:11:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  是莱丽\NGuys, it's Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.03,0:11:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她快上来了\NShe's on her way up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.21,0:11:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  快  蛋糕  蛋糕\NGo, go. Cake, cake, cake.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.32,0:11:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大喜的日子  祝贺你啊\NCongratulations on your big day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.03,0:11:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该继续穿白色  我就那样\NYou should still wear white. I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.33,0:11:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  玛尔戈\NHey, Margo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.84,0:12:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有可能凯蒂在你房间呢\NIs there any chance Katie's in your room?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.18,0:12:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.25,0:12:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪会啊  她当然在这儿\NNo, of course she's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.89,0:12:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我打电话了  忙着呢  再见\NStop calling me. I'm very busy. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.84,0:12:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍天啊  凯蒂\NOh my God. Katie.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.71,0:12:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不到三小时之内我们就要走向圣坛了\NWe are walking down the aisle in less than three hours
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.21,0:12:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去像在垃圾桶里睡了一宿\Nand you look like you slept in a dumpster.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.62,0:12:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意思是\NI mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.77,0:12:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊\NHow are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.06,0:12:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我不行\NI don't think I can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.70,0:12:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我是不是该结婚\NI don't know if I can get married.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.09,0:12:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂  怎么回事\NKatie, what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.67,0:12:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一门心思的想毁了这场婚礼吗\NAre you determined to destroy this wedding?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.55,0:12:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  本  你真是不可思议\NHonestly, Ben. You are unbelievable.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.39,0:12:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  有时候我都对自己感到吃惊\NYeah. Sometimes I surprise even myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.65,0:12:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可要是大嘴巴新娘可闭嘴的话\NBut if our blabbity bride would shut up,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.34,0:12:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就完全没问题了\Nthis whole problem would go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.82,0:12:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的\NIt's not going away.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.05,0:12:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在考虑取消婚礼\NShe's thinking of calling off the wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.69,0:12:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  因为我\NReally? Because of me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.06,0:12:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不是  因为她跟着马戏团跑了\NNo, because she's running away with the circus.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.26,0:12:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是因为你了\NYes, because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.31,0:12:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你搅乱了人家的生活啊  本\NGod, these are people's lives that you're messing with, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.16,0:13:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那我该怎么办  -我不知道\N- So what should I do? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.27,0:13:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你得把问题解决了\NBut you are gonna fix this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.79,0:13:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗\NAre we clear?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.64,0:13:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当明白\NVery.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.39,0:13:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说现在啊  好的  -苍天啊\N- Oh, you mean now? Okay... - Oh my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.79,0:13:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊\NYou.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.10,0:13:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呦  凯蒂\NYo, Katie.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.56,0:13:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是想过来看看\NI just wanted to check in
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.40,0:13:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认一下你没有重新考虑\Nand make sure you weren't having any second thoughts.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.96,0:13:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新考虑\NSecond thoughts?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.03,0:13:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是过去式了\NOh, we're way past second thoughts.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.62,0:13:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我该不该这么做了\NI don't know if I can do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.96,0:13:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我不知道我该不该结婚了\NI don't know if I can get married now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.39,0:13:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\NOh, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.98,0:13:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望这跟我没有任何关系\NI sure hope it doesn't have anything to do with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.21,0:13:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为你\NIt has everything to do with you!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.09,0:13:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我已经听说了\NYeah, I've been kind of hearing that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.39,0:13:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本以为我能行的\NI thought that I could do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.59,0:13:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我就想  "天啊  我不行"\NAnd then I thought "Oh my God, I cannot do this."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.52,0:13:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着我又想"不需要告诉任何人怎么回事\NAnd then I thought "Nobody needs to know what happened
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.14,0:13:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我都不知道是怎么回事"\Nbecause I don't even know what happened,"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.31,0:13:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着我又想  "我会知道的"\Nand then I thought "I will know,"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.24,0:13:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着我又想"天啊想了这么多我脑仁疼"\Nand then I thought "Oh my God my head hurts from all my thoughts"!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.86,0:13:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又没有想过你有点反应过度啊\NDid you ever think you might be overreacting just a titch?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.84,0:13:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反应过度\NOverreacting?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.06,0:13:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我反应过度了吗\NYou think that I'm overreacting?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.99,0:13:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就这么一说\NJust throwing it out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.30,0:14:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有\NBecause I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.59,0:14:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要嫁给世界上最棒的男人了\NI think I am reacting exactly the way you're supposed to react
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.93,0:14:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而婚礼当天早晨却和某白痴睡在一起\Nwhen you wake up in bed with some idiot
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.40,0:14:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我的反应恰到好处\Nthe morning of your wedding to the most wonderful man in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.17,0:14:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了这一天我等了一辈子\NI have been waiting for this day my entire life.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.80,0:14:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却  你  你\NAnd you! You-- you,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.03,0:14:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本·维勒  却把这一天毁了\NBen Wheeler, have stolen it from me!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.10,0:14:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你现在让我不好受了\NOkay, now you're making me feel bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.88,0:14:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  大卫发现了怎么办啊\NBen, what if Dave finds out?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.15,0:14:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么向他解释啊\NHow can I ever explain it to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.42,0:14:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\NIt's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.73,0:14:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我离开这房间\NI'm gonna leave this room,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.56,0:14:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我们再也不说这件事\Nand we're never gonna mention it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.22,0:14:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗\NOkay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.34,0:14:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从未发生\NNever happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.40,0:14:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫永远不会发现的\NDave is never gonna find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.40,0:14:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂\NKatie?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.80,0:14:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在吗\NAre you there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.51,0:14:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我啊  大卫\NIt's me, Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.07,0:14:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫  婚礼之前你不可以跟我见面\NDave, you're not supposed to see me before the wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.48,0:14:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我们得谈谈\NBut we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.80,0:14:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收到一条短信说我应该问你些本的事情\NI got a text saying I should ask you about Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.06,0:14:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你没跟任何人说过\NI thought you said you didn't tell anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.79,0:14:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是没有啊\NI didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.36,0:14:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得没有吧\NI don't think.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.66,0:14:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对昨晚的记忆仍然很模糊\NStill a little fuzzy on the whole last night thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.01,0:14:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卫  你得相信我\NDave, you have to believe me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.80,0:15:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\NI, uh--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.90,0:15:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿燕尾服真帅\NOh, you look so cute in your tux.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.30,0:15:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和本发生了什么\NWhat happened between you and Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.90,0:15:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有  我发誓\NNothing, I swear.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.33,0:15:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道你在说什么\NI don't even know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.83,0:15:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就愿意看到这一幕\NOh, that's what I like to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.75,0:15:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两只爱情鸟复合了\NOur two lovebirds are back together
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.34,0:15:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚礼又可以举行了\Nand our wedding is back on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.32,0:15:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候不举行了\NWhen was it off?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.68,0:15:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啊\NNever.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.98,0:15:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是一种表达\NYou know, that's just an expression.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.73,0:15:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像"演出成功""祝你今天愉快"\NLike "Break a leg" Or "Have a nice day."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.46,0:15:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又是什么意思啊\NWhat does that even mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.16,0:15:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  快走啦\NAll right, run along now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.53,0:15:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定一切都好吗\NYou sure everything's okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.95,0:15:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确定\NI'm sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.16,0:15:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  好啦\NOkay, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.99,0:15:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  我就知道你能回过神来\NSee, there, I knew you would come to your senses.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.00,0:15:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和本之间不管发生了什么\NWhatever happened between you and Ben
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.70,0:15:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都只是你通往幸福大道的艳遇休息站\Nwas just a dirty rest stop on your way down the happiness highway.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.16,0:15:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  莱丽  我刚才在处理这事儿呢\NExcuse me, Riley. I was haling this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.90,0:15:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本  -我不行了\N- Ben? - I can't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.28,0:15:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚礼正式取消\NThe wedding is officially off.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.54,0:15:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来好好的  你一来就坏事\NYou know, we were doing fine until you showed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.92,0:15:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很了不起吧  艾玛\NPretty impressive, huh, Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.83,0:15:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说出去哈  第二层和第三层\NDon't tell anyone, but levels two and three
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.53,0:16:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全是用硬纸板做的\Nare completely made of cardboard
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.16,0:16:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有牙膏\Nand toothpaste.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.21,0:16:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  维太太\NHey, Mrs. Whee.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.36,0:16:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  妈  你看怎么样啊\NHey, mom. What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.13,0:16:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看我们得行动起来\NI think we should get a move on
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.13,0:16:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁着我发型还没乱\Nwhile my hair is still up
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.16,0:16:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腋窝的吸汗垫子还是干的\Nand my dress shields are still dry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.67,0:16:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弟呢\NWhere's your brother?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.46,0:16:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要迟到了\NWe're gonna be late for this wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.76,0:16:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果婚礼还举行的话\NIf it's even actually happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.52,0:16:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要举行啊\NIt better be.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.67,0:16:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的适婚女士名单已经减少到\NLook, I have narrowed down my list of eligible ladies
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.78,0:16:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八位优胜者了\Nto an elite eight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.55,0:16:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们可不会拒绝身着燕尾服的塔克尔\NDo not deny them Tucker in a tux.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.75,0:16:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  为什么可能不举行啊\NWait, why wouldn't it be happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.40,0:16:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\NOh, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.50,0:16:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能有起小事故叫"本睡了新娘"\NMaybe a little thing called "Ben slept with the bride."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.37,0:16:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本睡了新娘\NBen slept with the bride?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.78,0:16:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不应该了\NThat is so wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.51,0:16:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是我先挑逗她的\NI totally hit on her first.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.72,0:16:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本不会干这事的\NBen would never do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.25,0:16:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  来点声援  妈妈\NCome on, back me up, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.30,0:16:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本有罪\NOh, Ben is guilty as sin.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.93,0:16:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该去看看录像\NYou should see the video.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.16,0:16:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.21,0:16:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是...\NThe question is...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.22,0:16:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道的  吉恩\NHow did you know, Gene?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.20,0:16:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我消息灵通着呢\NOh, I have my ways.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.25,0:16:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\NOh, and so do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.81,0:16:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.66,0:16:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-耳环拿着点  -瞧好吧  姐们\N- Hold my earrings. - I got you, girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.70,0:17:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂  求你出来吧\NKatie, please come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.39,0:17:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上婚纱  你就能舒服点了\NJust put on the dress. You'll feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.29,0:17:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我穿上的时候就是这样\NI know I did when I had it on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.83,0:17:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可能说这个不重要\NProbably not important right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.82,0:17:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不明白吗\NDon't you get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.28,0:17:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前从来没有向大卫撒过谎\NI have never lied to Dave before, ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.57,0:17:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我能向我未来的丈夫自如的撒这个谎\NIf I can lie this easily to my future husband,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.64,0:17:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么或许你和吉恩说得对\Nthen maybe you and Gene were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.22,0:17:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我还没准备好结婚\NMaybe I'm not ready to get married.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.18,0:17:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个教训  永远不要听本和吉恩的\NOkay, first lesson. Never listen to Ben and Gene.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.13,0:17:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯蒂  你得嫁给大卫\NKatie, you have to marry Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.83,0:17:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候本的话还可以听\NSometimes Ben's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.00,0:17:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢\NAnd why should I?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.35,0:17:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你就可以停止愧疚了吗\NSo you can stop feeling guilty?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.24,0:17:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们真的命中注定在一起\NBecause you're truly meant to be together.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.79,0:17:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们彼此相爱\NYou love him and he loves you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.74,0:17:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们一见钟情\NYou have since the moment you set eyes on each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.46,0:17:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个混蛋因为\NI was just being a jerk because...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.52,0:17:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我嫉妒\NI'm jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.31,0:17:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫉妒我和大卫吗\NOf me and Dave?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.86,0:17:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁不嫉妒啊\NWho isn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.77,0:17:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们拥有大家梦寐以求的东西\NYou have what everybody wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.92,0:17:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真爱  灵魂伴侣\NA true love, a soul mate,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.13,0:17:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好朋友  合三为一了\Na best friend, all rolled into one.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.12,0:18:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这些人跟白痴似的寻寻觅觅\NThe rest of us are just running around like idiots
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.67,0:18:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盼着能有你的一半就好了\Nhoping for even half of what you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.74,0:18:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望\NI just wish that...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.25,0:18:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天  我遇到一个女孩\None day, I'll look up at a girl and just...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.05,0:18:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相知足矣\Nknow.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.25,0:18:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应吧  你得答应啊\NSay yes. You have to say yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.86,0:18:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NYes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.09,0:18:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  谢谢你\NYes, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.12,0:18:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  行动起来\NAll right, let's move.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.47,0:18:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要举行婚礼呢  姐们\NWe've got a wedding to put on here, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.94,0:18:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都来这儿干什么\NWhat are you guys all doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.35,0:18:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送点东西\NMaking a few deliveries.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.74,0:18:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燕尾服  蛋糕  外加一混球\NTux, cake, and dirt bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.28,0:18:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会  艾玛呢\NWait, where's Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.46,0:18:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伴娘等待区\NBridesmaids holding area.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.69,0:18:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会  什么  真有这个区吗\NHold up. What? That's a real thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.67,0:18:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  那可不是我定的蛋糕\NWhat is going on? That is not the cake I ordered.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.59,0:18:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  先生\NOkay, mister.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.05,0:18:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该出场了\NYou're up.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.95,0:18:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉恩  你干了什么\NGene, what did you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.44,0:18:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚  你们俩在不同的房间里喝高了\NLast night after you both passed out in separate rooms,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.84,0:18:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我把你和凯蒂放到一张床上去的\NI kind of put you and Katie in bed together.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.28,0:19:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我捉弄了吧\NGotcha!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.79,0:19:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.14,0:19:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们没有\NSo we didn't--?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.34,0:19:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\NNope.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.51,0:19:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放着我来\NLet me handle this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.22,0:19:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在被我捉弄了吧\NNow I gotcha.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.73,0:19:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个时刻居然摄像机没有开啊\NOh, of all the times not to be rolling.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.64,0:19:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有可能你们再来一次捏\NOkay, is there any chance that you could do this again?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.72,0:19:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以在这个地方做\NAll right, we can do this here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.11,0:19:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\NHey.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.07,0:19:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\NHey.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.86,0:19:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什么\NSo, what'd you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.35,0:19:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你干的很不错\NI think you did a pretty amazing job.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.82,0:19:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们干得很不错\NWe did a pretty amazing job.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.45,0:19:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  就我自己\NOkay, me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.21,0:19:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今晚过得开心吗\NDid you have fun tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.17,0:19:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实很开心\NI actually did.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.04,0:19:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一遗憾的是\NMy only regret,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.80,0:19:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有和伴娘跳支舞\NI didn't get to dance with the maid of honor.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.37,0:19:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚还没结束呢\NWell, the night isn't over yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.04,0:20:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟凯蒂讲的那些话是真心的吗\NDid you mean everything you said to Katie?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.53,0:20:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NI did.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.10,0:20:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我们会找到那个特别的人吗\NDo you ever think we'll find that special someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.15,0:20:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意这样想\NI'd like to think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.85,0:20:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位智者告诉过我\NYou know, a wise man once told me
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.20,0:20:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终有一天你会遇到一个人\Nthat someday you'll meet someone
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.30,0:20:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会住进你的心里\Nand they'll look right into your heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.96,0:20:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该走了吧\NWe should probably get back, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.08,0:20:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,急什么\NWhat's the hurry?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.95,0:20:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想过会来得这么快\NI just never imagined this happening so soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.88,0:21:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我想如果两个人\NBut I guess when two people
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.01,0:21:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打小就认识的话\Nhave known each other their whole lives,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.47,0:21:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事就难以避免了\Nit just becomes inevitable.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.15,0:21:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道感觉太快了\NI know it feels fast,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.59,0:21:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可时机到了\Nbut when it's right, it's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.04,0:21:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.58,0:21:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始吧\NLet's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.80,0:21:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神赋予我此项权利\NBy the power vested in me,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.43,0:21:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我宣布你们成为\NI now pronounce you
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.89,0:21:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长颈鹿和妻子了\Ngiraffe and wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.15,0:21:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你可以把口水流到新郎身上了\NYou may now drool on the groom.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.23,0:21:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又高又黑  可以机洗\NTall, dark, and machine washable.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.91,0:21:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮  艾玛\NWell done, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.95,0:21:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  一个维勒搞定了\NAll right, that's one Wheeler down.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.39,0:21:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个是谁\NWho's next?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.61,0:21:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[本季终  第二季不见不散哦]
