[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.66,0:00:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快点出来  -我告诉你  每天中午让妈妈\N- Man. Come on. - I'm telling you, leaving Mom alone
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.37,0:00:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待在我们的公寓  绝对是个错误\Nin our apartment every afternoon is a bad idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.03,0:00:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛自己又不会订中餐外卖\NUntil you teach Emma to order in Chinese,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总得有人喂她吧\Nsomebody's got to feed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.42,0:00:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  你甚至不会感受到妈妈的存在\NDon't worry, you won't even know Mom was here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.39,0:00:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太迟了  昨天  她抽空翻检了\NToo late. Yesterday, she found time
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.24,0:00:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的床头柜  把我的套套都摆放整齐了\Nto go through my nightstand and tidy up my protection center.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.12,0:00:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈还帮你整理那东西\NYour mom organized your love drawer?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.33,0:00:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈做人的原则就是\NMom has this thing about boundaries.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.64,0:00:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,百无禁忌\NShe has none.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.48,0:00:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  队长大人\NSo, Captain Action,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.04,0:00:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你这位新女伴\Nhow much longer do you think
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.35,0:00:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要洗多久才能出来\Nyour new lady friend is gonna be in the shower?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.30,0:00:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  如果我迟到了 \NOkay, if I'm late, 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.07,0:00:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦内萨会把我脑袋塞罐子里的\NVanessa will have my head in a jar.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.26,0:00:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  只塞脑袋么\NReally? Just your head?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.79,0:00:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你计划和瓦内萨分手的\NI thought the plan was to break up with Vanessa?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.86,0:00:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过了\NI tried.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.77,0:00:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是用语言分的  但是\NNot using actual words, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.78,0:00:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真得好好考虑一下了\Nman, I did think it really hard though.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.97,0:00:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈怕小孩碰到  把橱柜全上锁了\NMom also baby-proofed all the cabinets.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.23,0:00:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我郑重声明  别让她来\NI'm telling you-- bad idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.82,0:00:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们需要她照顾艾玛\NBut we need her to watch Emma,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.00,0:01:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以肯定要学着适应啊\Nso we're gonna have to make some adjustments.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.76,0:01:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\NGood morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.95,0:01:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学着适应要时刻记着穿裤子\NLike remembering to wear pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.62,0:01:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小宝贝睡得好吗\NSo how did my baby sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.18,0:01:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我睡得挺好\NPretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.91,0:01:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问的是艾玛\NI meant Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.24,0:01:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么进来的\NHow did she get in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.59,0:01:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你给了我钥匙  亲爱的\NThanks for the key, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.96,0:01:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我省去了不少麻烦\NIt's gonna make this so much easier.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给了她钥匙\NYou gave her a key?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.56,0:01:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的命都是她给的\NShe gave me life.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.66,0:01:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但也许我确实不该那么做  -当然不该\N- But yeah, I probably shouldn't have done that. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.70,0:01:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边  惊喜无极限*\N*It‘s amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.67,0:01:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲  雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions.*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.29,0:01:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脑子进水了吗\NWhat is the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.71,0:01:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能把我们公寓的钥匙给老妈呢\NYou can't give Mom a key to our apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.06,0:01:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样她就能随意进出\NI mean if she coming and out whenever she wants
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.71,0:01:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为所欲为  妈  你要去干嘛\Nto do whatever...mom, what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.73,0:01:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-洗手  -在厨房洗吧\N- To wash my hands. - Use the kitchen.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.47,0:01:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  卫生间怎么不行\NWhy? What's wrong with the bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.77,0:01:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门坏了  卡住打不开了\NWe're having some trouble with the door, it's stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.62,0:01:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  其余五小时你不必来这里\NMom, you're not supposed to be here for another five hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.54,0:01:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  抱歉\NI know. I'm sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.00,0:01:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但昨天艾玛和我玩得太开心了\Nbut Emma and I had so much fun yesterday,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.86,0:02:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我准备带她去上"祖孙亲子班"\Nthat I signed us up for a "Grandma and Me" Class.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.97,0:02:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实那是"母女亲子班"\NActually it's a "Mommy and Me" Class,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.33,0:02:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我显年轻  看着和她妈一样\Nbut come on, I mean, huh, aah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.82,0:02:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是\NAnd today it is
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.99,0:02:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芭蕾舞裙日\Nballerina tutu day.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.12,0:02:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让我想起\NThis just reminds me
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.21,0:02:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有多渴望生个女孩\Nof how badly I wanted a little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.78,0:02:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓  B超检查时看到你的小鸡鸡\NI swear, I must have cried for two days
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.51,0:02:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我足足哭了两天\Nafter I saw your penis on the ultrasound.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.72,0:02:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是百无禁忌啊\NReally has no boundaries.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.37,0:02:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确  你得用心去找\NGranted, you really had to look for it,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.03,0:02:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一旦找到  却是\Nbut once I found it, you know, it's...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.98,0:02:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在修门\NStill working on the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.00,0:02:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是随便找个管子冲冲算了\NMaybe I'll just go hose off out back.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.59,0:02:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.45,0:02:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈    \NYou know, Mom...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.19,0:02:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上是我们唯一能和艾玛相处的时光\N...the mornings are kind of my only time with Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.16,0:02:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉她会我们带她去公园\NI told her that we were gonna go to the park and--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.07,0:02:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  她是个婴儿\NHoney, she's a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.17,0:02:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她连公园是什么都不知道\NShe doesn't even know what a park is.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.00,0:02:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈\NMom.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.62,0:02:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不必说\NYou don't have to say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.55,0:02:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用感谢我\NYou're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.96,0:02:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想只要大家齐心协力\NI just know if we all pull together,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.36,0:02:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定能让她茁壮成长\Nwe will do right by that little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.66,0:03:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝\NNow where is
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.84,0:03:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里呀\Nmy little pumpkin?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.59,0:03:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有丹尼\NAnd, Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.66,0:03:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让那个可怜的姑娘出来吧\NLet that poor woman out of the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.05,0:03:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛还太小\NI think Emma's a little young
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.38,0:03:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见不得这种香艳场面\Nto see her first Booty call.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.63,0:03:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈带艾玛还有个好处  \NAnd here's another good thing about having Mom watch Emma--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.20,0:03:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟共聚时间增多\Nmore bro time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.06,0:03:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收回钥匙\NGet the key.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.49,0:03:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缠着莱丽唠叨的那个人是谁\NWho's the nozzle talking to Riley?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.84,0:03:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法学院学生\NLaw school buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.93,0:03:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们最近总在一起温书\NThey've been hitting the books pretty hard lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.65,0:03:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似他对人比对书的兴趣更大\NLooks like he's interested in hitting more than the books.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.10,0:03:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\NYou think?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.53,0:03:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对莱丽是件好事  对吧\NGood for Riley, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.62,0:03:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对个头\NWrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.83,0:03:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你  我的法律顾问\NThank you, counselor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.99,0:03:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待下一次的律师会晤\NI look forward to our next sidebar.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.60,0:03:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不反对\NI wouldn't object to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.73,0:03:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NDanny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.96,0:03:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHey.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.54,0:03:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友杰克刚走\NYou just missed my friend, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.48,0:03:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在给他补课\NI've been tutoring him.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.92,0:04:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么补\NIn what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.33,0:04:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小脸羞红  言语暧昧\NBlushing, flirting,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.66,0:04:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搔首弄姿\Nhair flipping?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.91,0:04:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  没有那么夸张啦\NOkay. It's a lot harder than it looks.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.73,0:04:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他挺可爱的  是吧\NHe's kind of cute, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.34,0:04:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是你喜欢的类型吧\NThat isn't really the kind of guy you like, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.67,0:04:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花花公子式的律师\NFancy-ass lawyer wannabe?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.70,0:04:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然油腔滑调的酒保\NSince smooth-talking bartenders
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.17,0:04:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我没有兴趣\Ndon't really seem to be interested--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.20,0:04:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我何必在一棵树上吊死\Nyeah, I'm looking elsewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.37,0:04:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你该继续追寻\NThen maybe you should keep looking.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.15,0:04:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么那么在乎我喜不喜欢杰克\NWhy do you care if I like Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.58,0:04:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎\NI don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.04,0:04:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么会在乎\NWhy would I care?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.50,0:04:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许有人在乎\NBut maybe someone else cares.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.40,0:04:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样让他们怎么想\NAnd what kind of message is that to send them?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.95,0:04:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些在乎的你人会乱想啊\NThose people who care.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.75,0:04:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你的建议\NOkay. I'll,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.64,0:04:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会考虑  谢谢\Nkeep that in mind. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.58,0:04:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的那些\NWould any of those
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.75,0:04:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在乎我的人\Npeople who care
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.67,0:04:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰巧就在这间酒吧里吗\Nhappen to be in this bar?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.93,0:04:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许\NMaybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.09,0:04:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是  这位在乎我的人\NSo you're saying that this person
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.47,0:04:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许对我有意思\Nmight actually be interested?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.47,0:04:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也许是\NHe might be.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.13,0:04:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不该和杰克调情\NSo I should stop flirting with Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.47,0:05:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不该\NThat one's a definite yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.13,0:05:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白  谢谢你  丹尼\NMessage received. Thank you, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.68,0:05:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塔克尔  -你好\N- Tuck. - Oh, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.59,0:05:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐那多久了\NHow long were you there?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.43,0:05:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足够久啦\NLong enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.96,0:05:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我问问\NOkay. So...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.76,0:05:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好奇\NI'm curious.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.66,0:05:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很肯定\NSee, I'm pretty sure
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.97,0:05:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本对莱丽没意思\Nthat Ben's not really into Riley,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.03,0:05:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  这里那位在乎她的人到底是谁\Nso I wonder who at this bar is?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.16,0:05:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何人都有可能\NIt could be anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.03,0:05:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何人吗\NAnyone?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.80,0:05:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别坏笑了  -那可不行\N- Quit smiling. - I don't think
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.22,0:05:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计以后一直会奸笑下去\NI'm ever going to quit smiling.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.59,0:05:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑  又这样\NReally? Again?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.78,0:05:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你  要不是你总给\NYou know, you might have
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.71,0:05:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下东区的姑娘们提供\Na better shot with Riley
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.92,0:05:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费浴室  没准你和莱丽\Nif you didn't offer free showers
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.71,0:05:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}下东区：穷人区  为作家和艺术家时尚聚居区
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.21,0:05:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早成情侣了\Nto every girl on the Lower East Side.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.01,0:06:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说了一百遍了  我不喜欢莱丽\NFor the 100th time, I don't like Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.05,0:06:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管那里面是谁  总之不是我带来的\NAnd whoever's in there, she isn't mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.10,0:06:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛哪儿去了\NWho's got Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.91,0:06:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\NGood morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.25,0:06:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡裤  我需要你们\NPajamas-- got to get me some.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.65,0:06:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你昨晚住这里了吗  -别说傻话了\N- Did you spend the night? - Don't be silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.86,0:06:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道艾玛会醒的很早  我早来\NI just know how early Emma wakes up,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.55,0:06:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了让你们睡个懒觉\Nso I thought you might like to sleep in.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.15,0:06:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下水道可能有点堵\NAnd the drain's a little backed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.17,0:06:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  大概是我的排泄能力太强了\NSorry. I think some of my extensions might have come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.15,0:06:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最好在本给便便们钥匙之前\NI better go pull them out of the drain
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.49,0:06:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把它们清理掉\Nbefore Ben gives them a key, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.91,0:06:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要迟到了  教练想让我在冰场上练习\NAnd I'm late for the rink. Coach wants me to practice
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.31,0:06:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-几个关键动作  -不错啊\N- some of my key moves. - Subtle.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.43,0:06:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  你来得太早了\NSo, Mom, you're here awfully early.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.25,0:06:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-又一次  -我必须得早来\N- Again. - I have to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.84,0:06:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也看到排队洗澡多困难了\NYou've seen the line for this shower.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.16,0:06:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨晚没来的及\NI really didn't get to see her
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.83,0:06:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在宝宝睡着前看她  而且...\Nbefore she went to bed last night and--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.52,0:06:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她作息规律  这难道不好吗\Nisn't it great she's on a schedule?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.11,0:06:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\NTerrific.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.16,0:07:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从我开始下午上班\NBut since I work in the afternoons,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.17,0:07:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答应帮我在\Nwhen you oh so graciously offered
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.24,0:07:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得闲的这段时间照顾她\Nto watch her for that oh so brief window of time,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.89,0:07:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为早上我能自己带她\NI assumed I'd see her in the mornings.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.80,0:07:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我把你的早上也解放了\NAnd now you've got your mornings free.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.01,0:07:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是在我把你拉扯大的时候\NOh! How I wish I had a me
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.55,0:07:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个这样的我出现就好了\Nwhen I was raising you. Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.87,0:07:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你能听得懂人家的暗示就好了\NAnd I wish I had a you that could take a hint.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.06,0:07:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥  亲爱的\NDid you say something, honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.12,0:07:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没  老妈  没说啥  -好吧\N- Oh, no, Mom. No. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.31,0:07:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的生活总算有了一点光明了\NAnd finally my day gets a little brighter.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.40,0:07:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NOh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.20,0:07:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-出什么事了吗  -没  就是我老妈啦\N- Is something wrong? - No, just my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.76,0:07:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要和杰克约会吗  -没有啊  怎么了\N- Are you meeting Jack? - No. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.18,0:07:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你小小打扮了一番嘛\NOh, you look a little dressed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.39,0:07:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每隔一个下午的三小时\NThree hours every other afternoon,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.41,0:07:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要的就只有这么多而已\Nthat's all I needed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.23,0:07:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我要和杰克去约会吗\NDo you think that I'm going out with Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.86,0:07:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有啊  -那太可惜了\N- Because I'm not. - Oh, too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.44,0:07:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了她把钥匙\NI gave her a key,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.17,0:07:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在她就整个搬进来了似的\Nand now she's practically moved in.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.64,0:07:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么可惜\NWhy too bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.83,0:07:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得你们俩看起来挺配的\NOh, I just thought you guys looked good together.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.05,0:07:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都见不到艾玛了\NAnd I never get to see Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.24,0:07:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  你觉得我应该和杰克去约会\NSo you're saying I should go out with Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.95,0:08:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥不去呢  我跟丹尼就是这么说的\NWhy not? That's what I told Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.23,0:08:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你跟丹尼这么说的\NThat's what you told Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.36,0:08:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  我没法跟她开口\NYeah, but I can't talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.54,0:08:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是没办法跟她开口谈\NI've never been able to talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.86,0:08:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我真是没辙了  我应该\NBut I have no choice. I just have to
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.25,0:08:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她坐下来谈谈某些界限的问题  对吧\Nsit her down and lay out some boundaries, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.77,0:08:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  他为啥要那样做\NNot right. Why would he do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.31,0:08:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -丹尼\N- Who? - Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.19,0:08:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说我老妈\NI meant my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.29,0:08:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我今晚应该跟她谈谈吗\NSo do you think I should talk to her tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.52,0:08:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  她要参加读书会\NYou can't. She has book club.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.63,0:08:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我掌心都在冒汗了\NYes, my palms are starting to sweat.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.34,0:08:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说吧  你对我向杰克投怀送抱\NSo just so we're clear, you have no issues
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.42,0:08:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没一点意见是吧\Nwith me throwing myself at Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.04,0:08:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我还觉得这是件好事呢\NActually sounds like a pretty good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.43,0:08:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分男人都挺蠢的\NMost guys are fairly clueless.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.14,0:08:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.63,0:08:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了\NI'm getting that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.70,0:08:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这几天大家过得都挺不爽的\NHey, look, I know the last few days have been a little rough,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.11,0:08:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我希望啤酒男给的这一小桶免费啤酒\Nso I hope this free pony keg from the beer guy
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.37,0:08:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有酒吧厨房这些稍稍有点过期的肉\Nand some slightly-expired meat from the bar kitchen
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.61,0:08:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让你们知道我有多抱歉\Nwill let you know how truly sorry I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.50,0:08:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能摆脱老妈我真替你高兴\NHey, I'm just glad you got rid of Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.56,0:08:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我能在场听到就好了\NWish I could have heard that go down.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.96,0:08:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实跟她谈过了  对吧\NYou did talk to her, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.83,0:08:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些牛排闻起来真香啊\NHow good do those steaks smell?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.37,0:08:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是在转移话题哦\NLike they're trying to change the subject.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.46,0:08:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你都没勇气\NI can't believe you can't stand up
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.74,0:08:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对你自己的老妈\Nto your own mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.24,0:08:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱就不能\NOh, g-- can we not go five minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.55,0:08:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消停五分钟吗\Nwithout talking?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.34,0:09:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦内萨\NHey, Vanessa.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.39,0:09:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想你呢\NOh, I miss you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.44,0:09:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔说得没错  老弟\NTucker's right, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.91,0:09:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得那辆小货车眼熟不\NDoes that minivan look familiar to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.60,0:09:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老妈  快走\NMom! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.58,0:09:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-把包带上  -好吧\N- Get the bag! - Okay. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.76,0:09:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛\NEmma!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.26,0:09:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看奶奶给你带啥好东西了\NLook what your grandma brought you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.38,0:09:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一只和你老爸的室友一样大的兔兔哦\NIt's a bunny the size of your daddy's roommate.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.33,0:09:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地你在家\NOh, thank God you're home.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.60,0:09:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没带手机  也没带钱包\NNo phone, no wallet--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.00,0:09:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真是无处可去了\Nwe really had nowhere else to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.41,0:09:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  一切还好吧\NWhat's going on? Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.98,0:09:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  我老妈又来了\NNo. Mom showed up again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.87,0:10:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么就不明白她不能老是这样\NShe's got to learn that she can't
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.09,0:10:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不打声招呼就来毁掉我们的夜生活呢\Njust barge in unannounced and ruin our evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.58,0:10:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以为了让她明白\NOh. So you're teaching her a lesson
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.26,0:10:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就要不打声招呼就来毁掉我的夜生活是吧\Nby barging in unannounced and ruining my evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.66,0:10:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  不  我是说\NExactly. No, I mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.18,0:10:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今晚应该没啥节目的  对吧\NIt's not like you had any plans, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.73,0:10:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这红酒是怎么回事\NHey, what's with the wine?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.75,0:10:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这蜡烛\NAnd the candles?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.68,0:10:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你的乳沟\NAnd the cleavage?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.93,0:10:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好\NOh, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.56,0:10:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是杰克  杰克·帕克\NJack-- Jack Parker.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.25,0:10:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我和...  -还有你卫生间里的这个家伙\N- I go to school with-- - And the man in your bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.35,0:10:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  这是丹尼\NJack, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.70,0:10:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  这是杰克  杰克  这是本\NDanny, Jack. Jack, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.68,0:10:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  这是杰克  他们都是老朋友\NBen, Jack. They're just old friends
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.20,0:10:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来串个门好秀下他们家的宝宝\Nwho stopped by to show off their new baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.61,0:10:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个好可爱的小宝宝啊\NYeah, you're such a cute baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.86,0:10:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  多谢  再见\NOkay, thanks so much, bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.24,0:10:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见  所以你还真的对他\N- Bye. - So you threw yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.69,0:10:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投怀送抱了是吧\Nat him, after all, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.88,0:10:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴你能听进我的建议\NGlad to see you took my advice.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.90,0:10:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气  顾问\NYou're welcome, counselor.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.59,0:10:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别在意\NDon't pay attention to anything
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.08,0:10:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本说的话  因为他抽疯呢\Nthat Ben says, because he's crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.74,0:10:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新生儿嘛  睡眠质量不太好\NNew baby, doesn't get a lot of sleep,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.17,0:10:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的  来  来  吃点奶酪\Nyou know. Here. Here, have some cheese.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.72,0:10:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红酒配奶酪  你这是要吃我豆腐了吗\NWine and cheese? Are you coming on to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.17,0:10:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正有此意呢\NStand by.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.78,0:10:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吧  本的建议\NDid you hear that? Hmm? Ben's advice?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.09,0:10:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  真抱歉打搅了你们\NHey, man. Really sorry for messing up
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.82,0:11:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚必要的闲话时段  只是\Nthe obligatory small talk portion of the evening, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.46,0:11:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得给她换尿布了\NI just gotta change a diaper.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.57,0:11:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有喂奶\NAnd feed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.61,0:11:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了咱们还得给她喂奶呢\NDon't forget we need to feed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.94,0:11:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗\NIs that okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.64,0:11:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  不过要速战速决\NFine. Just be quick please.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.59,0:11:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对让你感觉不到我们的存在\NYou won't even know we're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.32,0:11:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这里才不能没有我嘛\NThis is exactly why I need to be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.87,0:11:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过出去了一会儿\NI'm gone for two seconds,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.19,0:11:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就让艾玛睡不成觉了\Nand they've got Emma out past her bedtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.56,0:11:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道他们在什么鬼地方做啥呢\NGod knows where, doing God knows what?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.79,0:11:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嗨  本"\N"Hi, Ben."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.84,0:11:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被你老妈困住了\NI'm trapped with your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.15,0:11:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里  我恨你\NWhere are you? I hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.40,0:11:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回个电话\N"Call me."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.47,0:11:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我会相信你不知道他们在哪儿吗\NDo you expect me to believe that you don't know where they are?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.67,0:11:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看得出来吗  要是我知道\NKnow how you can tell? If I did,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.49,0:11:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早去找他们了\NI'd be with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.34,0:11:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你搞清楚他们在哪里之前\NWell, until you dig up some information,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.27,0:11:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就只能和我还有那个钟待在一起\Nit's just you, me and the clock.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.50,0:11:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘀嗒嘀嗒  塔克尔\NTick, tock, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.67,0:11:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望我可以在这里呆着呢\NWow. Really wish I could hang around,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.26,0:11:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你知道吗  在你来这儿之前\Nbut you know what? I was just on the phone with Vanessa
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.57,0:11:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才和瓦内萨通过电话  绝对真事儿\Nbefore you got here-- which is totally true.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.45,0:11:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说\NAnd, um, she said
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.19,0:11:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她希望我过去一趟  所以\Nshe'd like me to come on over, so--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.15,0:11:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没和她分手吗\Nhaven't you broken up with her yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.23,0:12:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你怎么知道  -地球人都知道了\N- How do you know about-- - Oh, everyone knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.59,0:12:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我今晚就会跟她分手\NWell, maybe I'll do it tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.39,0:12:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你个小忠告吧\NLet me give you a little advice,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.98,0:12:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小屁孩\Ntuck-a-doodle-do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.52,0:12:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有女人都想听实话  我们受得住\NAll women really want to hear is the truth. We can take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.54,0:12:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们坚强着呢  看着我\NWe're tough. Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.22,0:12:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都可以跟我说的呢\NYou can tell me anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.83,0:12:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是不知道他们在哪儿\NI still don't know where they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.36,0:12:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要她睡醒了  我们就走  我发誓\NAs soon as she wakes up, we're out of here, I swear.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.15,0:12:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还等什么  赶紧把她叫醒\NOh, well, what are we waiting for? Wake her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.49,0:12:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会知道你正在约会\NHow was I supposed to know you were on a date?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.19,0:12:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉  下次我会放只袜子在门上\NOh, I'm sorry. Next time I'll put a sock on the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.01,0:12:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和莱丽\NSo, you and Riley--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.04,0:12:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啥情况\Nwhat's that about?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.58,0:12:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时没啥情况  不过她很聪明\NNothing yet, but she's smart,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.71,0:12:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还很有趣\Nand funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.99,0:12:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且显然很有吸引力\NAnd obviously very attractive.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.03,0:12:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真应该见见她高中时的样子\NWell, you should have seen her in high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.41,0:12:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个就是一庞然大物  莱丽\NShe was ginormous. Hey, Riles?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.96,0:12:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这里有毕业年鉴吗\NYou got a copy of your yearbook around here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.42,0:12:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  你在抽什么疯呢\NI don't think so. What is the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.55,0:12:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在把关\NI'm just checking him out
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.46,0:12:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他是不是真的适合你\Nto make sure he's good enough for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.72,0:12:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我自己来吧\NWell, how about I do the inspection
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.52,0:12:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后再告诉你详情好不\Nand get back to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.51,0:13:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\NLook.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.46,0:13:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你不敢和你老妈挑明\NI know you're terrified of talking to your mom,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.85,0:13:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要诚实点\Nbut just be honest.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.04,0:13:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉她实话\NTell her the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.87,0:13:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是所有女人想要听到的\NThat's really all any girl wants to hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.38,0:13:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点怕告诉你\NI was kind of afraid to tell you this,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.74,0:13:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛在你的被子上吐了\Nbut Emma threw up on your comforter.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.79,0:13:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  瓦宝贝\NNo-- no, V-Baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.99,0:13:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  咱们得谈谈\NI'm just saying, I think we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.93,0:13:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  就是这样\NYeah. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.68,0:13:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我只是\NNo no no, I'm just--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.08,0:13:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  只是咱们真的...\Nno no. We've just been really--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.97,0:13:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你就不能让我说完吗  -看在上帝的份上\N- if you could just let me speak-- - Oh, for the love of God,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.73,0:13:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话给我  瓦内萨  亲爱的\Ngive me that. Vanessa, honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.36,0:13:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是邦妮·维勒  本和丹尼的老妈\NHi, Bonnie Wheeler-- Ben and Danny's mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.80,0:13:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  塔克尔要和你分手\NReal quick-- Tucker is breaking up with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.56,0:13:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\NBye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.64,0:13:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完事\NDone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.56,0:13:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚...\NWhat did you ju--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.04,0:13:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  真不敢相信你\NOh my God, I can't believe you ju--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.99,0:13:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做到了\NYou did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.88,0:13:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自由了\NI'm free.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.72,0:13:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太惊人了\NThat was amazing!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.77,0:14:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\NI know.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.84,0:14:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说让你待在身边是个坏主意来着\NAnd who said having you around was a bad idea?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.50,0:14:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\NOh, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.49,0:14:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  塔克尔\NI don't know, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.18,0:14:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说的啊\NWho did?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.39,0:14:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道速跑算不上是真正的运动  你懂得吧\NYou know, track isn't a real sport, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.27,0:14:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一墙的绶带不这么想哦\NWell, I've got a wall full of ribbons that beg to differ.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.55,0:14:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绶带啊  \NRibbons. Do you keep them
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.98,0:14:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是跟你的发带和头绳放一块了\Nnext to your headbands and scrunchies?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.31,0:14:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  别说了\NDanny, stop talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.84,0:14:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望有办法知道她是不是还在那儿\NI wish there was a way to find out if she's still there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.72,0:14:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有办法的  回家就行了\NThere is-- go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.02,0:14:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  太冒险了\NNo, that sounds a little risky.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.90,0:14:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  让我换种说法\NAll right. Let me put this for you another way--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.45,0:14:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出我的公寓  跟你们的妈聊去\Nget out of my apartment and go talk to your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.05,0:14:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊\NYou know what, um.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.47,0:14:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能该走了\NI should probably go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.57,0:14:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不了解我们的妈\NYou don't even know our mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.32,0:14:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克  好主意  你是该走\NYou know what, Jack? That is a good idea. You should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.05,0:14:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呦  这话说的太直了点吧\NOuch. Don't know how much clearer that could be.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.85,0:15:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾你俩没戏\NSorry it didn't work out between you two.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.70,0:15:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说我和他一起走\NI meant I'm going with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.13,0:15:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走的时候记得锁门\NSo, uh, just lock the door when you leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.87,0:15:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  再见\NAll right?  Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.99,0:15:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看着不错哦\NHe seemed nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.89,0:15:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢相信啊  那么做就行了\NI can't believe that's all I had to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.96,0:15:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿  瓦内萨  我们完了"  挂机\N"Hey-yo, Vanessa. It's over." Click.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.21,0:15:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我不给你打电话\N"Don't call me 'cause I so won't
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.45,0:15:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也别给我打电话了"  挂机\Nbe calling you." Click.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.17,0:15:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们真的说过\NDid they really say
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.24,0:15:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想让我待在他们身边吗\Nthat they don't want me around?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.82,0:15:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁管他们怎么说啊\NWho cares what they said?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.15,0:15:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照我看你棒极了\NIn my book you are awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.69,0:15:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦内萨来了\NOh, it's Vanessa!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.80,0:15:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干了什么呀  你这女人\NWhat have you done, woman!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.02,0:15:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我不在\NLook, I'm not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.98,0:15:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  莱丽  警官\NHi, Riley. Officer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.60,0:15:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩儿子和艾玛躲在我公寓呢\NYour sons and Emma are in my apartment hiding out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.67,0:15:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你可以去解决一下\NSo maybe you can settle this
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.93,0:15:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我就有地方待了\Nso I can have my place back?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.02,0:15:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们躲起来了\NThey're hiding out?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.20,0:15:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲着我吗\NFrom me?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.39,0:15:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOh. Well, I think
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.83,0:16:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去抓个现行\Nthey're about to be found.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.37,0:16:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想来场复审吗  律师\NCare for a retrial, counselor?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.84,0:16:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求核准了\NPermission to approach the bench.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.68,0:16:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  求你了  我可以解释的\NMom, please. I can explain.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.39,0:16:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  解释吧\NAll right, go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.39,0:16:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不吗  我可不这么觉得\NNo? Didn't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.41,0:16:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是给每人都发过钥匙了\NAre you just giving keys to everyone now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.32,0:16:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么\NWhat are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.84,0:16:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尝试尝试史上最糟的约会\NJust trying out the worst date ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.77,0:16:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊  很顺利嘛\NOh, look, it's working.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.84,0:16:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去哪儿了\NWhere were you guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.48,0:16:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.15,0:16:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那儿多久了\NHow long have you been there?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.31,0:16:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够久啦\NLong enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.51,0:16:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哄艾玛睡觉\NI'll put Emma to bed,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.80,0:16:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就可以回归到\Nand then you can all return
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.15,0:16:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们定期的堕落日程上去了\Nto your regularly scheduled depravity.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.05,0:16:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以哄她睡觉\NI can put her down.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.26,0:16:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀\NOh. Oh, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.56,0:16:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也用不着外婆帮忙了\NDon't need grandma's help any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.32,0:16:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了\NI get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.77,0:16:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  妈妈  我不是那个意思\NNo, Mom. That's not what I'm saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.66,0:16:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是什么意思\NThen what are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.47,0:17:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  告诉你妈你怎么想的\NBen, just tell your mom how you feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.02,0:17:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NDanny?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.51,0:17:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我们俩挺好的\NOh, we're actually cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.39,0:17:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这样下去不会有进展的\NOkay, well, this is going nowhere,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.40,0:17:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们尝试点别的\Nso, uh, let's try something different.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.04,0:17:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  聚过来\NAll right, gather around.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.86,0:17:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay. Well,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.31,0:17:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们在调解课上新学到的\Nthis is something we just learned in our mediation class
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.98,0:17:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解决争纷的方法\Nfor settling disputes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.63,0:17:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得找个东西作为真相图腾\NI just need to find something to use as a truth totem.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.29,0:17:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调解课上我们可没学过那个\NWe didn't learn that in mediation.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.82,0:17:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我是在减肥夏令营学到的\NOkay, so I learned it at fat camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.84,0:17:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-减肥夏令营  -我早说过啦\N- Fat camp? - Told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.44,0:17:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NAll right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.54,0:17:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们的真相拨浪鼓\NThis will be our truth rattle.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.90,0:17:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是也罢\NOr not.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.55,0:17:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  谁抱着真相宝宝\NAll right. Um, so whoever's holding
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.07,0:17:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁就得说实话\Nthe truth baby has to tell the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.01,0:17:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然本很合事宜的抱着我们的图腾  本\NAnd since Ben is conveniently holding our totem, Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.67,0:17:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么名堂  有话直说\NOh, for crying out loud, just spit it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.12,0:17:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我还有不能说的吗\NYou can tell me anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.53,0:17:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骄横又粗鲁\NYou're overbearing and rude,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.02,0:17:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把钥匙和宝宝通通还给我\Nand I want my key and my baby back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.89,0:18:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,减肥夏令营里可没人这么口无遮拦\NNo one was ever that truthful at fat camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.02,0:18:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  等等\NMom, wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.10,0:18:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夹得好\NGood.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.00,0:18:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  先是赶我出门\NWhat? First you throw me out,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.62,0:18:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在又把我锁起来\Nand now you lock me in?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.70,0:18:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别摇摆了  做个决定吧  本\NMake up your mind, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.87,0:18:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  求你了\NMom, please. Look,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.40,0:18:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我应该一开始就告诉你真相的\NI know I should have just told you the truth from the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.64,0:18:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想我在身边的真相吗\NThat you don't want me around?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.11,0:18:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不明白\NNo, you don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.61,0:18:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是想要点空间\NWe just need some space.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.94,0:18:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有男人喜欢做的事\NWe have our guy stuff that we like to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.91,0:18:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如穿着内裤打游戏\NLike sit around in your underwear playing videogames
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.52,0:18:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陌生女子来而往之吗\Nwhile strange women flounce in and out?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.06,0:18:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你明白啊\NSo you do understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.86,0:18:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都不记得这其实是我的公寓\NI'm annoyed because everyone keeps forgetting
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.63,0:18:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让我很不爽\Nthat this is my apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.41,0:18:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把冰盒装满水你会掉块肉吗\NAnd would it kill you to refill an ice cube tray?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.97,0:18:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这些吗\NThat all you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.99,0:19:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长清单在另一间房里\NMy big list is in the other room.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.05,0:19:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.59,0:19:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\NCome here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.44,0:19:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真相  我朋友都是白痴\NTruth-- my friends are idiots
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.04,0:19:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望今晚我们可以从头来过\Nand I really wish we could start tonight over.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.44,0:19:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是白痴\NNot idiots,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.30,0:19:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是多疑\Njust suspicious.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.31,0:19:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不信任这家伙\NI truly don't trust this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.34,0:19:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼说的对  我撒谎了\NDanny's right. I lied.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.85,0:19:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要辅导\NI didn't really need tutoring.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.16,0:19:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想多多了解你\NI just wanted to get to know you better.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.50,0:19:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早猜到了\NI kind of knew that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.92,0:19:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  他刚才没抱着宝宝\NWait. He wasn't holding the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.67,0:19:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  你知道没你我不行\NMom, you know I couldn't do this without you,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.37,0:19:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可抚养艾玛的是我\Nbut I need to be the one raising Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.91,0:19:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要帮助  不是替代\NI need help, not a replacement.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.72,0:19:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样想吗\NIs that what you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.62,0:19:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想过替代你\NI never meant to replace you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.31,0:19:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过每天都来\NI just came to the city every day
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.27,0:19:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每时每刻都跟艾玛在一起\Nand spent every moment with Emma
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.90,0:19:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么都带着她\Nand did all the things with her
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.93,0:19:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能做了你想和她一起做的\Nthat you probably wanted to do with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.89,0:20:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上是替代了你了\NBasically replacing you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.23,0:20:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我就是这么干的\NYeah, that's what I was doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.92,0:20:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  真对不起\NOh, Ben, I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.01,0:20:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.98,0:20:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们设定好界限就行了\NWe just need to set some boundaries.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.92,0:20:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像高中时  你得先敲门\NIt was like in high school when you had to learn
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.47,0:20:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能进我房间\Nto knock before you came into my room.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.21,0:20:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人总得碰见那一幕十至十二次\NWell, you only gotta walk in on that
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.59,0:20:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能学乖好吗\N10 or 12 times before you learn your lesson.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.86,0:20:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我得把这个还你\NI guess I should give you this back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.50,0:20:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经多配了一副了  是吧\NYou already made a copy, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.04,0:20:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我孩子就是了解我\NOh, my baby knows me so well.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.79,0:20:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  莱丽\NReally, Riley?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.37,0:20:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开间房去吧\NGet a room.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.33,0:20:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我们是想开来着\NBelieve me, we are trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.94,0:20:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手指直接插进花生酱里吃\NFinger tracks in the peanut butter.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.87,0:20:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地板上的脚趾甲\NToenails on the floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.47,0:20:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有\NTwo words--
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.69,0:20:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾上头发的肥皂\NHairy soap.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.91,0:20:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.59,0:20:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-结束了吗  -当然  可以结束\N- Can we be done? - Oh yeah, sure. We can be done
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.46,0:21:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你想聊聊莱丽的话\Nif you want to start talking about Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.63,0:21:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-继续念吧  -就是  好的\N- Continue. - Exactly. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.49,0:21:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把毛巾当地巾\NUsing towels as bathmats,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.15,0:21:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把地巾当毛巾\Nusing bathmats as towels,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.83,0:21:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随意使用我的香波  护发素\Ntaking any of my shampoos, conditioners,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.26,0:21:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软膏  洗液  粉剂还有润发油\Nointments, lotions, powders or pomades.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.52,0:21:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鞋上带泥巴  健身背包汗津津\NOkay? Muddy shoes. Sweaty gym bags.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.05,0:21:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不自己买口香糖吃\NAnd never having your own gum.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.71,0:21:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-完了吗  -你觉得呢  当然没有\N- Is that it? - What do you think? No.
