[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.11,0:00:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恶心\NThat's disgusting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.28,0:00:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要来点吗  -来吧\N- Want some? - Hit me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.97,0:00:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没\NSee?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.02,0:00:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总能学到点新东西\NConstantly learning something new.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.77,0:00:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天学到的是  给宝宝洗完澡之后\NToday's lesson: Always get dressed for work
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.76,0:00:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再穿好衣服去上班\Nafter you give the baby a bath.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.34,0:00:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给塔克尔和丹尼叔叔问好\NSay good morning to Tucker and your Uncle Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.04,0:00:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  小宝贝\NHi, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.13,0:00:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们已经正式地\NOkay, so I think we're officially
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.81,0:00:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把所有婴儿用品都用光了\Nout of everything with the word "Baby" in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.21,0:00:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清单在哪儿\NWhere's the list?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.33,0:00:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么清单\NWhat list?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.37,0:00:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们用完一切之后\NThe one we should have started
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该照着采购的清单\Nbefore we ran out of everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.41,0:00:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不让你妈\NWhy can't you just ask your mom
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.14,0:00:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-去帮我们买点  -不  不行  不行\N- to go pick up some stuff? - Oh, no no no no no.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.69,0:01:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能让妈妈做\NThere will be no asking the mom anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经觉得我犯了弥天大错\NShe already thinks I'm making a huge mistake,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得我没责任感\Nthat I'm too irresponsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.87,0:01:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我要自己解决问题\NSo I'd like to get a handle on this
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.49,0:01:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让她打击我  然后跟我说\Nbefore she hits me with a giant
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.55,0:01:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不听老人言吃亏在眼前"\N"I told you so."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.74,0:01:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是准备好受打击吧\NThen get ready to be smacked,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.29,0:01:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我确定她已经在来的路上了\Nbecause I'm pretty sure she's on her way over.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.93,0:01:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  现在吗  你怎么知道\NWhat? Here, now? Why do you think that?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.42,0:01:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我告诉她你打算留着艾玛的时候\NBecause when I told her you decided to keep Emma,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.84,0:01:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只听到一句"噢  上帝啊"\Nall I heard was "Oh, dear lord,"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.76,0:01:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就是电话摔地板  轮胎摩擦的声音\Nthe phone hit the floor and tires squealing,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.08,0:01:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我就合理推断了一下\Nso I kind of put two and two together.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.59,0:01:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们得打扫干净\NOkay. Uh, we gotta clean up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.20,0:01:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  先给宝宝换尿不湿\NNo, change the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.83,0:01:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用  我刚换过了  整个计划表吧\NNo, I just did that. A schedule.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.40,0:01:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她特别喜欢做计划\NShe's crazy about having a plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.99,0:01:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要上白班\NOkay, I've got a day shift,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.45,0:01:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午六点回家\Nso I can be home by 6:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.51,0:01:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我要去溜冰场\NSorry, but I'm heading down to the rink.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.36,0:01:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和瓦内萨一起过禁欲星期六\NAnd it's emasculation Saturday with Vanessa.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.63,0:01:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们是去假装购物\NI think we're sham shopping.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.22,0:01:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟们  拜托\NGuys, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.95,0:01:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的想证明妈妈是错的\NI really want to prove mom's wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.89,0:01:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要向她证明我是个好爸爸\NI want to show her I can be a good dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.80,0:01:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛去哪儿了\NWhere's Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.49,0:02:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边  惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.71,0:02:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲  雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.55,0:02:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾玛  艾玛  -宝宝  宝宝\N- Emma? Emma? - Baby baby baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.81,0:02:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-宝宝在哪里  在哪里  -艾玛\N- Where's the baby? Where's the baby? - Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.09,0:02:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  找到了\NEmma? Found her!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.84,0:02:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在桌子下面  -等下  这不是我的牙架吗\N- Under the table. - Wait, here is my retainer.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.10,0:02:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在到处找它呢\NI have been looking everywhere for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.64,0:02:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.87,0:02:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点  抬住这头\NBe careful. Grab this end.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.88,0:02:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了吗  我数三下\NAll right? On three.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.24,0:02:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二  三\NOne, two, three.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.87,0:02:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.85,0:02:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咚咚咚  儿童服务来喽\NKnock knock, child services.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.35,0:02:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真应该让自己习惯听这个的\NYeah, you really should get used to hearing that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.82,0:02:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是玩玩捉迷藏罢了\NJust playing a little hide and seek.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.10,0:02:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来你在这呀  艾玛\NOh, there you are, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.95,0:02:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可真会藏\NYou're such a good hider.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.34,0:02:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  她不是在捉迷藏\NHoney, she's not hiding,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.75,0:02:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是想逃跑\Nshe's trying to escape.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.96,0:02:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不用担心  小艾玛\NBut don't you worry, little Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.94,0:02:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的仙女奶奶来救你了\NYour fairy grandmother is here to save you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.42,0:02:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛不需要什么拯救\NEmma doesn't need to be saved.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.75,0:03:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经处理好一切了\NI've got this under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.76,0:03:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到最后还会是我把你解救出来\NOnce again, it's going to be up to me to bail you out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.14,0:03:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少这次\NAt least this time,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.15,0:03:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不用飞去墨西哥了\NI don't have to fly to Mexico.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.50,0:03:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次旅行很棒\NThat was a good trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.08,0:03:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不喜欢说\NYou know I hate to say
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.62,0:03:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不听老人言..."  但是...\N"I told you so," But--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.24,0:03:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  这次不会有什么"不听老人言"的情况了\NMom, there is gonna be no "I told you so" this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.88,0:03:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有的话也是我跟你说\NYou know, unless it's me saying it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.95,0:03:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在告诉我你已经有\NSo you're telling me you've worked out a plan
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.84,0:03:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-照顾宝宝的计划了呗  -当然\N- to take care of this baby. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.46,0:03:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我正在跟他们俩商量呢\NI was just working it out with the guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.23,0:03:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你稍等片刻\NJust give me a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.94,0:03:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来救我\NPlease help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.90,0:03:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  上午我来照顾她\NFine. I've got her this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.78,0:03:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午我带她出去\NAnd I am taking her out this afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.73,0:03:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上我来照顾她\NAnd I've got her tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.01,0:03:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们的...  "宝贝计划"\Nwhich is what we like to call a plan!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.82,0:03:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们等等  奇奇和蒂蒂[松鼠大作战中的动画人物]\NYeah, hold up there, Chip and Dale.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.77,0:03:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你们先说清  如果我孙女\NJust so you know, if anything
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.75,0:03:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生任何一点状况\Nhappens to my granddaughter,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.71,0:03:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就死定了\Nyou're both dead men.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.19,0:04:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的...  "夺命威胁"\NWhich is what I like to call a threat.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.30,0:04:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  艾玛\NAll right, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.99,0:04:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们已经万事齐备了\NI think we've got everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.79,0:04:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的需要把所有的婴儿用品都带上吗\NDo I really need to take all the baby stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.24,0:04:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄   你就出去\NDude, you're gonna be gone
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.32,0:04:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四五个小时\Nfor four or five hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.15,0:04:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就带上片尿不湿和奶瓶就行了\NJust take a diaper and a bottle.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.51,0:04:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  怎么回事\NHey, man, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.76,0:04:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个计划根本不行\NThis plan is not working.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.57,0:04:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶粉吃完了  尿不湿也用完了\NI'm out of food, her diaper's history,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.60,0:04:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新换的一片随时有报废的危险\Nand the new one's gonna blow any minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.09,0:04:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显  要把宝宝带进更衣室\NAnd apparently there's some new rule
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.75,0:04:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得重新定规矩了\Nabout bringing babies into the locker room.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.56,0:04:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  老兄  你就不能围条毛巾什么的吗\NHey, buddy, why don't you put a towel on or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.64,0:04:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边有个宝宝呢\NI got a baby over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.18,0:04:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太粗鲁了  你得马上过来\NRude! You gotta get over here, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.02,0:04:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在分身乏术啊\NI-- I can't right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.12,0:04:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你稍等\NOkay, hang on one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.39,0:04:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  好的  我马上就去\NWhat? Okay. I'm on my way. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.14,0:04:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么总是塔克尔\NWhy is it always up to Tucker
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.18,0:04:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来拯救你们呢\Nto save the day?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.02,0:05:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塔克尔  怎么了  -不行  我不能干这个了\N- Hey, Tuck, what's going on? - I cannot do this, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.96,0:05:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大腿上全是尿  这尿还不是我撒的\NI've got a lap full of pee, and it isn't even mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.21,0:05:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我真的需要片尿不湿\NHey! I could really use a diaper out here
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.96,0:05:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们有人有\Nand I know one of y'all is holding.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.90,0:05:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  20块一片尿不湿  婴儿的成人的都行\N$20 for a diaper, miss. Please? Baby or senior,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.99,0:05:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个节骨眼上  尺寸都无所谓了  你别走啊\Nat this point, it really don't matter. Where you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.38,0:05:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我一收到你的信息就过来了\NI'm sorry. I came as soon as I got your message.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.44,0:05:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都还好吗\NIs everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.37,0:05:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没事\NYeah, she's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.51,0:05:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我要提醒你  陌生人\NThough I should remind you, complete stranger,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.09,0:05:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这里可不是托儿所\Nthat we're not a daycare center.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.38,0:05:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有人知道她是我的宝宝\NI'm five minutes away from getting fired
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.93,0:05:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我肯定会被炒的\Nif anyone finds out she's really my baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.86,0:05:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟老板说的她妈妈出去抽烟了\NI've been telling my boss the mom's outside smoking
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.87,0:05:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去了一个小时\Nfor the last hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.05,0:05:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是个酒鬼妈妈  真棒啊\NDouble Margarita, rocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.78,0:05:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  很明显  我是个\NSo, apparently, I'm a bad mom
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.17,0:05:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酗酒的坏妈妈\Nwith a drinking problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.40,0:05:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管它呢\NWhat the hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.66,0:05:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂  很抱歉\NI know, I know. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.83,0:05:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我得处理好这一切\NI just have to get this right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.61,0:06:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  艾玛  爸爸会想办法的\NDon't worry, Emma. Daddy will figure this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.30,0:06:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额  爸爸一会儿就回来了   你能照顾艾玛一会儿吗\NAnd he'll be right back. Can you watch Emma for a sec?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.77,0:06:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦  你不会跟我说\NWow. Wouldn't have pegged her
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.74,0:06:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个育儿专家吧\Nfor a parenting expert.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.36,0:06:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  她叫克洛伊\NPlease? Her name's Chloe.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.53,0:06:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周六都会过来吃蟹饼\NShe comes in every Saturday for crab cakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.78,0:06:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你也吃过的话\NAnd if you've ever had ours,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.51,0:06:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就会知道她的真正目标肯定不是蟹饼了\Nyou'd know that's not why she's really here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.66,0:06:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了\NOh, crapballs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.37,0:06:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好啊  小本  -你好\N- Hey, Benji. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.96,0:06:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人见过艾玛吗\NHas anyone seen Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.39,0:06:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来在这里啊\NOh, there she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.52,0:06:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前说对了  她真的很会捉迷藏\NOh, wow, you're right. She really is a good hider.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.10,0:06:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈\NMom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.18,0:06:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我没听到计划中\NI guess I missed out on the part of the plan
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.99,0:06:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要和酒吧零食一起玩的那部分\Nwhere she hangs out with the bar snacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.84,0:06:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  天呐  我的啤酒小零食里有个婴儿\NOh, no, there's a baby in my beer nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.84,0:06:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了点小状况  好吗\NSomething came up, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.06,0:06:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是所有的好计划都有后备计划\NBut like any good plan, I had a plan B,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.23,0:06:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划的名字就是  "莱丽计划"\Nalso known as Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.46,0:07:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有女孩子都渴望听到这样的话\NWords every girl just lives to hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.49,0:07:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也看见了  一切都没问题了\NSo as you can see, we've got this all under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.74,0:07:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想喝点什么吗  -我想跟你谈谈\N- Did you want something? - Yeah, I actually wanted to talk about
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.07,0:07:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜心小天使的未来\Nthat sweet little angel's future.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.74,0:07:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正打算重写遗嘱\NI was thinking about redoing my will--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.15,0:07:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建立个大学基金账户什么的\Nyou know, setting up a college savings account.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.99,0:07:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这倒是高瞻远瞩啊\NYou know, you really can't be too proactive.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.52,0:07:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我在上产业规划课...\NActually I've been taking this estate planning class--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.77,0:07:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊\NOh my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.83,0:07:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚想到个绝妙的主意\NI just had an amazing idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.12,0:07:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让莱丽帮你规划名下产业\NThat Riley should help you with your estate planning,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.66,0:07:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既能帮你省钱  又能让她增加实践经验吗\Nthus saving you money and giving her some real world experience?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.13,0:07:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这主意是挺妙的\NThat is an amazing idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.64,0:07:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩先聊着  我先歇会儿\NWhy don't you two discuss that while I go on break?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.29,0:07:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算说  我们点些油炸食品吧\NI actually was gonna say, "Why don't we order some fried things?"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.96,0:07:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我更欣赏他的提议\NBut I like his idea better.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.81,0:07:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要喝完它吗  -是的\N- Gonna finish that? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.82,0:07:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.58,0:08:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  她睡着了\NAll right, she's out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.35,0:08:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉睡的宝宝\NThere's nothing cuter
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.30,0:08:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是世上最可爱的人\Nthan a sleeping baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.55,0:08:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  不过他们一睁眼\NYeah, it's when they're awake
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.89,0:08:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就得格外小心了\Nyou gotta watch your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.77,0:08:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  他们用超萌的外表引你上钩\NYeah, they suck you in with their cuteness
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.74,0:08:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦你被套牢  就永无宁日\Nand then once they got you-- bam!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.25,0:08:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口水奶水满天飞  \NFluids are flying everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.58,0:08:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  你们都在\NOh. I'm so glad you're all here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.49,0:08:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直太完美了\NThis is perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.32,0:08:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划有变\NSo a little change of plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.47,0:08:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道今晚轮到我带艾玛  但是\NI know it was my turn with Emma tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.58,0:08:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个蟹糕控克洛伊邀我去她家\Nbut Crab Cake Chloe just invited me over
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.70,0:08:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,增进对彼此的了解\Nto get to know each other a little better,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.56,0:08:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥意思大家心知肚明吧\Nif you know what I mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.20,0:08:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚你自求多福吧\NYou're on your own tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.32,0:08:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真不走运啊  奶爸  -希望她喜欢小孩\N- Tough break, dad. - I hope she likes kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.43,0:08:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然你们没听懂我的潜台词\NSo obviously you don't know what I mean.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.41,0:08:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你们要去哪儿\NWait, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.26,0:08:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没听见我说的吗\NDid you all miss the part
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.39,0:08:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想要多了解我的那一段\Nwhere she said she wants to get to know me better?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.07,0:08:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听见  但你显然也没听见答案\NNo. But you obviously missed the part
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.72,0:08:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才不在乎呢\Nwhere we don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.25,0:09:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你同时还忘记了\NAnd also the part
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.51,0:09:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得已扔掉裤子的那一段\Nwhere I had to throw out my pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.19,0:09:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你们了\NPlease, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.08,0:09:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会很快完事的  额  也不至于那么快啦\NI'll be quick. Well, not that quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.60,0:09:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是某人安排了欢乐之夜\NIf someone hadn't already committed me
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.84,0:09:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬让我帮他妈妈修改遗嘱\Nto a fun-filled evening
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.38,0:09:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不定会考虑帮帮忙\Nof helping his mother with her will...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.98,0:09:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\NSorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.53,0:09:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  再让你帮忙就有点不合适了\NSo probably not a good time to ask for another favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.57,0:09:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你能不能在我妈面前替我美言几句\NBut if you could try to wedge in a word or two
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说我照顾艾玛尽心尽力\Nabout how great I'm doing with Emma,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.64,0:09:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,责任感超强那一类的话\Nyou know, how responsible I am?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.65,0:09:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我撒谎吗\NSo you want me to lie?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.30,0:09:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得都对\NLook, you're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.35,0:09:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过能自己搞定就一定会尽力\NI said I'll figure this out and I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.67,0:09:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我保证  -这才对嘛\N- I promise. - Good man.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩先别急着跑呀\NBut you two, not so fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.90,0:09:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说过会自己搞定\NYou just said you were gonna figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.97,0:09:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就靠你们俩搞定了\NAnd that's what I'm doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.41,0:09:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  兄弟们  我追克洛伊\NCome on, guys. I've been working on Chloe
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.16,0:09:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快五个星期了\Nfor, like, five weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.23,0:09:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我收拾头发做造型\NOkay, look, you can probably tell
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.42,0:09:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个大块头也把自己洗香香\Nfrom the extra hair product
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.31,0:10:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大概能猜得出来\Nand the fact that the big guy showered,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.26,0:10:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也有自己的安排\Nthat we have plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.34,0:10:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了  老弟\NSorry, little bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.36,0:10:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己想办法吧\NWork this one out on your own.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.09,0:10:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是你们逼我的\NI can't believe you're gonna make me do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.17,0:10:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要援引兄弟章程了\NI'm invoking the bro code.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.89,0:10:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是认真的吗\NAre you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.08,0:10:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在2010年6月21日\NJune 21st, 2010,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.16,0:10:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和那个隆胸的女招待调情  被瓦内萨抓包\Nwho covered for you when Vanessa caught you flirting
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.52,0:10:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁替你遮掩过去的\Nwith that unnaturally enhanced waitress?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.41,0:10:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中时  你和杰西卡·菲尔特申克的姐姐 \NSenior year, who told Jessica Feltshank
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.57,0:10:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在咱家树屋里乱搞  是谁帮你骗杰西卡\Nthat you were sick in bed when, in fact, you were having
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.44,0:10:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说你卧病在床的\Ncarnal knowledge of her sister in our tree house?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.03,0:10:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我罩着你们\NAnswer to both? I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.95,0:10:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你去吧\NFine. Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.49,0:10:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了  别等我回来了  \NYes! Don't wait up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.57,0:10:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得十点再给她喂一次奶\NAnd remember, she needs a second bottle around 10:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.85,0:10:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨这章程\NI hate that code.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.13,0:11:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱死那树屋了\NI loved that tree house.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.00,0:11:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能相信吗  过了这么多年\NDo you just believe that
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.56,0:11:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩竟然能坐在一起\Nafter all these years we would be here together?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.71,0:11:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  人生  妙不可言\NYep. Life is... Funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.91,0:11:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你带齐文件了\NSo if you have all the info,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.65,0:11:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们就...  -都在这里\N- we should be able-- - Oh, here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.18,0:11:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个有条理的人\NI like to stay organized,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.33,0:11:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把重要文件都放在一起\Nso I keep all my important papers together.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.93,0:11:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  老实说  \NHonestly, Riley,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.40,0:11:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底那儿做错了\Nwhere did I go wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.35,0:11:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一时可说不清\NSo many ways to go with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.00,0:11:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是指本这件事儿上\NI meant with Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.30,0:11:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他表现的还行啊\NI think he turned out all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.72,0:11:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实\NIn fact,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.76,0:11:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我遇到的最有责任感的男人之一\Nhe's one of the most responsible young men I've ever met.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.60,0:11:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  咱们怎么没喝就说胡话了呢\NOh. I'm sorry, I didn't know we were drinking before this meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.12,0:11:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他周六晚哪儿也不去  正老实呆在家\NHe is sitting at home on a Saturday night
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.04,0:11:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心照顾女儿呢\Ntaking care of his daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.26,0:11:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他很有责任心\NThat sounds awfully responsible to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.72,0:11:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHi.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带给你的  我肯定这是瓶好酒\NFor you, and I'm pretty sure it's good
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.68,0:11:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为产地我读不出  而且还有软木塞\Nbecause it's from a place I can't pronounce and it has a cork.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.84,0:12:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  我去拿酒杯\NNice. I'll get some glasses.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.05,0:12:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -随便坐\N- All right. - Make yourself comfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.22,0:12:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这住处利用率...\NYour place is really...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.79,0:12:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是很高\Nefficient.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.76,0:12:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有一个独立的...\NSo is there a separate...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.57,0:12:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息空间\Nsleeping area?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.82,0:12:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙发压一下就变成床了\NThe futon flips out into a bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.00,0:12:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请你来家里  希望你不会误解为\NI hope you didn't think I was too forward
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.71,0:12:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对感情太急于求成\Nby asking you to come over.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.38,0:12:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"急于求成"是我的最爱\NForward is my favorite direction.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.72,0:12:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许多人都误会了\NSo many guys get the wrong idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.76,0:12:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都以为是被请来是约炮的\NThey just automatically assume you want to hook up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.71,0:12:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于让我等到一位正人君子\NIt's so nice to finally meet a guy
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.37,0:12:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人高兴\Nwho's not like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.93,0:12:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本的问题在于\NSee, the trouble with Ben is,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.31,0:12:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和他爸  老丹尼\Nhe's exactly like his father,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.74,0:12:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一模一样\NDanny Sr.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.18,0:12:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个男人\NNow there was a man
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.44,0:12:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从不知责任为何物\Nwho was clinically allergic to responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.29,0:12:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢维勒先生\NI liked Mr. Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.29,0:12:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年7月4日独立日的烟火表演\NGod, he always put on the best
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.73,0:12:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都是最棒的\N4th of July fireworks displays.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.79,0:13:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他眉毛都烧光了  右手只有四个手指\NHe has no eyebrows, and only four fingers on his right hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.14,0:13:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢老天这不妨碍他\NI was lucky he could sign
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.44,0:13:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能签字离婚\Nthe divorce papers.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.61,0:13:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有这样一个老爸\NBut with a father like that,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.49,0:13:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就意味着我要承担起全部责任\Nit meant that I had to be the responsible parent.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.03,0:13:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要以身作则\NThe role model.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.77,0:13:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉里·霍夫曼是谁\NWho's Larry Hoffman?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.20,0:13:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  怎么  不  我从没听说过\NWhat? Why? No, I've never heard of--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.53,0:13:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  别别  给我\NNo no no, give me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.02,0:13:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我  快给我  拿来\NGive it, give it, give it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.95,0:13:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可怪了  你说不认识他  可这上面\NThat's funny that you don't know him,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.50,0:13:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写着你18岁时和他在拉斯维加斯\Nbecause it says here that you two were married
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.88,0:13:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登记结婚了\Nin Vegas when you were 18.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.54,0:13:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉把你的沙发床放倒了\NI really am sorry about your futon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.25,0:13:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不想让你以为\NI certainly don't want you to get the impression
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.75,0:13:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和那些人一样  \Nthat I'm one of those guys. 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.25,0:13:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前你留给我的唯一印象是\NMy only impression so far
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.17,0:13:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个蹩脚的骗子\Nis that you're a horrible liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.30,0:13:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你细想\NWhich, if you think about it
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.38,0:13:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-未必是件坏事  -为什么\N- is a good thing. - Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.55,0:13:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁愿意跟精明的骗子约会啊\NI mean, who'd want to go out with a good liar?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.60,0:13:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我是不会\NNot me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.13,0:13:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点绝对能给你加分\NDefinitely something for the plus column.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.50,0:13:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能做点什么\NIf there's anything I can do
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.87,0:13:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为自己加分吗  -也许能做\N- to help that total-- - There might be
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.40,0:14:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么一两件事\None or two things.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.36,0:14:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是你的宝宝吧\NThat's not your baby, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.77,0:14:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  天啊  不是  你能想象要是的话\NWhat? Oh God, no. Could you imagine?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.60,0:14:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不如杀了我\NShoot me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.96,0:14:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我姐姐的\NIt's my sister's.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.27,0:14:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -没什么\N- Why? - Oh, no reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.82,0:14:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很可爱\NShe's cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.19,0:14:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安  艾玛\NGood night, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.99,0:14:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  我正在琢磨\NHey, Tuck, I was thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.55,0:14:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩没必要今晚都在吧\NThere's really no reason we both need to stay in tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.99,0:14:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我出去了\Nso I'm out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.59,0:14:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟拉里离婚了\NSo I divorced Larry,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.58,0:14:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跑回家  嫁给了老丹尼\NI rushed home and I married Danny Sr,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.97,0:14:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我初婚就应该嫁给他\Nwhich is what I should have done in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.15,0:14:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪  如果没有发生这件事\NSo, oddly, if this hadn't happened,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.49,0:14:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的两个活宝就不会诞生了\Nyour two greatest accomplishments never would have been created.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.34,0:14:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道我的纹身的\NHow did you know about my tattoos?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.40,0:14:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是丹尼和本\NI'm talking about Danny and Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.60,0:14:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则你就不会有这两个儿子了\NYour sons never would have been born.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.37,0:14:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒也是\NThat's a really good point,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.44,0:14:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次你可以试试\Nbut maybe next time you could try it
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.03,0:14:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哪壶不开提哪壶\Nwithout the sledgehammer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.42,0:14:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都能看出来\NEven I can tell
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.73,0:15:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最近对本很苛刻\Nthat you're being especially hard on Ben lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.32,0:15:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我跟说这个\NI mean, I know he'd hate me
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.26,0:15:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会恨我的\Nfor telling you this,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.25,0:15:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真应该让你帮帮他\Nbut he could really use your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.66,0:15:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想啊\NWell, I am trying to.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.96,0:15:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但他不让我帮他  -也许因为怕你\N- He won't let me. - Maybe because it's not worth
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.30,0:15:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是念叨"不听老人言吃亏在眼前"\Nthe "I told you so" that always comes with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.38,0:15:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个母亲  这是本能反应\NWell, I'm a mother. It's a package deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.93,0:15:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍夫曼太太  如果不犯点小错\NWell, you didn't get to be a mom
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.47,0:15:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不会知道该怎么做妈妈的\Nwithout making a few mistakes, Mrs. Hoffman.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.89,0:15:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能承认\NSo, maybe if you could admit
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.41,0:15:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一直这么完美的\Nthat you weren't always so perfect
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.23,0:15:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本也应该会承认他需要帮助\NBen could admit that he needs help.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.11,0:15:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不打算饶了我是吧\NYou're just not gonna let it go, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.49,0:15:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你去跟他谈谈\NNot until you go talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.63,0:15:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他需要你\NHe needs you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.91,0:15:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你莱丽\NThanks, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.13,0:15:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你变成了一个\NYou know, you've turned out to be
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.54,0:15:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秀外慧中的女孩子\Na pretty smart young lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.20,0:15:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你应该保持下去\NI think you might just make a go of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.66,0:15:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-做律师吗  -不是  保持身材\N- Being a lawyer? - No, keeping the weight off.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.59,0:15:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你几乎没碰过那奶酪\NYou barely touched the cheese board.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.53,0:15:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  宝贝  我们得谈谈\NBen honey, we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.39,0:15:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.07,0:16:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小公主  你好啊\NOh hey, princess.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.59,0:16:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在睡觉觉啊\NOh, you're taking a nap.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.24,0:16:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大个子  我们俩没必要\NHey, big guy, there's really no reason
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.02,0:16:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚都在这里  对吗\Nwe both need to stay in tonight, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.21,0:16:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  再见了\NSo, um, see you!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.43,0:16:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗\NHello?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.26,0:16:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在吗\NIs anyone here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.93,0:16:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.42,0:16:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  还有那谁\NDanny? The other one?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.84,0:16:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来要轮到老娘说\NOh, this is gonna be the mother
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.46,0:16:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不听老人言吃亏在眼前"了\Nof all "I told you so"S.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.42,0:16:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧\NIs everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.84,0:16:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是忍不住想艾玛\NI can't stop thinking about Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.25,0:16:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\NOf course.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.97,0:16:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已婚啊  同性恋啊  害怕承诺啊什么的\NMarried, gay, commitment issues--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.88,0:16:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐总是这么倒霉\Nit's always something.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.17,0:16:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的\NNo no, it's not that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.31,0:16:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛是我的女儿  我有个女儿\NEmma's my daughter. I have a daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.45,0:17:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是今天酒吧里那个小女孩\NShe was that little girl at the bar today.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.35,0:17:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看吧  我知道应该一早告诉你\NLook, I know I should have told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.77,0:17:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是担心如果我说了\NI guess I was just afraid that I wouldn't be here
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.65,0:17:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不能跟你在这里做这些事情了\Ndoing this with you now if I had.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.07,0:17:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的\NHey, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.53,0:17:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这其实是另一件加分的事情\NIt's actually another thing for the plus column.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.89,0:17:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -真的\N- Really? - Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.24,0:17:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想看她的照片吗\NDo you want to see her picture?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.88,0:17:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\NSure.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.88,0:17:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上她第一次翻身了\NI think she rolled over for the first time this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.42,0:17:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我打个电话回家看看  我就放心了\NYou know, maybe I'll call and check in and then I'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.09,0:17:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  你在哪呢\NDanny, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.47,0:17:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  我见到了几个新队友\NHey, man. I just met a couple of my new teammates
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.71,0:17:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在外面喝酒呢  -艾玛呢\N- out for a drink. - Ben: Where's Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.68,0:17:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她睡得很香  塔克尔看着她呢\NOh, she's totally conked out. Tucker has it covered.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.92,0:17:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你...\NI thought you were--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.11,0:17:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  再给我两秒钟\NNever mind. Two seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.38,0:17:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  我就是想...\NHey, Tuck, I was just--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.97,0:17:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在打保龄吗\NAre you bowling?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.14,0:17:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛呢\NWhere's Emma?!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.61,0:17:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了\NOh. I gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.03,0:18:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  没事  老爸在这呢\NEmma, it's okay, daddy's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.18,0:18:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  艾玛  你在哪\NOh my God, Emma, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.40,0:18:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  别介啊  别这样啊\NOh my God. No no no. This can't be happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.74,0:18:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -找人呢\N- Oh my God. - Looking for someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.90,0:18:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  谢天谢地你没事\NEmma. Thank God you're okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.09,0:18:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是万分抱歉\NI am so so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.65,0:18:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为再也见不到你了呢\NI thought I might never see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.73,0:18:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不会让你离开我的视线了  好吗\NI never want you out of my sight, ever. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.57,0:18:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是世界上最差劲的父亲\NI'm the worst father in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.31,0:18:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  你能抱一下艾玛吗\NRiley, can you take Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.40,0:18:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  宝贝\NCome here, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.99,0:18:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备好了  开始吧\NI'm ready. Let me have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.91,0:18:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论你对我说什么\NBut just know that nothing you can say to me
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.95,0:19:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不会比我的自责更严重\Ncan be any worse than what I'm already saying to myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.83,0:19:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  本\NActually, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.61,0:19:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想说\NAll I wanted to say
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.08,0:19:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你骄傲\Nis that I'm proud of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.29,0:19:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是碰巧没看到我把宝宝独自丢在家\NDid you miss the part where my baby got left alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.80,0:19:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼两岁的时候  我有次把他丢在沃尔玛了\NI once left Danny at a Wal-Mart when he was two.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.52,0:19:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-结果呢  -他就此失踪了\N- What happened? - He was never seen again.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.59,0:19:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想说  我也犯过错误\NMy point-- I made mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.05,0:19:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种感觉\NBut that feeling?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.00,0:19:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种精神煎熬\NThat gut-wrenching,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.73,0:19:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛心脏停跳的感觉\Nheart-stopping,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.27,0:19:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我的宝宝出了什么事\Nif-anything- happens-to-my-child-
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.42,0:19:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会死掉的感觉\NI-think-I-will-die feeling--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.85,0:19:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你刚才的感受\Nwhat you just had-- that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.31,0:19:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是让你知道  你已为人父母\NThat is what let's you know that you're a parent.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.08,0:19:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我相信你会不遗余力地\NAnd, honey, I guarantee that you will do anything
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.21,0:19:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保再不会发生这样的事情了\Nto make sure that you never feel that again.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.62,0:19:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺你\NSo congratulations,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.21,0:20:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  你是个父亲了\Nnow you're a dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.31,0:20:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我觉得你会成为一个特别棒的老爸\NAnd I think you're gonna be a pretty great one.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.41,0:20:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不知道我在做什么\NBut I don't know what I'm doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.40,0:20:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然说我知道了\NI know I said I got this,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.72,0:20:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实我一头雾水\Nbut I just so don't got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.78,0:20:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾玛  -如果你还没懂的话\N- Emma! - Well, if it isn't--
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.99,0:20:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就当我站在这里  自言自语吧\Nme standing here, talking to myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.51,0:20:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还好吗\NIs she all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.08,0:20:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有三个男孩在对她献媚呢\NShe's got three boys fawning over her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.19,0:20:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分女孩都吃这一套滴\NWorks for most girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.35,0:20:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  真对不起\NEmma, I am so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.28,0:20:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不会再发生这样的事情了\NThis will never happen again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.31,0:20:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  没事了\NGuys, it's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.12,0:20:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都会犯错\NWe all make mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.54,0:20:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们真的需要别人的帮助\NBut I think we could definitely use some help.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.10,0:20:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你  妈妈\NI need you, mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.01,0:20:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐看高潮\NWait for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.88,0:20:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不听老人言吃亏在眼前啊\NI told you so.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.74,0:20:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝宝已经就位\NBaby's at the ready...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.79,0:20:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦耶\NOh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.38,0:21:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒数  三  二\NIn three, two,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.12,0:21:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  翻滚吧\None, roll!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.02,0:21:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  艾玛  到我这边来\NCome on, Emma, come here!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.05,0:21:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-滚啊  -来艾玛  滚到老爸这\N- Roll! - Come on, Emma. Roll to daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.65,0:21:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻滚吧  快滚啊\NRoll roll roll.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.44,0:21:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚到这边来  用头带动身体\NThis way, lead with your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.29,0:21:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧  艾玛\NAre you kidding? Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.88,0:21:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-加倍下注还是弃权  -加倍\N- Double or nothing? - You're on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.03,0:21:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生们  下注吧\NGentlemen, place your bets.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.66,0:21:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是宝宝的"翻滚时刻"\NIt's time for baby roll.
