[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.66,0:00:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正式出发喽\NAnd we are officially out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.26,0:00:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纽约的妹子们  准备好迎接\NLadies of New York, get ready for the return
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.39,0:00:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅哥本和潮男塔克尔的回归吧\Nof the benjinator and the tuckatron.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.78,0:00:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们听见了吗\NOh, do you hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.66,0:00:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,200万女人在对你们翻白眼呢\NThat's the sound of two million women rolling their eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.54,0:00:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别小瞧我们\NDo not underestimate us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.54,0:00:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们单独出动已经魅力无敌\NAlone we're impressive,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.77,0:00:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强强联手  那绝对势不可挡\Nbut together, we're a force to be reckoned with.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.72,0:00:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  女童子军也这样\NYeah. So are the girl scouts.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.27,0:00:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你们玩儿得开心  我都准备好了\NBut have a good time. I am all set.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.69,0:00:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆米花和真人秀\NI have enough popcorn and reality TV
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.01,0:00:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足够我撑到艾玛上大学了\Nto last me until Emma goes to college.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.05,0:00:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你留在这儿\NHey, thanks for staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.09,0:00:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从艾玛来了以后\NWe haven't had a real bro night
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.16,0:00:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们两兄弟就没机会爽一把\Nsince Emma showed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.08,0:00:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.17,0:00:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩总有办法毁了你的生活\NKids have a way of just sucking the life out of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.35,0:00:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗\NAll right, ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.73,0:00:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牙齿\NTeeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.11,0:00:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻子\NNose.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.54,0:00:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口气\NBreath.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.39,0:00:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  -我们走吧\N- Ready. - Let's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.20,0:00:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老天  多少...  -嘘\N- Oh my God, how much... - Shh!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.54,0:00:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  是艾玛  对吧\NOh, sorry. Emma. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.30,0:00:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是艾玛\NNo, not Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.22,0:00:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老妈\NMom.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.09,0:01:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}傅满洲:萨克斯·罗默小说中的大胡子人物形象
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.09,0:01:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  傅满洲回归了  \NSweet. The return of fu mom-chu.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.61,0:01:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拍照不  -好啊\N- Picture? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.40,0:01:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-今晚玩好了吗  -我的天  爽歪歪\N- Good night? - Oh my God. The best, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.10,0:01:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中一个保镖的表姐的男朋友的\NOne of the bouncer's cousin's boyfriend's
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.84,0:01:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹是本的同事\Nsister's works with Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.54,0:01:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们直接就进去了\NOkay? So we pretty much sailed right in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.92,0:01:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那地方挤爆了\NThe place was wall to wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.13,0:01:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和塔克尔失去联系长达40分钟\NI lost Tucker for, like, 40 minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.09,0:01:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他就被人潮给举着传递过来了\Nwhen he got passed over the top of the moshpit.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.09,0:01:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些醉鬼干的  毛手毛脚的  \NDrunken mobs. Okay? Kinda handsy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.39,0:01:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一切都是值得的  因为他们把我挤到了\NBut it was so worth it 'cause they dropped me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.39,0:01:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个辣妹跟前\Nright in front of this crazy hot girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.23,0:01:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没听你说过这些细节\NOh. I have not heard these details.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.61,0:01:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  她觉得我很搞笑\NOh, dude. She thought I was hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.81,0:01:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就是\NOf course.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.80,0:01:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  她刚从洛杉矶搬过来\NListen, she just moved here from L.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.55,0:01:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  长而乌黑的秀发\NMan, long dark hair,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.35,0:01:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅力四射的笑容\Njust gorgeous smile,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.55,0:01:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她叫...  -艾娃\N- her name was... - Ava?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.06,0:01:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.34,0:01:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你怎么知道\NWait, how did you know...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.35,0:01:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明晚要和她出去\NI'm going out with her tomorrow night.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.00,0:02:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边 惊喜无极限*\N*It‘s amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.96,0:02:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲 雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions.*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.82,0:02:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  所以你真要和艾娃约会吗\NWait, so you actually made a date with Ava?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.65,0:02:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是真正的约会啦\NWell, not an actual date,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.79,0:02:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过她让我打电话给她\Nbut she said I should call her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.98,0:02:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很确信这不是为了检查\NAnd I'm pretty sure it's not to see
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.20,0:02:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她手机有没有坏\Nif her phone works.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.70,0:02:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我知道我和她刚认识\NOkay. I know I just met her,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.25,0:02:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得我有资格替她说话  好吗\Nbut I feel like I can speak for her. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.94,0:02:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对你没兴趣\NShe was not into you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.83,0:02:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们该祈祷我打给她以后\NThen let's hope I don't get my heart broken
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.21,0:02:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心没碎\Nwhen I call her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.06,0:02:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是她让我打的\NWhich she asked me to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.50,0:02:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吗  -好啊\N- Okay? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.65,0:02:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不准给我的妞打电话  懂吗\NYou are not calling my girl, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.84,0:02:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都不能打电话\NNo one is calling anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.53,0:02:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我没带泳衣哎\NBut I didn't even bring my swimsuit.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.49,0:02:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不能打\NNo one is calling anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.57,0:02:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸取我的教训吧\NLearn from my mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.89,0:02:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在卡尔加里[加拿大城市]打球时\NWhen I played in Calgary,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.12,0:02:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了一个妹子和队友打架\NI fought over a girl with one of my teammates.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.24,0:02:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  结果我赢了妹子\NSure. I got the girl,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.19,0:02:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我输了兄弟\Nbut I lost the guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.21,0:02:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  我连妹子都没了\NThen I lost the girl, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.86,0:03:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着手机还丢了\NThen I lost my phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.41,0:03:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那周真是倒霉透顶\NIt was a really bad week.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.06,0:03:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  我懂了\NYou're right. I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.58,0:03:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  你的意思呢\NTucker, what do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.49,0:03:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊\NFine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.27,0:03:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都不给她打电话\NNeither of us will call her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.12,0:03:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说好了吗  -说好了\N- Agreed? - Agreed.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.51,0:03:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意吗\NAgreed?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.45,0:03:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我同意\NI said agreed.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.59,0:03:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我起来了\NI'm up!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.49,0:03:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错过了啥\NWhat did I miss?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.89,0:03:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我画成傅满洲了  是不是\NYou fu mom-chued me, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.09,0:03:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈\NMom?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.92,0:03:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你昨晚用我电脑了吗\NWere you on my computer last night?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.78,0:03:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  亲爱的\NOh, yeah, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道不  你应该养成\NAnd you know what? You should really make a habit
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.34,0:03:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,删除历史浏览记录的习惯\Nof erasing your history.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.35,0:03:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远不知道谁会偷窥你的电脑\NYou never know who's gonna be snooping around.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.59,0:03:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建议不错啊\NThat's excellent advice,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.99,0:03:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辣妹79号\Nhotbon79.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.37,0:03:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你上网交友的个人资料吗\NIs this your online dating profile?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.66,0:03:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  没错\NYes. Yes, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.64,0:03:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好羞愧的\NAnd there is nothing to be ashamed of.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.39,0:03:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不藏着掖着\NI have nothing to hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.58,0:03:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面写着你是个寡妇\NIt says you're a widow.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.81,0:04:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你爸对我来说跟死了差不多\NYeah, well, your father's kind of dead to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.11,0:04:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年龄这栏  你写的是...\NAnd for age, you said that you're...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.96,0:04:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  小姑娘\NYou listen up, little miss,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.16,0:04:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可能青春永驻\Nyou ain't gonna look like that forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.70,0:04:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听见了吧  所以趁你还年轻貌美\NYeah, you heard me. Enjoy those
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.01,0:04:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受吧\Nwhile they're up high.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.16,0:04:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,网上交友就是这么回事儿  好吗\NThis is how online dating works, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.24,0:04:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人人都撒谎\NEverybody lies.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.57,0:04:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你驾照上的体重\NIt's like the weight on your driver's license.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.04,0:04:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个提示罢了\NIt's more of a suggestion.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.86,0:04:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以当我想要重新开始生活\NSo I would appreciate a little support
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.46,0:04:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能支持我一下  我会很感激\Nwhile I am trying to restart my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.13,0:04:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生彻底完了\NMy life is officially over.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.98,0:04:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\NMine too.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.80,0:04:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  睡袍那啥\NMom, robe.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.69,0:04:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  不好意思\NOh, God. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.70,0:04:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游骑兵队要举办大型媒体日\NThe rangers are having a big media day,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.79,0:04:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公关部门想让我做点演讲\Nand the front office wants me to give some kind of speech.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.04,0:04:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超有趣的啊\NOh, how fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.53,0:04:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见过丹尼在镜头前的样子吗\NHave you seen Danny on camera?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.28,0:04:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像被车撞了的小鹿\NHe looks like the deer after it got hit by that car.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.17,0:04:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会去的\NI'm not doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.65,0:05:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩就不能别那么损吗\NCould you people possibly be less supportive?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.05,0:05:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  但时间还早  我还没睡醒呢\NYeah, but it's early. I'm still waking up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.92,0:05:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒\NWheeler,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.49,0:05:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松点\Nrelax.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.10,0:05:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为了生活能让人赛场上流血\NYou make people bleed for a living,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.73,0:05:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信公共演讲难不倒你的\NI'm pretty sure you can handle a little public speaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.90,0:05:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揍人  简单\NCrushing bones, easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.77,0:05:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出口成章  还是免了\NPutting words one after another, no thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.42,0:05:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  不如我帮你啊\NOkay, well, then let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.44,0:05:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我参加过模拟法庭研讨班\NI just took this mock trial seminar,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.15,0:05:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是班里的明星啊\Nand I was pretty much the star of the class.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.65,0:05:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没乱  乱的是你\NI'm not out of order. You're out of order!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.04,0:05:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个体系都乱套了\NThis whole system is out of order!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.70,0:05:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你临时想的吗\NYou just made that up?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.11,0:05:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到吗  我永远做不到你那样\NSee, I could never do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.52,0:05:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以的\NBut you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.80,0:05:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望你能像我欣赏你一样\NI just wish you could see yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.06,0:05:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认可自己\Nthe way that I see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.82,0:05:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底怎么看我的\NHow do you see me exactly?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.98,0:05:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个迷人有爱心又慷慨的人\NYou're an amazing, loving, big-hearted guy
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.55,0:05:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对每件事都满怀激情\Nwho's passionate about everything that he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.05,0:05:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是我  激情四射\NThat's me. Full of passion.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.56,0:05:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需要一起全力以赴\NWe just need to hunker down together.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.25,0:06:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好这是我的强项\NFortunately, I'm an excellent hunkerer.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.60,0:06:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就太好了\NOkay, then it's perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.32,0:06:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再退缩了\NIt's time you stopped holding back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.27,0:06:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么想来着\NI was just thinking the same thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.03,0:06:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一言为定\NThen it's a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.30,0:06:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你失望的\NI won't let you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.42,0:06:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚才是什么意思\NWhat was that all about?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.55,0:06:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽给我出了些主意\NRiley just had a few ideas for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.72,0:06:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  看上去你对她也有点意思嘛\NYeah. It looked like you had a few ideas for her too.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.79,0:06:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.96,0:06:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有  没意思\NNo. No ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.57,0:06:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我的眼睛告诉我\NLook at me and tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.36,0:06:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对大裤衩没意思\Nthat you don't have a crush on fatpants.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.98,0:06:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我做不到  -为啥\N- I can't. - Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.45,0:06:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你的睡袍那啥  -老天  不好意思\N- Your robe. - Oh, God, sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.05,0:06:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  别别别\NOh, no, no, no, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.37,0:06:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你喜欢老爸的手机\NI know you like daddy's phone,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.70,0:06:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但上次你随便乱按\Nbut the last time yov baby dialed someone,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.48,0:06:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把警察都给招来了\Nthe police showed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.40,0:06:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看哪  你差点打给艾娃了\NLook, you almost called Ava.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.49,0:07:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你差点打给艾娃了\NYou almost called Ava.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.23,0:07:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTucker!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.03,0:07:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克\NTuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.96,0:07:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖  这是爸爸的手机\NOkay, here's daddy's phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.17,0:07:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗\NOkay?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.29,0:07:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要按这里\NIf you just hit right here,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.82,0:07:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  就这儿\Nokay? Right...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.89,0:07:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着  按这里\NHold on, right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.81,0:07:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要 好了...\NIf you just, uh, okay...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.75,0:07:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这儿哦\Nright here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.51,0:07:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  艾玛  集中精力\NNo, Emma. Focus.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.10,0:07:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  按那里\NOkay? Just... just right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.36,0:07:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成了\NYes!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.05,0:07:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈啰\NHello?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.18,0:07:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是本吗  有人吗\NBen? Is anybody there?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.38,0:07:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHello?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.16,0:07:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  拜托  拜托  拜托\NOh, please please please please please please.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.89,0:07:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}艾娃来电
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.39,0:07:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有电话哦\NIt seems we have a call.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.51,0:07:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHello?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.05,0:07:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾娃\NAva?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.47,0:07:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  你打过来我很高兴\NOh, yeah. So nice of you to call.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.26,0:07:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦\NWhat's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.77,0:08:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你显然不是第一个\NWell, you're definitely not the first guy
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.99,0:08:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约我来酒吧见面的人\Nto ask me to meet him at a bar,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.53,0:08:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是第一个让我要觉得该给小费的人\Nbut you are the first guy I feel like I should tip.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.45,0:08:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我通常不这么做\NI don't usually do this,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.54,0:08:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但凑巧约你的日子我上班\Nbut it happens to be bring your date to work day.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.57,0:08:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  你打给我的时候我正往这儿走\NPlus, I was already on my way here when you called me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.53,0:08:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你打给我的\NWhen you called me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.68,0:08:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是艾玛...\NWhen Emma...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.88,0:08:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不重要啦\Nit's not important.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.97,0:08:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得纽约怎么样\NSo, what do you think of New York so far?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.57,0:08:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这儿\NI like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.72,0:08:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有活力  有美食\NGreat energy, good food...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.96,0:08:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有小帅哥\NCute guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.40,0:08:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对很多男人说过这话了吗\NBeen talking to a lot of those?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.17,0:08:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会把秘密都告诉你\NI'm not gonna tell you all my secrets.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.24,0:08:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你再帮我弄一杯\NUnless you make me another one of these.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.79,0:08:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上回来\NI'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.08,0:08:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾娃  你的手机\NAva, your phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.80,0:08:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}塔克尔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.96,0:08:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  塔克尔\NHello, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.77,0:08:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你打给她了\NI can't believe you called her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.30,0:08:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没打电话  我发的短信嘛\NI didn't call her. I texted her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.23,0:08:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后她短信我让我打给她\NAnd then she texted me back to call her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.21,0:08:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严格来说  我只是在回短信\NSo technically, I was returning her text.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.98,0:08:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当初可不是这么定的\NThat is not what we agreed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.75,0:08:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我至少为了男人的尊严让艾玛帮我打\NI at least have the decency to have Emma call for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.46,0:09:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说这事儿没完呢\NI want you to know that this is not over, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.82,0:09:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没赢呢\NYou have not won.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.84,0:09:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会打给艾娃  然后我们约会\NI am calling Ava, and we are going out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.93,0:09:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想怎么比较选择咱俩都行\NShe can compare and contrast all she wants,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.82,0:09:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥一点意见都没有\NI ain't got no issues.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.44,0:09:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真要为这事儿和我杠上吗\NYou're really willing to go up against this?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.02,0:09:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我奉陪  狭路相逢勇者胜    \NFine. May the best man win.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.07,0:09:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}Best man还有伴郎的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.07,0:09:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说伴郎吗  那百分百是你\NBest man? Oh, then that'll definitely be you
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.28,0:09:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我和艾娃的婚礼上\Nat my and Ava's wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.87,0:09:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿好看点哦\NWear something nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.49,0:09:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是莱丽·佩兰  这里是发刷新闻网  \NThis is Riley Perrin, hairbrush news network.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.18,0:09:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很激动  马上就要采访到纽约游骑兵队的\NI'm thrilled to be talking with New York ranger,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.30,0:09:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼·维勒  丹尼\NDanny Wheeler. Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.65,0:09:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我作为这支优秀队伍的一员\NTell me what it's like to be a part
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.58,0:09:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何\Nof this exciting team.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.33,0:09:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NWell,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.51,0:09:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是...\Nthe thing is...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.16,0:09:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你想让我说什么\NI don't know what you want me to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.76,0:09:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  进展太快\NOkay. Too advanced.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.67,0:09:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从基础开始\NUm. We'll start with the basics.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.59,0:09:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起来\NStand up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.57,0:09:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先做一下深呼吸集中精神\NWe'll do a little deep breathing to focus us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.82,0:09:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  深吸气\NAll right? Deep breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.74,0:10:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  不对  用这儿\NNo, no, no, here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.70,0:10:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从隔膜呼吸\NFrom your diaphragm.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.52,0:10:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦  你是用腹肌切奶酪的吗\NWow. Do you grate cheese on this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.27,0:10:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿\NHere.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.60,0:10:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你感受一下我是怎么做的\NFeel how I'm doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.20,0:10:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗\NComfortable?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.20,0:10:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极舒服\NVery.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.17,0:10:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒  你没事吧\NWheeler, you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.53,0:10:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发了一分钟呆\NYou got all slack-jawed there for a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.53,0:10:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把口水弄我身上\NLet's try not to drool on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.98,0:10:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专心点\NFocus.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.22,0:10:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你儿子真是个白痴\NYour son is an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.50,0:10:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得缩小一下范围[两个儿子]\NReally gonna have to narrow it down.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.81,0:10:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.01,0:10:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的裤子呢\NWhere are my pants?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.83,0:10:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪条\NWhich ones?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.69,0:10:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的\NAll of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.06,0:10:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥好像不巧把送去洗了那么几条\NOh, I might've run a few things down to the laundromat.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.72,0:10:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20分钟后我要去见艾娃了\NI'm meeting Ava in 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.57,0:10:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你囧了\NThat could be awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.83,0:10:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我带个好吧\NSay "Hi" For me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.23,0:10:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  她早晚会看到哥不穿裤子的样子的\NHey, man. She gonna see me without pants sooner or later.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.53,0:11:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不过是给哥省了点时间\NYou're just saving me some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.03,0:11:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\NOh, hi, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.72,0:11:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是母子连心的感觉终于来了\NMaybe it's that mother-child bond
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.79,0:11:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么预感你有话要跟我说呢\Nfinally kicking in, but I'm getting the sense you want to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.27,0:11:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于莱丽  你说的对\NIt's Riley. You were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.07,0:11:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实喜欢她  一直都喜欢\NI do like her. I've always liked her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.31,0:11:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\NOh, I knew it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.17,0:11:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你们以前每天放学在房间里\NOh, wait. So is that what you guys were doing
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.71,0:11:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就做这些事情吗\Nevery day up in your room after school?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.15,0:11:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"妈妈  你出去  我们正学习呢"\N"Get out, mom. We're studying."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.41,0:11:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么也没发生过\NNothing has ever happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.54,0:11:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她都不知道我喜欢她\NShe doesn't even know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.96,0:11:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我确实想亲她来着\NThough I did just try to kiss her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.54,0:11:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我竟然想亲莱丽\NOh my God! I just tried to kiss Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.17,0:11:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是怎么了\NWhat's wrong with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.20,0:11:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明摆着就是个坠入爱河的小伙子\NWell, apparently you're a boy in love.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.91,0:11:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不想做那个坠入爱河的\NBut I don't want to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.71,0:11:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说  我想让她坠入爱河\NOr... I want her to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.53,0:11:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯呢  那样会更好\NYeah, that's better.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.50,0:11:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她为我坠入爱河  那才是我想要的\NHer in love with me. That's what I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.69,0:11:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  不好意思\NWell, I'm sorry, honey,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.76,0:11:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没法让别人为你坠入爱河\Nbut you can't make somebody fall in love with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.74,0:12:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你多努力\NNo matter how hard you try.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.20,0:12:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话\NIf you could,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.79,0:12:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字就是邦妮·邦·乔维了\N my name would be Bonnie Bon Jovi,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.58,0:12:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在应该正半裸着泡在热气腾腾的浴缸里\Nand I'd be floating in a hot tub, topless right now, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈呀\Nmom.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.59,0:12:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办\NWhat am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.21,0:12:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庆幸你有个像莱丽这样的\NWell, be grateful that you have a friend
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.61,0:12:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐于奉献及关爱他人的朋友\Nas devoted and caring as Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.80,0:12:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  跟你借条裤子  希望你别介意\NOh, hey, man. Borrowing these. Hope you don't mind. okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.11,0:12:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去赴个约  你...  天啊\NGot a date to get to, you... oh my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.02,0:12:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我丹尼  知己不易求\NTrust me, Danny. Good friends are hard to find.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.20,0:12:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而  这地方傻子无处不在\NHowever, stupid ones are lying all over the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.89,0:12:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出去吗\NGoing somewhere?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.30,0:12:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  等我老妈一到  我就\NYeah, as soon as my mom gets here, I was...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.17,0:12:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去酒吧见艾娃吗\Nhoping to meet Ava down at the club?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.44,0:12:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也听说她要去酒吧了\NI heard she was gonna be there, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.32,0:12:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  得了吧\NDude, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.62,0:12:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果咱俩同时现身  那多奇怪啊\NIt's gonna get really weird if we both show.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.44,0:13:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好在不会发生这种情况\NOh, well, fortunately that's not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.23,0:13:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为令堂正在手机店买电池\NBecause your mom's at the cell phone store
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.29,0:13:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来那块莫名其妙就不见了\Nreplacing her battery that mysteriously disappeared.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.45,0:13:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远不会得手的\NYou'll never get away with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.86,0:13:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还真就得手了\NOh, I believe I just did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.15,0:13:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点忘记带唇膏\NForgot my lip balm.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.65,0:13:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定用得上的\NDefinitely gonna need this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.84,0:13:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跳得真好\NYou're a really good dancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.73,0:13:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是需要点灵感\NI just needed some inspiration.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.00,0:13:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.05,0:13:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵感[还有喘气的意思]\NInspiration.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.50,0:13:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  这里太热了\NYeah, me too. It's pretty hot in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.32,0:13:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾娃  -本\N- Ava, hey. - Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.62,0:13:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊喜啊  想喝点东西吗\NWhat a surprise. You want to get something to drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.54,0:13:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有伴了\NI'm kind of with somebody.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.61,0:13:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  没看见他\NOh, sorry. I didn't see him there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.59,0:14:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  这位是塔克尔  塔克尔  这位是本\NBen, Tucker. Tucker, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.55,0:14:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好吗哥们\NHey, what's up, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.92,0:14:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛呢\NWhere's Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.03,0:14:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人照看她\NI got it covered.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.76,0:14:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  你怎么看\NWhat you think, Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.05,0:14:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看起来有21岁吗\NThis guy look 21?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.01,0:14:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个认识吗\NDo you two know each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.71,0:14:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不认识  -从来没见过\N- No. - Never seen him before.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.03,0:14:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  回头再聊啊\NOkay, well, I guess I'll talk to you some other time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.36,0:14:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NRight. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.23,0:14:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回见\NAnother time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.66,0:14:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧\NRun along now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.27,0:14:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跳得真好\NWow. He's really good.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.09,0:15:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-艾娃  -艾娃等等\N- Ava. - Ava, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.32,0:15:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  刚才简直诡异爆了\NOkay, that was just full on weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.58,0:15:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说实话吧\NHere's the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.04,0:15:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是室友\NWe're roommates.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.54,0:15:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不一定非做室友\NWe don't have to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.62,0:15:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不要让这事\NSo don't let that stand in the way
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.96,0:15:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妨碍我们的缘分\Nof you and me fulfilling our destiny.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.62,0:15:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和两个人约会已经让我很不舒服了\NDating two guys was already a little out of my comfort zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.49,0:15:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是室友\NBut, roommates?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.92,0:15:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真心不行\NI don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.32,0:15:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.64,0:15:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是想骗你\NWe weren't trying to lie to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.08,0:15:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我们都觉得你很特别\NIt's just, we both think you're pretty special.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.42,0:16:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值得我们为你而战斗\NAnd obviously worth fighting for.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.83,0:16:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看啊  没理由我们俩都放弃\NLook, there's no reason that one of us
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.70,0:16:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你觉得可以的话\Nshouldn't at least get to know you better.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.14,0:16:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩至少有一个可以和你深交一下\NIf that's cool with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.83,0:16:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想让我选吗\NYou guys want me to choose?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.74,0:16:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就选吗\NRight now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.22,0:16:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们确定吗\NAre you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.75,0:16:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心  他很坚强的\NDon't worry. He's tough.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.40,0:16:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他承受得了\NHe can take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.06,0:16:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选塔克尔\NI guess I pick Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.88,0:16:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈  选的真...\NHa! In your...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.55,0:16:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\Nwhat?!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.49,0:16:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我能跟你谈谈吗\NBen, can I talk to you for a sec...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.91,0:16:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用废话了\Ndo not need to have this conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.43,0:16:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥好的很\NI'm cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.01,0:16:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她选了你  成王败寇\NShe picked you. Winner, loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.67,0:16:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了\NI get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.72,0:16:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理解不了  但我认了\NDon't understand it. But I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.44,0:16:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想跟你确认一下\NI just wanted to make sure if you were okay
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.78,0:16:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果艾娃一会来你能不能接受\Nif Ava came by the apartment later.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.91,0:16:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题\NNo issues whatsoever.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.47,0:16:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主要因为我要去丹尼的新闻发布会\NMainly because I'll be at Danny's press conference.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.62,0:16:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走运了  我老妈会照顾艾玛\NOh, and lucky you... mom will have Emma,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.55,0:16:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方全归你了\Nso the place is totally yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.55,0:16:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞没搞错\NWhat is your problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.51,0:16:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你说过咱俩没事的\NI thought you said you were cool with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.38,0:16:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是没事啊\NI am cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.53,0:17:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事就是这样子的\NThis is me being cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.48,0:17:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能借你的新香水用用吗\NWould you mind if I borrowed some of that new cologne...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.32,0:17:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没到那地步\NI'm not that cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.22,0:17:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒\NWheeler?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.74,0:17:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来真迷人\NWow. You look amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.94,0:17:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得怎么样\NWhat do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.07,0:17:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得出来是体育专业人士吗\NDoes this say sports professional?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.94,0:17:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  还像一个乔装的超级英雄\NThat, or superhero in disguise.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.47,0:17:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会非常棒的\NYou're gonna be so great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.14,0:17:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.51,0:17:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  我不知道我以前有没有说过\NAnd, Riley, I don't know if I've ever said this before...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.10,0:17:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常感激生命中有你\NI'm really grateful to have you in my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.19,0:17:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道没有你我该怎么办\NI don't know what I'd do without you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.44,0:17:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你永远都不需要知道\NThen let's hope you never have to find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.73,0:17:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我迟到了吗  我错过什么了吗\NHey, am I late? Did I miss anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.44,0:17:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间刚好\NHey, perfect timing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.88,0:17:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得下一个就是他了\NI think he's up next.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.30,0:17:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个吗\NNext?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.50,0:17:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是不是很热啊\NOh! Is it hot in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.05,0:17:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得坐一会\NI think I'm gonna sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.82,0:17:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\NYou're gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.92,0:17:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔在哪里\NWhere's Tucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.99,0:17:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他在哪里\NWhere do you think he is?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.19,0:17:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忙着出演塔克尔秀呢\NBusy starring in "The Tucker show."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.08,0:17:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你照我说得邀请他了吗\NYou invited him like I asked you to?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.39,0:18:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木有\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.20,0:18:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正他也不会来\NIt's not like he'd come anyways.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.47,0:18:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和艾娃忙着呢\NHe's too busy with Ava.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.57,0:18:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  你犯什么毛病了\NDude. What is the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.56,0:18:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就跟你说过\NThis is exactly what I told you would happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.00,0:18:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是一个团队\NYou guys are a team.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.38,0:18:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个团队的意思就是你们要互相支持对方\NAnd being on a team means you have each other's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.76,0:18:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论比赛打成什么样\NThat no matter how you're playing,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.27,0:18:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有个人庆祝你们的胜利\Nsomeone's always there to celebrate your wins
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.91,0:18:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者为失利复仇\Nand avenge your losses.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.74,0:18:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有团队\NWithout a team,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不过是冰上一个孤独的失败者\Nyou're just some loser out there alone on the ice.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.40,0:18:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰球不是这么打的\NAnd that's not how you play hockey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.67,0:18:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活也不是\NOr life.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.35,0:18:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游骑兵队加油\NGo rangers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.34,0:18:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  -对  加油游骑兵\N- Yeah. - Yeah. Go rangers!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.98,0:18:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  丹尼你太棒了\NOh my God. Danny, you were amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.03,0:18:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做到了\NYou did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.28,0:18:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我做到了吗  -是啊\N- I did? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.17,0:18:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做到啦  谢谢你\NI did. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.48,0:18:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒  过来一下\NWheeler, over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.83,0:18:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.85,0:18:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可太感人了\NWell, that was rousing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.11,0:19:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\NI'll say.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.92,0:19:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们排练的一样\NJust like we practiced.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.71,0:19:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了\NI should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.00,0:19:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我一直扮演一个守门员\NI feel like I've been playing goalie
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.39,0:19:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过防守的是我自己的队伍\Nagainst my own team.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.80,0:19:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  就他能用运动打比方啊\NOh, what? He's the only one who can use sports analogies?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.81,0:19:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你没带钥匙吗\NBen? Did you forget your key?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.30,0:19:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想撞见\NI didn't want to barge in on whatever
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.76,0:19:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能会发生也有可能不会发生的那件事\Nmight or might not be happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.52,0:19:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想跟你说\NI just wanted to tell you that
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.24,0:19:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你值得拥有一个好女孩\Nyou deserve a great girl
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.42,0:19:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及一个好朋友\Nand an even better friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.53,0:19:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  哥们\NThanks, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.54,0:19:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是关于那一点\NBut about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.72,0:19:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.71,0:19:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这姑娘疯了  你得帮帮我啊兄弟\NThat girl is crazy. You have got to help me, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.07,0:19:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从她到这开始嘴就没停过  一直说啊\NShe has not stopped talking since she got here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.30,0:19:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我一只耳朵已经聋了\NI think I am deaf in one ear.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.87,0:19:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  咱们这么办\NAll right, here's what we'll do.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.09,0:19:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得让她对你失去好感\NWe just have to turn her off of you...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.99,0:20:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  你觉得这可能吗\Noh, please. Like that's possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.15,0:20:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重罪犯  枪支爱好者\NFelon. Gun nut.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.62,0:20:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头虱\NHead lice.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.89,0:20:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪教\NCult.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.14,0:20:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟们\NHey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.31,0:20:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-用丹尼好不  -同意\N- Danny? - Sold.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.89,0:20:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都还好吧\NEverything good out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.85,0:20:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快好了\NOh, it's about to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.85,0:20:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  过来\NOkay, come here. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.54,0:20:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾娃  这是本的哥哥\NAva, hey. This is Ben's brother,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.46,0:20:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼维勒  纽约游骑兵队的\NDanny Wheeler. New York ranger.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.07,0:20:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我超爱冰球\NOh my God, I love hockey!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.54,0:20:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到冰球我能聊好几个小时\NI could talk about it for hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.60,0:20:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂的\NI figured. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.11,0:20:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能先陪陪她吗\NIf you could just keep her company
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.50,0:20:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再去搞点...\Nwhile we go run out for more...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.39,0:20:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-啤酒  -啤酒  太好了\N- beer? - Beer sounds great.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.83,0:20:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  没问题\NSure, no problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.12,0:20:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  哥们\NThank you, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.46,0:20:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个才啊\NThat was genius.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.74,0:20:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  有我呢  一直挺你\NHey, man. I always got your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.92,0:20:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾娃说对了一件事\NOne thing Ava was right about...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.52,0:20:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们斗舞那事太怪了\Nthat dance off was weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.46,0:20:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐要拍的"短小"  "简单"\NI'll make this fast and easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.12,0:20:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两个词也是姐高中时代的代名词\NWhich FYI was two of my nicknames in high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.02,0:20:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个40岁的城市妙女郎\NI'm a 40-and-fab city gal
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.03,0:20:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚开始我的祖母生涯\Nwho's living with early onset grandmahood.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.10,0:20:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离异  哦耶  猜对了\NDivorced, oh yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.36,0:21:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失业  但我也做很多事情哦\NUnemployed? Not if you count how I work it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.42,0:21:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢  我喜欢火锅\NI like... I like fondue.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.04,0:21:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以随时把食物蘸着东西吃\NAnytime you can dip food in other food,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.86,0:21:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人间美味啊\Nthat's game on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.93,0:21:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你爷们到能够承受这些\NIf you're man enough to take this on,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.46,0:21:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联系辣妹79好呦\Ncontact hotbon79.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.66,0:21:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外  你至少要这么高\NAlso, you need to be
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.87,0:21:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能驾驭姐这身躯\Nthis tall to ride this ride.
