[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.66,0:00:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想把孩子她妈请过来的\NWell, I would have invited the baby's mother,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.31,0:00:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我都没见过她\Nbut I never met her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.40,0:00:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她是本的某个比较有"收获"的炮友\NShe was one of Ben's more productive one night stands.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.29,0:00:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  有三个字我是再也不想听到了\NOkay, three words I never want to hear again,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.41,0:00:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"真可爱"\N"That's so cute."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.93,0:00:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不可爱吗\NWasn't that cute?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.02,0:00:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有史以来最好的送礼会了\NBest shower ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.14,0:00:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  五个多小时就那么飞逝而过了\NYeah, those five hours just flew by.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.09,0:00:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打再多场橄榄球赛\NThere's not enough football in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.64,0:00:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能让我忘了刚刚发生的事\Nto erase what just happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.71,0:00:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.65,0:00:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点儿忘了我的礼物呢\NI almost forgot my present.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.22,0:00:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激动人心的时刻到了\NSo exciting!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.16,0:00:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里已经够多了\NThere can't actually be more.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.26,0:00:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  这个湿纸巾加热器有啥用\NI mean, seriously, what are we gonna do with a wipes warmer?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.18,0:00:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还真想用下这玩意儿呢\NOh, I was actually gonna hold on to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.87,0:00:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  难道只有艾玛才能享受\NWhat? Oh, Emma's the only one who can appreciate
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.71,0:00:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这温暖的湿纸巾带来的那份柔软舒适不成\Nthe soothing comfort of a warm towelette?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.12,0:00:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来不错哦\NThat does sound nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.44,0:00:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  所有东西都可以退的\NDon't worry. Everything can be returned.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.86,0:00:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小公主终于有她的专属座驾了\NFinally, my little princess has her carriage.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.91,0:00:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很完美吧\NIsn't it perfect?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.33,0:01:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  小公主\NHello, princess.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.22,0:01:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说"所有东西"对吧\NYou said, "Everything," Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.94,0:01:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边 惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.90,0:01:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲 雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions.*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.85,0:01:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我突然不再计较\NOkay, suddenly don't care
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.41,0:01:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸以前从不让我开敞篷车的事了\Nthat dad never let me drive the convertible.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.17,0:01:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连新婴儿车的那股味道都能闻到呢\NAh, it's even got that new stroller smell.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.10,0:01:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真的酷毙了\NOh-h, this thing is so cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.10,0:01:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-婴儿车不错嘛  -你好\N- Nice stroller. - Hello...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.47,0:01:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下更酷了\NAnd it just got a whole lot cooler.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.32,0:01:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们推她出来走走而已\NWe just drove her off the lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.14,0:02:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去挺快的\NLooks fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.56,0:02:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也要看是谁在推啊\NWell, that depends on who's pushing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.70,0:02:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话一出口他肯定没戏了\NThere's no way he's recovering from that line.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.81,0:02:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有戏呢\NIt's not over yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.58,0:02:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -我会打给你的\N- Okay. - I'll call you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.05,0:02:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小子挺自信的嘛\NThat boy's got confidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.67,0:02:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自婴儿车的自信\NStroller confidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.37,0:02:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫佐伊\NHer name's Zoe.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.41,0:02:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算钓到个名字以"Z"开头的了\NFinally one for the "Z"S.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.89,0:02:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这婴儿车太有用了\NThis stroller is amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.43,0:02:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把钥匙给我  我来推\NYeah, give me the keys. I'm driving.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.28,0:02:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我所说的颇有收获的室外活动\NThat is what I call a very successful outing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.02,0:02:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为啥咱们现在待在室内\NSo why are we "In-ing"?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.30,0:02:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们得回大街上溜达去\NWe need to get back on the street.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.91,0:02:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  急什么\NDude, what's the rush?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.89,0:02:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能没注意到\NMaybe you haven't noticed.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.38,0:02:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我整个就是一块把妹磁铁\NBut I'm a relationship magnet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我享受偶遇  我渴望偶遇\NI enjoy casual. I want casual.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.84,0:02:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是偶遇从来没渴望过我\NBut casual has not wanted me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.87,0:02:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到现在  明白不\NUntil now, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.17,0:02:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我的趣味之窗  伙计们\NThis is my fun window, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.65,0:02:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不能就这样关了它\NDon't shut it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.74,0:02:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦  那车没人管都能发挥威力呢\NWow! It even works by itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.26,0:02:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我的\NThat one's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.62,0:02:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  他来这里做什么\NOh, crap! What's he doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.84,0:02:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是亨德森  酒吧的老板\NThat's Henderson, the owner.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.09,0:02:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五分钟前我就该上班了\NMy shift started five minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.23,0:02:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你装作不认识我\NYou don't know me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.33,0:03:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好  先生  不知不觉已经积了\NAfternoon, sir. Things can really pile up
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.52,0:03:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一堆活儿要干了\Nif you don't stay on top of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.34,0:03:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  沃克  -是维勒\N- Hey, Walker. - Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.45,0:03:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便吧  你见过麦克尼利吗\NWhatever. Have you seen Mcneely?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.61,0:03:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  说不定在休息室呢\NNope. Could be in the break room.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.52,0:03:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不太清楚  因为我都没去那里休息过\NDon't know, 'cause I've never been in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.22,0:03:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见到他了跟我说一声\NWell, let me know when you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.85,0:03:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟他谈谈新的管理职位的事\NI wanna talk to him about a new management position.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.17,0:03:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么  亨德森先生\NExcuse me, Mr. Henderson.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.57,0:03:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爸难道在这里吗\NOh, is my father here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.89,0:03:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我"H"就成\NCall me "H."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.89,0:03:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  H\NOh, you got it, H.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.95,0:03:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以叫我"W"\NYou can call me "W."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.38,0:03:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者"B"  因为我叫本\NOr "B" For Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.04,0:03:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过既然咱们是以姓氏来称呼的话  那就...\NBut we're doing the last name thing, so it's--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.83,0:03:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎样  沃克\NWhat do you want, Walker?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.45,0:03:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我姓维  无所谓了\NIt's Wheel-- never mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.94,0:03:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于那个新职位\NAbout that new position, I
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.31,0:03:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我自己就是做管理层的料\Nlike to think of myself as management material.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.88,0:03:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对是当领导者的料  而不是当个下属\NI'm definitely a leader, not a follower.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.27,0:03:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你需要的是个下属\NUnless you need a follower.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.38,0:03:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就会追随你的领导\NAnd then I'll follow your lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.43,0:03:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我挺喜欢你的  真的\NLook, I like you. I really do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.03,0:03:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为人风趣  长得也帅  还善于调情\NYou're fun, you're personable, a little flirtatious.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.69,0:03:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您的夸奖  所以呢\NThank you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.73,0:03:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具备所有我要求的酒吧招待应有的品质\NAll qualities I'm looking for in a bartender.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.11,0:03:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这些品质还不足以当一个管理者\NBut not in a manager.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.46,0:03:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经做了你梦寐以求的工作了  孩子\NYou've got yourself a dream job, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.42,0:04:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情享受吧\NEnjoy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.49,0:04:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你会考虑下我吗\NSo you'll think about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.07,0:04:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小公主终于回来了\NFinally. There's my little princess.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.34,0:04:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  你可得记着\NMom, remember,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.46,0:04:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校的心理医生早跟你说过\Nthe school therapist said you had to
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.85,0:04:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后不能再那样叫我了\Nstop calling me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.88,0:04:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为艾玛和你一起回来了呢\NI thought Emma was with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.96,0:04:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弄了套亲子装过来\NI got us matching outfits.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.05,0:04:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她被那两个家伙带出去了\NShe's out with the guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.07,0:04:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了\NSomething wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.46,0:04:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有  -工作上出啥事了吗\N- No. - Did something happen at work?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.81,0:04:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  怎么了  我好着呢\NNo, why? I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.97,0:04:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你可骗不了我哦\NHoney, you can't hide things from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.57,0:04:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前你打破了我挡风玻璃  被我知道了\NChip my windshield, I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.42,0:04:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放火烧了地下室  也被我知道了\NSet the basement on fire, I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.13,0:04:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞大女生肚子了...\NGot a girl pregnant--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.67,0:04:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  你不是又搞大一个女生的肚子了吧\Noh my God, you did not get a girl pregnant again, did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.62,0:04:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能给我个香蕉和安全套呀\NSomebody get me a banana and a condom!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.78,0:04:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我发誓  那种事有一次就够了\NNo! I swear, once is enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.09,0:04:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我能当比酒吧侍应生更好的人吗\NDo you think I could ever be more than a bartender?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.51,0:04:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你枕头底下的那些宣传手册\NHoney, it wasn't the community-college fairy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.34,0:05:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是社区大学的仙女姐姐塞进去的\Nwho left all those brochures under your pillow.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.67,0:05:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然还能更有作为\NOf course you can do more.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.39,0:05:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以成为你想成为的任何人\NYou can be whatever you want to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.10,0:05:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒吧里有个经理的空缺\NThere's a manager position open at work.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.96,0:05:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  咱也别异想天开了\NOkay, let's not go crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.59,0:05:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可不止关乎我自己了\NIt's not just about me any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.93,0:05:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要考虑下艾玛的将来\NIt's Emma's future too.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.35,0:05:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此  那你就回去\NWell then, you go back there
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.48,0:05:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得到肯定答复誓不罢休\Nand don't take "No" For an answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.80,0:05:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他有可能因为你太固执\NUnless there's a chance he might fire you
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.54,0:05:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而让你辞了现有的这份工作走人\Nfrom the job you already have for being too pushy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.50,0:05:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那样的话  那你就算了吧\NThen, you know what? I'd just let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.06,0:05:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的加油打气  老妈\NThanks for the pep talk, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.63,0:05:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时随地  小公主\NAnytime, princess.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.61,0:05:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来看看\NHey, check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.63,0:05:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个不同的女孩  两个不同的电话\NTwo different girls, two different numbers.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.95,0:05:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者称之为\NOr as I like to call it,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.36,0:05:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"帅哥的困扰"\N"Hot guy problem."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.62,0:05:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没想到呢\NWhat? I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.14,0:05:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿到了十一个呢\NI got 11.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.73,0:05:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这方面还是新手好伐\NI'm new at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.54,0:05:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情享受  这可能是你们最后一次推这辆车了\NSavor it, because that might have been your last ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.99,0:05:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老妈在里面  -现在\N- Mom's here. - Now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.58,0:05:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我们该怎么办\NWait? What are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.63,0:05:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要这辆婴儿车\NNo, I need this stroller.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.03,0:05:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放轻松  我的朋友\NRelax, my little friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.89,0:05:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来搞定我妈那边  给你\NI'll handle Mom. Take this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.99,0:05:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  艾玛  跟着爸爸升职去\NAll right, Emma. Let's go get Daddy a promotion.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.02,0:06:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话还是由我来说\NBut let me do the talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.17,0:06:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  记住\NCome on. And remember,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.06,0:06:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟着我的节奏\Njust follow my lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.32,0:06:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.65,0:06:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈\N- Hey, Mom. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.17,0:06:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塔克尔卖了你的婴儿车  -老天  你个叛徒\N- Tucker sold your stroller! - Oh my God, you tattletale!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.75,0:06:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\NWhat?!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.82,0:06:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽\NRiley!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.04,0:06:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  你能帮我照看下艾玛吗\NPerfect. Can you watch Emma for two seconds?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.65,0:06:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然  -谢谢\N- Yeah. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.69,0:06:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐车舒服吧\NOoh, sweet ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.19,0:06:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H  还好吗\NH. Hey, what's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.59,0:06:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我  维勒  沃克  W\NIt's me-- Wheeler Walker W,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.55,0:06:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那个会调情的酒吧招待\Nyour slightly flirtatious barkeep.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.66,0:06:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不用回家的么  沃克\NDon't you ever go home, Walker?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.59,0:06:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见你比见我老婆还多\NI have wives I see less than you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.49,0:06:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚还在想我们之前的谈话\NI was just thinking about our conversation from earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.63,0:06:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你说错了  而我是对的\NAnd I think you're wrong and I'm right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.17,0:06:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我能胜任那个职位\NI mean-- I mean I'm right for the job,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.66,0:07:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你不考虑我是错的\Nand you're wrong not to consider me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.92,0:07:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在洗手间对着镜子\NHmm. Wow. When I said this to my myself
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.56,0:07:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的时候可顺溜多了\Nin the bathroom mirror, it was really smooth.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.82,0:07:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我很欣赏\NLook, I appreciate
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.72,0:07:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这副"摩拳擦掌要大干一场"的架势\Nthe whole "Eager kid" thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.64,0:07:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要的是一个更有责任心的人\Nbut I'm looking for someone a little more... responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.10,0:07:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正是我竭力想成为的人\NAnd that's exactly what I'm trying to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.11,0:07:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个孩子要养而且...\NI've got a kid now and I--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.78,0:07:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有孩子了\NYou've got a kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.07,0:07:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\NYeah...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.68,0:07:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫艾玛\NHer name's Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.40,0:07:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有位娇妻呢\NAnd a hot young wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.81,0:07:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\NYes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.06,0:07:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我确实  是个有家室的人\NYes, I do... family man.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.45,0:07:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么比这更需要责任心了吧\NAnd there's nothing more responsible than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.21,0:07:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然你认识的居家男人还不太多\NYou obviously don't know a lot of family men.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.94,0:07:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉打搅你们\NHi, I am so sorry to interrupt.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不得不把她交给你了\NBut I've got to hand her off.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.12,0:07:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一小时后我还有场考试  现在\NI have an exam in an hour, and right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.25,0:07:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她比我更懂得移民法的事了\Nshe knows more about immigration law than I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.82,0:07:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子她妈还在上法学院  快迟到了\NLittle lady goes to law school and she's running late.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.08,0:07:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不快跑可就真要迟到了\NWell, not running, but she should be.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.36,0:07:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快去  快去  -上法学院吗\N- Go go go. - Law school, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.91,0:07:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要兼顾看孩子肯定不容易吧\NMust be tough with the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.57,0:07:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚还在说有你在艾玛身边真好\NI was just saying how great you are with Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.66,0:07:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  亲亲她  跟她拜拜\NOkay, give her kiss. Wave bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.62,0:07:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太贴心了  -再见\N- Aww, that is so sweet. - See ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.42,0:07:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家庭的重担确实都压在本身上\NBut Ben truly does all the heavy lifting.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.33,0:07:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我基本都没怎么帮忙的\NI mean, I'm barely even helping out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.19,0:08:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这位娇妻真是令人印象深刻呢\NThat is one impressive wife you've got there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.94,0:08:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"比我更好的另一半"可不是白叫的\NWell, I don't call her my better half for nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.82,0:08:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个女儿跟她差不多大\NGot a daughter about her age.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.82,0:08:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可悲的是  她们都没啥相似之处\NSadly, they have nothing in common.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.86,0:08:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也许低估你了  维勒\NI might have underestimated you, Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.79,0:08:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊\NOh my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.52,0:08:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你第一次叫对我名字呢\NThat's the first time you've said my name.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.04,0:08:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天咱们一起吃个午饭并谈谈工作的事吧\NLet's have lunch tomorrow and discuss that job.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.22,0:08:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得叫上你的律政俏佳人\NOh, and bring your lovely little barrister with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.55,0:08:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你都能找着个这么好的老婆\NIf you can get a woman like that,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.63,0:08:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我之前还真是看错你了\Nthere really must be something about you I'm missing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.29,0:08:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次谢谢你的夸奖\NAgain, thank you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.16,0:08:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是怎么回事\NWhat was that about?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.99,0:08:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有两个问题要问你\NTwo questions for you:
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.75,0:08:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天午饭时间你有事没\NWhat are you doing tomorrow for lunch?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.23,0:08:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有就是你愿意嫁给我吗\NAnd... will you marry me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.72,0:08:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要假扮你老婆呢\NI am not pretending to be your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.88,0:08:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我需要你\NBut I need you!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.96,0:08:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是我那个脆弱谎言的粘合剂\NYou're the glue of my very flimsy lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.51,0:08:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天去不了  我要和杰克吃午饭\NWell, I can't tomorrow. I'm having lunch with Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.87,0:08:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪个杰克  -就是我的交往对象\N- Jack? - The guy I'm seeing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.90,0:08:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在现实世界里\NIn the real world.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.18,0:09:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个"我是单身也不需要给孩子喂奶"的世界\NWhere I'm single and not breastfeeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.51,0:09:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  不如这样\NOkay, how's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.75,0:09:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦亨德森让我坐上那个职位\NOnce Henderson hires me,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.59,0:09:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱就迅速友好地离婚\Nwe'll get a quick- but-amicable divorce.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.14,0:09:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你得有值得我想分掉一半的东西\NIf only you had anything I wanted half of.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.47,0:09:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想让艾玛有个引以为荣的爸爸\NI just want Emma to have a father she can be proud of.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.39,0:09:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  你一定要帮我\NPlease, you have to help me...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.38,0:09:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"莱丽·维勒"\N"Riley Wheeler."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.17,0:09:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这名字我倒是每天会在我的笔记本里写一遍\NI only wrote that in my notebook every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.21,0:09:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在杜撰咱们的背景故事\NI'm just working on our backstory.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.03,0:09:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是答应咯\NSo you'll do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.28,0:09:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\NOh, hell no!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.26,0:09:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西要退回去\NThis is going back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.45,0:09:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  愤怒的金发女郎带着孩子路过\NAngry blonde with a baby coming through, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.32,0:09:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让让  快点  让让\NMove it. Come on. Move it, move it, move it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.87,0:09:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\NOh, hell no.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.48,0:09:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把它退回去\NThis is going back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.19,0:09:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我可喜欢当人家叔叔了\NYeah, I just love being an uncle.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.09,0:09:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然准确说来  我更像是一个朋友\NAlthough technically I'm more of a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.35,0:09:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我可称得上是个"友叔"了\NI guess that makes me a frunkle.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.53,0:10:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  友叔  把你手机给我下\NOkay, frunkle. Let's see that phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.85,0:10:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NAll right.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.66,0:10:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-打给我哦  -好的\N- Call me. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.07,0:10:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺厉害的嘛\NImpressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.81,0:10:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似你越来越上手了嘛\NYou seem to be getting the hang of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.86,0:10:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有兴趣咱们来个小比赛\NYou up for a little challenge?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.32,0:10:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说  -咱们每人逛一个街区\N- I'm listening. - We each take a block.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.65,0:10:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要到的电话号码最多\NWhoever lands the most numbers,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.97,0:10:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,余下时间这辆婴儿车就归谁所有\Ngets the stroller the whole rest of the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.72,0:10:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏开始  不过我得给你提个醒\NGame on. But I gotta warn you--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.52,0:10:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔我正当红呢\NTucker's in the zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.46,0:10:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你的提醒  友叔\NThanks for the heads-up, frunkle.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  酸奶店和美甲沙龙是你的地盘了\NWait wait wait. You get the yogurt shop and the nail salon?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.29,0:10:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天怎么这么热呢\NWoo! Is it ever hot out today!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.17,0:10:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  这不公平\NHey! Hey, man! That is not fair!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.53,0:10:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟你再商量下\NHey! I wanna re-negotiate!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.64,0:10:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在高中相识\NOkay, so we met in high school,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.24,0:10:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直疯狂暗恋我\Nyou had a crazy crush on me,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.39,0:10:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你因为体重问题而不敢向我表白\Nbut were too shy because of your weight problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.12,0:10:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我以前不胖啊  你才是胖的那个\NWait, I wasn't fat. You were.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.10,0:10:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我帮忙就照我说的来  我以前不胖\NNot if you want my help, I wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.01,0:10:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们打了个平手\NWe tied!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.02,0:10:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  虽然其中有两个号码是靠哭拿到的\NWell, I had to cry for two of the numbers.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.23,0:10:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但毕竟是个平手\NBut we tied.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.74,0:11:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你们推婴儿车出去了吗\NWait. You took out the stroller?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.04,0:11:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分钟前老妈才把艾玛送过来\NMom just put Emma down 10 minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.87,0:11:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来有没有宝宝都不要紧\NTurns out the baby part is optional.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.42,0:11:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要说她在睡觉\NYou just say she's asleep
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.83,0:11:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没人会朝里面看\Nand nobody looks inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.11,0:11:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但是老妈还在这里呢\NOkay, but Mom's still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.97,0:11:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-此刻  -又来了\N- Now. - Again?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.86,0:11:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快走  -老天\N- Go! - Oh my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.43,0:11:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚是塔克尔吗\NIs that Tucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.44,0:11:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他往那边跑了\NHe went that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.10,0:11:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道哪部分更有趣了\NI don't know which is more fun,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.41,0:11:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老妈对塔克尔穷追猛打呢\Nsiccing Mom on Tuck,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.86,0:11:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是推着婴儿车闲逛\Nor cruising around with that stroller.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.20,0:11:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  有时间你也可以试试\NBen, you gotta get in on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.63,0:11:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没空呢  我现在可是有老婆的人了\NCan't. I have a wife now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.94,0:11:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也没出去多久吧\NHow long were we gone?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.71,0:11:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们通过假扮夫妻\NWe are pretending to be married
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.52,0:11:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来让他获得升职机会\Nso that he can get a promotion.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.56,0:11:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒给我提了个醒\NOh, which reminds me,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.56,0:11:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在回家的路上捡到了这样东西\NI picked this up on my way home.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.34,0:11:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽\NRiley,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.81,0:11:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意嫁我为妻吗\Nwill you do me the honor of being my wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.13,0:11:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  是的\NSure. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.93,0:11:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意\NI do.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.10,0:11:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  你确定这是个好主意吗\NRiley, are you sure this is a good idea?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.84,0:11:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好着呢\NI'm fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.57,0:12:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是何时意识到爱上了我\NSo when did you first know you were in love with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.52,0:12:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们嘿咻之后\NAfter we had sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.86,0:12:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你得详细描述下\NCome on! You have to paint a picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.67,0:12:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要浪漫点的  比如说\NIt has to be something romantic, like--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.77,0:12:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大一时的春假\Nspring break, freshman year.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.59,0:12:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在水库沿岸\NDown by the reservoir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.31,0:12:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天你穿着一条蓝色的连衣裙\NYou were wearing a blue dress.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.87,0:12:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕阳西下  你身上泛着光晕\NAnd the sun was setting so it made it look like you had a halo.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.66,0:12:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就像他说的那样  但没那么肉麻\NExactly. Something like that, but not so sappy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.07,0:12:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天的日落美极了\NAnd the sunsets were incredible.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.21,0:12:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以至于我们都没出门\NNot that we ever left the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.27,0:12:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒  这真是一次有意义的会面\NWell, Wheeler this has been an excellent meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.25,0:12:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想我可以负责任地说  -你好\N- I think I can safely say-- - Hi there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.34,0:12:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不是  -绝对不是\N- Hey, didn't you-- - A-absolutely not!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.10,0:12:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  这位小姐\NSorry, miss, but we're
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.14,0:12:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正在开一个商务会议\Nkind of in the middle of a business meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.20,0:12:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么冲嘛  维勒  这是我女儿佐伊\NTake it down a notch, Wheeler. This is my daughter Zoe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.59,0:12:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你女儿\NYour daughter?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.55,0:12:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见到你很高兴\NWell, uh, so nice to meet you for the first time ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.94,0:12:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很高兴认识你\NNice to meet you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.28,0:12:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伊  这是本和他的娇妻莱丽\NZoe, this is Ben and his lovely wife Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.37,0:12:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真应该好好认识下\NYou should really get to know each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.99,0:13:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那真是  -太不合时宜了\N- Oh, that would be-- - Impossible!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.61,0:13:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是正打算出去一趟么  亲爱的\N'Cause we're about to head out, right, babe?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.98,0:13:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别急着走啊  能和你还有你的妻子\NOh, don't leave now. There's nothing I'd like more than
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.01,0:13:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是太高兴了\Nto chat with you and your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.90,0:13:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我得先去补个妆\NAs soon as I freshen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.94,0:13:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那杯冰茶都被谁喝了呀\NWow, where'd all that iced tea go?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.30,0:13:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来都被我喝了  去去就来\NOops! There it is. I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.63,0:13:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好参加复赛了吗\NReady for a rematch?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.37,0:13:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去吧  我就算了\NYou go. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.93,0:13:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有想过只要一个人的号码吗\NYou ever think you want just one phone number?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.02,0:13:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好汉不提当年勇啊\NBeen there, done that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.65,0:13:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间我都是批量采购呢\NThese days I'm shopping in bulk.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.15,0:13:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说那个特别的她的号码\NI'm talking about one special number.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.39,0:13:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个足以让你删了其他所有人的号码\NThe kind that makes you want to delete all the other ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.58,0:13:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.34,0:13:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在说莱丽吗\NIs this about Riley?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.99,0:13:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个你发誓永远不会喜欢的人\NWho you swear you don't like?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.84,0:13:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是  我就是随口一说\NNo. I'm just saying,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.70,0:13:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让所有女生都喜欢你容易\Ngetting lots of women to like you is easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.57,0:13:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想得一心上人难呐  我该怎么办\NIt's getting one that's hard. How do I do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.08,0:13:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  假设有个女孩儿\NOkay, so assuming there is a special girl
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.60,0:13:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的名字不是以"莱"开头也不是以"丽"结尾\Nwhose name doesn't start with "R" And end with "Iley"...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.78,0:13:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在向我咨询如何追到她吗\NAre you asking my advice on how to get her?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.87,0:13:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  你不是把妹磁铁么\NYeah. You're the relationship magnet, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.80,0:13:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就磁化我吧\NMagnetize me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.55,0:14:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  听着  要是你真想和她开始的话\NFine. Look, if you really want a relationship,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.45,0:14:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告诉她你的感受\Nyou gotta tell her how you feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.86,0:14:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定她也喜欢着你呢\NI mean maybe she's into you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.63,0:14:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就甜蜜了  随时随地都想见到她\NThen it's all sweet, can't wait to see her,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.44,0:14:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短信传情\Nsend each other fun little texts,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.78,0:14:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒适地待在一起\Nget comfortable together,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.74,0:14:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能也会有点无聊\Nmaybe even a little bored.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.03,0:14:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到有天你意识到你们之间已经没有爱了\NUntil one day you realize it's not even love any more,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.38,0:14:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却依然跳着令你们两半俱伤的痛苦之舞\Nbut a horrible dance of pain that will leave you both
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.15,0:14:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着时光的流逝你们最终变成两具空壳\Ndamaged, empty shells for years to come!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.04,0:14:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来也不错\NThat sounds nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.39,0:14:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这事很瞎  但我真的没有劈腿\NI know this looks horrible, but I'm not a cheater.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.51,0:14:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是假装已婚\NI'm just faking being
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.58,0:14:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让你爸爸把那份工作交给我\Nmarried so your dad will consider me for a job.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.45,0:14:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是个骗子咯\NSo you're a liar?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.33,0:14:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更愿意你称我为有创意的上进青年\NI'd probably go with creative go-getter.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.26,0:14:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心\NNo worries.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.21,0:14:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整蛊我老爸是我最喜欢的消遣方式\NScamming my dad is my favorite pastime.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.66,0:14:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你会守口如瓶咯\NSo you won't say anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.27,0:14:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个字都不提\NNot a word.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.84,0:14:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不你让我看下你的"简历"\NSo how about you show me your resume?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.50,0:14:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的简历可不在这里\NThat's not where I keep it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.12,0:14:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是吧  -莱丽  不是你看到的这样\N- Seriously? - Riley, it's not what it looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.04,0:14:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  因为看起来就像是你甩了我\NReally? Because it looks like you abandoned me
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.04,0:14:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和某个陌生女人在舌吻呢\Nto shove your tongue down some stranger's throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.82,0:14:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事  是她要跟我舌吻呢\NWrong! She was shoving her tongue down my throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.03,0:15:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还想拒绝来着\NI was trying to push it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.65,0:15:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本·维勒  我恨你\NBen Wheeler, I hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.47,0:15:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  维勒  是时候了\NOkay Wheeler, it's go time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.67,0:15:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着告诉她你的真实想法\NTake your best shot and tell her how you feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.65,0:15:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何你都不要回头\NNo matter what you can't turn back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.62,0:15:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NDanny?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.97,0:15:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里干嘛\NWhat are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.30,0:15:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能借用下你家的洗手间吗\NCan I use your bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.77,0:15:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弟弟真是个混球\NYour brother is such a jerk.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.32,0:15:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你再看到我主动提出帮他的话\NIf you ever see me offering to help him again,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.26,0:15:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应我  你一定要阻止我\Nyou have to promise to stop me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.68,0:15:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我保证会  -把这个弄下来\N- I promise. - Take this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.95,0:15:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  我真不敢相信本会和我假扮情侣\NGod, I can't believe Ben would just take our fake relationship
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.21,0:15:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却完全不把它当一回事\Nand throw it all away.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.98,0:15:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你该谈场真正的恋爱了\NWell, maybe it's time for a real relationship.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.93,0:15:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一个对的人\NYou know, with a real guy who's--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.85,0:15:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是个大混球\NNot a gigantic tool.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.61,0:15:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你走吧  本  -对不起\N- Go away, Ben. - I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.22,0:15:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女生是几天前我推婴儿车搭讪时认识的\NThat girl-- I hit on her a couple days ago with the stroller.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.84,0:15:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪知道她竟是我老板的女儿呀\NDid not know she was my boss's daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.47,0:15:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了之后  我就追去跟她说\NWhen she came, and I went after her to be like,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.80,0:15:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"别告诉你老爸"\N"Hey, don't tell your dad."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.76,0:15:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后她发神经就开始吻我\NThen she went all psycho and started kissing me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.71,0:15:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不会那样做了\NI would never do something like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.10,0:15:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  帮我说句话呀\NDanny, back me up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.95,0:15:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你说得挺好嘛\NOh, I think you're doing great.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.75,0:15:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在根本不在乎那个职位了\NI don't even care about the job any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.25,0:16:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唯一在意的只有你\NAll I care about is you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.98,0:16:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着说\NI'm listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.51,0:16:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯帮我  真是太好了\NYou were so sweet to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.20,0:16:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续说\NKeep going.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.28,0:16:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算告诉亨德森\NWell, I'm gonna tell Henderson
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.29,0:16:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对你的看法是对的  却看错了我\Nthat he was right about you and wrong about me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.14,0:16:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样你就别想升职了\NYou're never gonna get that promotion.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.75,0:16:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但是至少我能赢回你的心\NNo, but maybe I'll get you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.97,0:16:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宁愿要个真朋友也不要个假老婆\NI'll take a real friend over fake wife any day.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.27,0:16:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我们可以再回去\NOr... we could go back in there one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.65,0:16:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.40,0:16:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我就该阻止你了\NThis is the part where I'm supposed to stop you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.27,0:16:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  坚强点儿\NRiley, stay strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.88,0:16:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然戏都演到这一步了\NI mean we already made it this far.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.72,0:16:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你至少也要得到那份工作\NAt least if you get the job,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.02,0:16:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不枉费我这么多时间\NI won't feel like I totally wasted my time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.88,0:16:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亨德森今晚会来酒吧喝点东西\NWell, Henderson does want to have drinks tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.33,0:16:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但这是最后一次\NOkay, but this is the last time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.23,0:16:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  把戒指还给我\NAll right, I need my ring back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.09,0:16:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  莱丽\NThank you, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.35,0:16:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请你喝咖啡  咱们接着杜撰我们的情史\NI'll buy you coffee and we can work on our story.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.38,0:16:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那段你虽然是个傻蛋  我还是嫁给了你的情史吗\NThe one where you're a dork, but I marry you anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.42,0:16:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  松手  谢谢\NAll right-- hand. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.08,0:17:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有空吗\NWhat's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.12,0:17:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塔克尔  -维勒太太\N- Tucker? - Mrs. Wheeler?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.17,0:17:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\NOh, hell no!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.82,0:17:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了  完了\NOh no no no!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.79,0:17:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是吧  -停下\N- Oh yeah? - Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.87,0:17:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还想跑\NYou gonna run from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.22,0:17:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你跑得真快  -这回你可跑不了了\N- You're so fast! - You're gonna run from me?!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.81,0:17:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然我已经征服了纽约了\NSo now that I've conquered New York,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.35,0:17:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我要让亨德森这个牌子享誉全国\NI'm taking the Henderson brand national--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.95,0:17:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芝加哥  亚特兰大\NChicago, Atlanta,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.59,0:17:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一站是迈阿密  你准备好了吗  维勒\Nfirst stop Miami. You ready for that, Wheeler?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.27,0:17:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你这是要请我了吗\NWait, are you offering me the job?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.88,0:17:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没最终定下来  要不你先和莱丽\NNothing's final, but why don't you and Riles
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.93,0:17:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞去那边过个周末实地考察下\Nfly down for the weekend and check it out?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.63,0:17:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定很有意思\NIt'll be fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.83,0:17:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个周末\NUh, this-- this weekend?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.64,0:17:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得去不了迈阿密了\NYou know what? I don't think I can make it down to Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.30,0:17:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗\NAre you sure about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.73,0:17:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们可都知道你有多喜欢酒店的房间哦\NWe all know how much you like hotel rooms.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.58,0:17:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来恭敬不如从命啊  你说呢  亲爱的\NSounds like an offer we can't refuse, huh, babe?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.88,0:17:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽\NRiley?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.32,0:17:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道现在不是跟你说这个的最佳时机\NI know this might not be the best time to tell you this,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.87,0:17:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要听好了  因为我不说不行\Nbut you need to hear it and I need to say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.60,0:18:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱上你了  我觉得咱俩应该在一起\NI'm in love with you and I think we should be together.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.08,0:18:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说句话呗\NPlease say something.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.22,0:18:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来事情终究还是败露了\NWell, I guess the cat's outta the bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.68,0:18:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我很抱歉这样对你\NBen, I am so sorry to do this to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.39,0:18:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我和你哥哥相爱了\Nbut your brother and I are in love.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.32,0:18:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的吗  -不是吧\N- We are? - You are?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.69,0:18:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我料想今年的感恩节会过得很尴尬\NI realize that Thanksgiving might be a little awkward this year,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.00,0:18:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我希望你慢慢能接受这个事实\Nbut I'm hoping that in time you'll come to accept it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.73,0:18:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对应该把这份工作交给本\NYou should really hire Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.90,0:18:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定不会让你失望的\NThe kid could use some good news.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.97,0:18:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  咱们走  亲爱的  -等等\N- All right, let's go, babe. - Wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.50,0:18:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我和我第一任妻子的经历真是如出一辙呢\NSame thing happened with me and my first wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.77,0:18:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过当时是我和她妹妹走了出去\NOnly it was me walking out the door with her sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.75,0:18:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莱丽  -你真聪明\N- Riley? - You were brilliant!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.79,0:18:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我爱上你了"\N"I'm in love with you"?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.79,0:18:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你打冰球没混出个样的话\NIf this whole hockey thing doesn't work out,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.35,0:18:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对要去当个演员\Nyou should totally be an actor.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.57,0:18:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓有那么一瞬间我还真相信了\NBecause I swear for like two seconds I actually believed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.00,0:18:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莱丽  -你肯当我的救兵真是太好了\N- Riley-- - You are so sweet to come to my rescue.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.38,0:18:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答应过我你会阻止我  你也做到了\NYou promised you would stop me and you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.45,0:18:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.32,0:18:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在终于知道\NWell, guess that finally answers the question
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.13,0:18:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫁给本是什么感觉了\Nof what it's like to be married to Ben, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.32,0:19:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是杰克  那个真正对我有意思的人\NJack-- a guy who's actually interested in me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.08,0:19:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我应该和他试试\NMaybe I'll see what that's like
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.52,0:19:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和我一起去么  我请客\Ndo you wanna come with? Drinks are on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.22,0:19:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不去了\NNo, I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.09,0:19:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  谢谢\NOkay. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.65,0:19:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天  我真应该好好选个时机了\NMan, I gotta work on my go time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.76,0:19:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去哪里了\NWhere have you guys been?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说\NTell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.44,0:19:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  本  刚才的事真是说了你都不信\NFine. Ben, you are never gonna believe what just happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.30,0:19:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -我\N- All right! - I--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.74,0:19:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我们应该把这个婴儿车退了\NBen, we need to return the stroller.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.59,0:19:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们太幼稚太自私了\NWe're being immature and selfish
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.49,0:19:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没顾及到艾玛的感受\Nand Emma deserves better.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.20,0:19:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我能回房间了吗\NCan I go to my room now?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.20,0:19:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住  死也不能说\NAnd remember-- to your grave.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.38,0:20:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  爸爸今天可想你了\NHey, Emma, Daddy really missed you today.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.82,0:20:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切还顺利吗\NIs everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.54,0:20:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得到那份工作了\NI got the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.85,0:20:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小本啊\NOh, Benji!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.86,0:20:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你能行的\NI just knew you could do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.04,0:20:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我拒绝了\NI turned it down.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.23,0:20:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发什么神经\NWhat is the matter with you?!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.60,0:20:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我胜任不了  出差太频繁了\NI couldn't do it. It's too much travel.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.47,0:20:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我都不能亲眼看到她的成长\NAnd what's the point of giving Emma everything,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.15,0:20:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我为她做的这一切又有什么意义呢\Nif I'm not even here to see her enjoy it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.81,0:20:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作还可以再找  但你只有一个\NThere will be other jobs, but there's only one you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.78,0:20:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点咱们都知道\NThat we know of.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.49,0:20:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我觉得你做了正确决定\NBut I think you made the right decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.90,0:20:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.00,0:20:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个\NSo...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.36,0:20:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和塔克尔之间有啥秘密呢\NWhat's the big secret between you and Tucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.27,0:20:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐在外面喝咖啡\NI was sitting outside having coffee
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.13,0:20:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后塔克尔过来  -事实才不是那样呢\N- and then Tucker comes up-- - That is not what happened!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.20,0:20:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是那样的  -你没有吗\N- No no, huh-uh. - Oh, you didn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.32,0:20:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没说"有空吗"\NYou didn't go "What's up"?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.38,0:20:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我没有\NNo, I did not!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我说了"有空吗"\NOkay, I said, "What's up?"
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.72,0:20:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  艾玛\NThat's right, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.82,0:20:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶奶要把咱家小公主的专属坐驾拿回来\NGrandma is gonna get her princess her special carriage back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.63,0:20:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婴儿车不错\NNice stroller.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.54,0:20:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  猛男\NHello...
