[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.27,0:00:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停  遥控器给我\NStop. Gimme that!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.43,0:00:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  别跟我大呼小叫的\NI've got it. Quit yapping at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.71,0:00:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他好点  丹尼  至少给他个梯凳用吧\NPlay nice, Danny. Or at least give him a step ladder.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.82,0:00:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家听着  我需要件干净的衬衫和一个干净的宝宝\NOkay, people. I need a clean shirt and a clean baby,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.42,0:00:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺序当然无所谓啦\Nnot necessarily in that order.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.14,0:00:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  准备好你的第一个玩耍约会了吗\NEmma, you ready for your first playdate?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.19,0:00:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  艾玛  你要记住我们说的\NOkay now. Remember, Emma, what we talked about.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.60,0:00:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是他给你买吃的\NJust because he buys you formula
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.22,0:00:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就得把玩具分给他玩儿\Ndoesn't mean you need to share your toys.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.92,0:00:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上她被她的新朋友\NShe's actually pretty smitten
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.91,0:00:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小乔丹迷得神魂颠倒呢\Nwith her new little friend Jordan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.11,0:00:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还和自己的大拇指有一腿呢\NWell, she's also having an affair with her thumb,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.12,0:00:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不用急着去买瓷器了\Nso I wouldn't be picking out china just yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.14,0:00:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你真可爱啊\NHoney, I think it's so cute that you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.75,0:00:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然去参加"我和妈咪"课程\Njoined a Mommy and Me class.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.67,0:00:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一屋子的辣妈\NRoom full of hot mommies?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.12,0:00:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  他真无私\NYeah, he's selfless.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.91,0:00:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是为了艾玛好吗\NThis is about Emma, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.92,0:00:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔丹的妈妈伊莎贝尔真的特别棒\NJordan's mom Isabelle is amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.29,0:00:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都叫她"妈咪专家"\NPeople actually call her the "Mommy whisperer."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.25,0:00:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思  那曾是你父亲的绰号\NFunny. That used to be your father's nickname.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.58,0:00:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个计划都是她负责的\NShe runs the whole program.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.09,0:00:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有好多人排队等着上她的课\NThere's a huge waiting list for her class.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.71,0:01:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  散发了一点维勒式魅力之后\NBut, using a little of the patented Wheeler charm,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.06,0:01:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就和艾玛挤到了队伍前面\NEmma and I have jumped to the front of the list.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.09,0:01:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今天通过玩耍约会面试之后就可以上课了\NWe pass our playdate audition today, and we're in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.70,0:01:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了  耶\NWe're in! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.07,0:01:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-终于赢了  -耶\N- Finally! - Whoo! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.73,0:01:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天将是充满呐喊\NToday is gonna be all about yelling,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.96,0:01:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脏话和拳打脚踢的日子\Nswearing and full-on body blows.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.63,0:01:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着像我的新婚之夜\NSounds like my wedding night.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.50,0:01:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说的是拳击  一个收费的叫做\NBoxing. It's the pay-per-view Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.34,0:01:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-《最棒拳击》的节目  -对\N- of the Decade. - Yup.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.42,0:01:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这场比赛就是我们保持男人的方法\NAnd watching it is how we stay manly.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.74,0:01:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  应该会起作用哦\NYeah, okay, that should do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.67,0:01:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  没事的  艾玛  我们捡起来\NOh! It's okay, Emma. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.73,0:01:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没到三秒呢\NThree-second rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.74,0:01:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  那都已经脏了\NNo! No-second rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.89,0:01:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹说那是假的\NIzzy said that's a myth.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.10,0:01:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道\NDo you have any idea
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.81,0:01:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让她暴露在什么细菌中\Nwhat kind of germ you're exposing her to?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.22,0:01:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我把你们拉扯大的时候\NHoney, when I was raising you boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.64,0:01:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉地上三天吃了都没事儿呢\Nit was a three-day rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.89,0:01:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你吃了没事  那就是安全的\NIf you kept it down, it was safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.16,0:01:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有事...我们当时养的狗就派上用场了\NIf you didn't-- well, that's why we had a dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.68,0:01:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹有一个简化版的父母须知清单\NWell, Izzy has this simple list of rules
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.88,0:01:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个为人父母的都要遵守\Nthat every parent needs to follow.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.31,0:01:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很震惊自己居然好多都不知道\NIt's amazing how much I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.95,0:01:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都很震惊  亲爱的\NWe're all amazed at that, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.24,0:01:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也整个了清单\NAnd I've got a list too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.38,0:01:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薯条  啤酒  沙司  鳄梨色拉酱\NChips, beer, salsa, guacamole,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.67,0:02:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要8点之前回家\Nand you be home by 8:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.95,0:02:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  我一定会的\NPlease. I'm so on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.74,0:02:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的晚了\NAnd I'm so late.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.80,0:02:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹列表第一条\NThe first thing on Izzy's list:
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.43,0:02:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为一切做好准备\NBe prepared for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.68,0:02:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,列表第二条\NThe second thing on the list:
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.79,0:02:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了宝宝\NDon't forget the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.42,0:02:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边 惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.71,0:02:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲 雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.78,0:02:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能今天不适合去公园\NSo maybe not the best day for the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.76,0:02:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你需要擦干的话...  -我们没事\N- If you need to dry off-- - We're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.52,0:02:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管刮风下雨烈日高照  我们有备无患\NRain or shine, we're always prepared.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.58,0:02:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们先自便  我们去回收雨衣\NMake yourself comfortable, while we recycle our raincoats.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.97,0:02:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里闻着很...\NIt smells very...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.43,0:02:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有男人味\Nmale.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.89,0:02:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我代表住在这里的三个男人\NOn behalf of the three men who live here,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.09,0:02:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\Nthank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.25,0:02:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是第一次\NLook, we're sorta new
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.39,0:02:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加这种宝宝约会活动\Non the whole baby-dating scene,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.91,0:02:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不知道下面要怎么做\Nso I'm not really sure what comes next.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.66,0:02:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲躲猫猫\NA little peek-a-boo.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.25,0:02:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转转奶瓶\NMaybe some spin-the-bottle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.07,0:02:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还挺好玩儿的\NThat's hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.17,0:03:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是快到乔丹的小睡时间了\NBut it's almost time for Jordan's nap
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.67,0:03:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里却找不到地方把他放下\Nand I can't imagine putting him down anywhere here,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.48,0:03:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们可能...\Nso we should...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.67,0:03:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该走了\Nprobably be going.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.54,0:03:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  别  别走\NNo no no no. Please don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.92,0:03:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们这里可能达不到你通常的标准\NI know we're probably not up to your usual standards.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.51,0:03:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里确实也需要略微加一点...\NAnd the place could use a touch more...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.10,0:03:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-保护婴儿的措施  -略微吗\N- Baby-proofing. - "A touch?"
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.70,0:03:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看那个巨型飞镖靶\NShe says, looking at a giant dartboard
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.32,0:03:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和各种有窒息危险的东西吧\Nand 75 choking hazards.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.30,0:03:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我很抱歉  我不知道\NBen, I'm sorry. I just don't know
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.93,0:03:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是认真对待父亲这个角色\Nif you're taking your role as a parent seriously enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.97,0:03:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是为什么我们需要上你的课啊\NAnd that's why we need to be in your class.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.09,0:03:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们厌倦了悲哀的从前\NWe're tired of being pathetic "Befores."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.99,0:03:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想享受美好的明天\NWe wanna be happy "Afters."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.75,0:03:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要跟伊兹学习\NWe need to be Izzied.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.24,0:03:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶  伊兹\NYay, Izzy!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.78,0:03:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我可以做一次上门私人集训\NI guess I could do a private home intensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.40,0:03:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一对一的来把这里所有的东西都检查一遍\NA one-on-one where we go through everything in the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.65,0:03:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  谢谢你\NYes! Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.24,0:04:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也可以边吃晚餐边做\NMaybe we could do it over dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.19,0:04:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈今晚会照顾乔丹\NMy mom's got Jordan tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.47,0:04:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说他可能会在两岁之前\Nwhich just means he'll probably know
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.33,0:04:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就知道怎么做马提尼了\Nhow to mix a Martini before he's two.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.78,0:04:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚  就在今晚吗\NTonight? As in this evening?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.92,0:04:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始\NHours from now?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.90,0:04:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的只有这时候有时间\NIt's really the only time I have.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.46,0:04:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的这种情形  你们俩\NAnd there's no way that I could let
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.68,0:04:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是没机会去上我的课的\Nthe two of you into my class.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.87,0:04:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就今晚\NThen tonight it is!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.84,0:04:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我要提前跟你说\NBut I'm just letting you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.00,0:04:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我学东西真的很快\NI'm a really fast learner,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.48,0:04:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好迎接我们父女的敲锣打鼓吧\Nso get ready to put the baby pedal to the daddy metal.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道我在说什么\NI have no idea what that means.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.23,0:04:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的本  你这是保护过度了\NBen, honey, there is such a thing as being too protective.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.64,0:04:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哭的时候我每次都把你抱起来吗  没有\NDid I pick you up every time you cried? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.25,0:04:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你饿的时候我每次都喂你吗  没有\NDid I feed you every time you were hungry? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.41,0:04:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我修过电视机后面的\NDid I fix those frayed wires
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.98,0:04:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,磨损电线吗  开什么玩笑  我又不是电工\Nbehind the TV? I mean, what am I? An electrician?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.96,0:04:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看  本  你这不是...\NCome on, Ben, you turned out--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.38,0:04:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依然健在吗\Nwell, you are still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.13,0:04:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实在是太娇生惯养了\NI feel so coddled.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.37,0:04:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是  现在都是我在\NWell, you should, since I'm making dinner
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.90,0:04:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你和你的小情人做饭\Nfor you and lady goo-goo.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.89,0:04:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那是有机鸡肉对吗\NHey, that's organic chicken, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.27,0:05:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只吃有机食品\NShe only eats organic.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.60,0:05:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  为此我还要花\NYeah, right. Like I'm going to spend
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.09,0:05:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四十块去买一个鸡胸脯肉\N40 bucks on a breast of chicken.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.82,0:05:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我胸罩一个罩杯算下来还不值那么多呢\NI don't spend that much per cup on a bra.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.31,0:05:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈  这很重要好吗\NMom! This is important.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.32,0:05:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你哥哥长到一米九五\NHoney, your brother is 6'5"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.15,0:05:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是"含垢忍辱"长的\Nand he grew up eating dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.57,0:05:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我成功了\NI did it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.71,0:05:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作到手了\NI got the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.01,0:05:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在站在你们面前的\NYou are looking at the newest employee
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.17,0:05:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是本德  鲍曼  布罗克曼\Nof Bender, Bowman, Brockman
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.36,0:05:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及一些名字我都不会念的人的新员工\Nand some guy whose name I can't pronounce.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.06,0:05:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-恭喜你  -谢谢\N- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.67,0:05:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个脱衣舞俱乐部的名字可真够长的\NWow. That's a really long name for a strip club.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.10,0:05:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一家律师事务所\NIt's a law firm
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.18,0:05:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我周一就可以开始实习了\Nand I start my internship on Monday.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.92,0:05:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你最好还是找到你裙子的另一部分吧\NWell, then you better find the rest of that skirt
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.59,0:05:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我都快看见你的小内内了\Nbefore then because I can kinda see your tonsils.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.23,0:05:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是我所有裙子中最保守的了\NThis is the most conservative thing I have.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.55,0:05:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和艾玛要去品牌特价商场了\NWell, Emma and I are heading to the Outlet Mall
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.71,0:05:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是每月疯狂大减价时期\Nfor their monthly madness sale.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.13,0:05:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打完六折之后再打六折\NIt's 40% off of 40% off.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.67,0:05:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这跟倒贴钱给我们差不多了\NWhich I think means, they pay you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.46,0:05:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实需要买几件新套装了\NWell, I actually could use a couple of new suits.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.34,0:05:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要做让自己后悔的事了\NHere's something I'm gonna regret.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.22,0:06:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒夫人  你能带我一起去购物吗\NMrs. Wheeler, will you take me shopping?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.58,0:06:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我总得找人帮我\NAbsolutely. I can always use
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.51,0:06:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挡住那些乱喷香水的女人\Nsomebody to block those perfume ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.64,0:06:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些泼妇真的很厉害\NThose bitches are tough.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.74,0:06:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该在战斗打响之前就准备上路了\NBut we should probably get going before the fight starts.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.92,0:06:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  对了\NOh, that's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.95,0:06:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点忘了今晚的拳击好戏了\NI forgot the fight of the decade is tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.66,0:06:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我指的是他们发现\NNo. I mean the one Ben's gonna be getting into
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.43,0:06:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本为了迪兹而抛弃他们之后\Nwith the boys when they find out
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.08,0:06:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会陷入的那场混战\Nthat he's ditching them for Dizzy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.58,0:06:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他叫伊兹  -随便\N- Izzy. - Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.62,0:06:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  这都是为了艾玛  他们会理解的\NHey, it's for Emma. They'll understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.00,0:06:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂啊\NI don't understand!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.33,0:06:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你不知道我们制定了\NDo you not see that we've instituted
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.83,0:06:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"薯片甲不留"政策吗  -对\N- a leave-no-chip-behind policy? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.74,0:06:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能这时候扯后腿啊\NYou cannot pull the plug.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.16,0:06:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要做拿手的五道工序豆瓣酱呢\NI'm making my famous five-layer bean dip.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.23,0:06:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我们要做洋葱酱\NI thought we were doing my onion dip.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.76,0:06:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以尝试点不同的嘛\NWell, maybe we can try something different.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.18,0:06:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你们\NGuys!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.18,0:06:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很抱歉  但是你们\NI'm really sorry, but you'll have to find
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.93,0:06:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得找别的地方看比赛了\Nsomewhere else to watch the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.13,0:06:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都得作出些牺牲\NWe all have to make some sacrifices.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.71,0:06:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚谁在牺牲\NOh, I know exactly who I'm sacrificing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.00,0:06:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我们要在自己家边吃着自己的东西\NYeah, we wanna watch the fight in our home
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.20,0:06:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,边用自己的电视看比赛\Nwith our stuff on our television!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.60,0:06:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我们无法接受你的行为\NYeah, this is unacceptable behavior.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.51,0:07:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们取消你打兄弟牌的权利\NWe are so revoking your bro card.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.76,0:07:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就请你们自觉把剩下的\NWell, feel free to put it in this box
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.11,0:07:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不适合婴儿的垃圾食品放进这个箱子里\Nwith the rest of your non-baby-friendly crap
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.65,0:07:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后扔进仓储笼里\Nand dump it in the storage cage.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.68,0:07:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去忙我的"我和妈咪"大业了\NI've got important Mommy and Me business.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.54,0:07:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他到底知不知道那个理由听起来弱爆了\NDoes he even hear how weak that sounds?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.84,0:07:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当然知道\NYes, he does!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.59,0:07:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你实在是太棒了\NYou were amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.51,0:07:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把衬衣从那个女人手里抢出来的样子帅呆了\NThe way you just ripped that shirt right out of her hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.76,0:07:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不这怎么叫疯狂大减价呢\NThat's why they call it a tag sale.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.60,0:07:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我疯狂的抓住她  然后直接绝杀\NI tagged her right on her ass-- just ka-blam!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.55,0:07:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰一下  女士们\NExcuse me. Ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.36,0:07:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常我会买你们家的\NNormally I would buy cookies
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.05,0:07:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饼干的  先生  但是我刚刚\Nfrom your troop, sir, but I just dropped
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.98,0:07:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经血拼过了...\Na boatload of cash--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.08,0:07:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就不废话了\NLet's cut the chatter.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.76,0:07:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边抓到了偷窃犯人\NI got a 942 in progress.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.92,0:07:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请跟我来\NFollow me, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.02,0:07:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  有什么事吗\NI'm sorry, is there a problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.45,0:07:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  你们被捕了\NYeah. You're under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.07,0:07:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排队跟我走  金发美女们\NLet's fall in line, blondies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.77,0:07:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  我真不敢相信你的仓储笼内\NDude, I can't believe you didn't have enough room
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.86,0:07:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然连几个盒子都装不下\Nin your storage cage for some boxes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.96,0:07:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些东西该扔就扔吧\NYou gotta get rid of some of that crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.61,0:07:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  我也无能为力\NDude, I can't help it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.95,0:08:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些家具都是我祖母的\NAll that furniture belonged to my nana.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.49,0:08:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的初吻就是在那张沙发上献出去的\NAnd I had my first kiss on that couch.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.68,0:08:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在能放下东西\NCould we please just dump these
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.84,0:08:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找个地方看比赛了吗\Nand find a place to watch the fight?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.82,0:08:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.97,0:08:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.37,0:08:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是有线电视接口吗\NIs that a cable outlet?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.19,0:08:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想的和我想的一样吗\NAre you thinking what I'm thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.88,0:08:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.83,0:08:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得找个地方看比赛\NWe need to find a place to watch the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.84,0:08:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  对啊\NOh! Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.74,0:08:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们\NGuys?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.80,0:08:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东西都去哪里了\NWhere is everything?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.69,0:08:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看洗衣房已经够我们用了\NI believe the laundry room is officially back in order.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.59,0:08:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁还需要本啊\NWho needs Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.06,0:08:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是  谁需要啤酒  来吧\NMore importantly, who needs beer? Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.20,0:08:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有人需要\NThis guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.14,0:09:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  煮面的开水  搞定\NOkay, water boiled for pasta-- check.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.79,0:09:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假装是我自己做的袋装沙拉  搞定\NSalad in a bag I'll pretend I made myself-- check.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.88,0:09:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衬衣上的男人味  也搞定啦\NSweating through my nice shirt-- double check.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.96,0:09:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在要干什么\NOkay, now what?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.95,0:09:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把鸡肉切成一口大小的块状  对\NCut the chicken into bite-sized pieces. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.05,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去哪里了\NWhere have you guys been?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.19,0:09:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都找你们找了一个多小时了\NI've been calling you for over an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.42,0:09:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人之家没有手机信号\NNo reception in the man cave.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.27,0:09:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里  无所谓了\NThe where? It doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.02,0:09:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们的配合\NThank you for getting on board with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.56,0:09:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说要拿洋葱和豆子\NI say onion and bean.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.08,0:09:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我爱死你了\NI say I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.92,0:09:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹一走我就给你们发短信\NI'll text you as soon as Izzy's gone
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.46,0:09:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你们就把电视机和兄弟牌都请回来\Nand you can bring back the TV and my bro card.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.55,0:09:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  你可以\NWe're good. Maybe you can catch
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.97,0:09:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去酒吧看比赛\Nthe fight down at the bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.42,0:09:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也是在那里看吗\NOh, is that where you're watching it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.56,0:09:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\NNope.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.12,0:09:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们不要告诉我在哪里吗\NSo you're not gonna tell me where?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.24,0:09:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到要告诉你的理由\NDon't see why we should.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.46,0:09:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来你对比赛不感兴趣\NNot really something you seem interested in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.55,0:09:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要这样吗  能再幼稚一点吗\NReally? Could you be more childish?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.62,0:09:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你们了\NPlease.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.81,0:10:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣房  里面太棒了\NLaundry room. It's so cool!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.38,0:10:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是邀请了本  那"无本俱乐部"\NWhat is the point in having a No-Ben club
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.85,0:10:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么意思\Nwhen you invite Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.40,0:10:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-叮咚  -伊兹  嗨\N- Knock knock. - Izzy, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.49,0:10:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿上这个婴儿监听器\NJust take this baby monitor
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.03,0:10:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么精彩的地方一定跟我说\Nand let me know if anything big happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.79,0:10:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们过来  我的哥哥和室友\NThank you for coming. My brother and my roommate,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.82,0:10:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的有力支持者\Nboth giant supporters.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.21,0:10:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -噢  我刚刚消过毒\N- Hi. - Oh, I actually just sanitized.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.88,0:10:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,享受你们的婴儿安全公寓吧\NEnjoy baby-proofing the apartment,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.55,0:10:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要在楼下享受安全生活了\Nand we'll be downstairs dull-proofing our lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.86,0:10:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  本  真是太棒了\NWow. Ben, I am so impressed.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.40,0:10:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好话不用说第二遍哦\NDo not need to tell me anything twice.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.11,0:10:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不用多废时间了\NThen this should take no time at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.77,0:10:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就直接进入\NAnd we'll be able to get to the
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.30,0:10:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚的一对一部分吧\None-on-one portion of the evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.84,0:10:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不是...\NIsn't that what we--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.62,0:10:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢   没有意识到爸爸也有玩耍约会\NOh. Didn't realize daddy had a playdate.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.38,0:10:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是总部的汤姆·曼  完毕\NThis is the Tom Man at home base-- over.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.75,0:10:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来21区一趟\NCome in sector 21.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.11,0:10:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是保安处的邦妮\NThis is Bonnie in security.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.36,0:10:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来一趟  大裤衩\NCome in, fatpants.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.87,0:10:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  邦妮\NHey there, Bonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们要做狱友了\NLooks like we're gonna be cellmates.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.74,0:11:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上铺是我的\NI call top bunk!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.26,0:11:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们耍宝大酬宾啊\NGuess there was a two-for-one sale on wisenheimers.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.76,0:11:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位女士是不是过够好日子了\NYou two ladies wanna tamp it down?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.11,0:11:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  不要告诉我妈\NPlease don't call my mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.26,0:11:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会吓坏的\NShe will totally freak out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.38,0:11:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要是关我禁闭  我就去不成舞会了\NAnd if she grounds me, I'm gonna miss prom.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.71,0:11:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得戴维和我可能会...\NAnd I think that David and I might actually...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.66,0:11:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做那玩意呢\Ndo it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.74,0:11:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-闭嘴  -你闭嘴\N- Shut up. - You shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.56,0:11:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩都闭嘴\NThe two of you shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.28,0:11:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要想唱这出  去大街上吧\NYou two should take this act on the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.19,0:11:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你们去不了\NOh! But you can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.50,0:11:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为据我所知\NBecause where I come from,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.77,0:11:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用无辜的小宝宝打掩护\Nusing an innocent little baby to steal
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.85,0:11:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷钻表就是我们所说的重罪\Na diamond watch is what we like to call a felony.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.10,0:11:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是哪儿来的  不是我们放进去的\NWhere did that come from? We didn't put that in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.24,0:11:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟假释官说去吧  姐们\NTell it to your parole officer, sister!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.13,0:11:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  容我离开片刻\NNow, if you'll excuse me,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.70,0:11:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把文件拿过来\NI need to get the proper paperwork.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.84,0:11:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍天啊  重罪吗\NOh my God! A felony?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.36,0:11:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会丢掉实习机会的\NI could lose my internship.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.30,0:11:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的律师资格证没到手就会被吊销\NI could get disbarred before I'm even barred.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.79,0:11:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能这样对我呢\NHow could you do this to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.10,0:11:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当真以为我偷了块表\NOh, you actually think I stole a watch
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.10,0:11:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还塞进了艾玛的手推车里吗\Nand shoved it into Emma's stroller?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.63,0:12:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道呢  你个失心疯\NHow should I know?! You're a crazy person.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.77,0:12:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我真当上了律师\NIf I do become a lawyer,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.09,0:12:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头等大事就是起诉你\Nthe first thing I'm gonna do is sue you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.11,0:12:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇士...  之...  家\NAnd the home... ...of the brave!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.14,0:12:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得本会享受"无聊与我"的约会吗\NYou think Ben's enjoying his "Boring and me" date?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.47,0:12:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得用什么好一点\NWhat do you think is better--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.47,0:12:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婴儿润肤油还是婴儿爽身粉\Nbaby oil or baby powder?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.04,0:12:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,个人最爱润肤油\NOh well, I personally like the oil the best
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.05,0:12:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无暇肌肤立刻拥有\Nbecause it leaves my skin blemish-free
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.12,0:12:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且会遍布\Nand just all over--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.83,0:12:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊  有人被打了\NCome on! Somebody hit somebody!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.01,0:12:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  规矩一\NOkay, rule NO.1:
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.30,0:12:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人洞里不许聊宝宝\Nno baby talk in the man cave.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.50,0:12:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶爸呼叫男人洞\NBaby daddy to man cave,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.65,0:12:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶爸呼叫男人洞  快来  男人洞\Nbaby daddy to man cave. Come in, man cave.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.40,0:12:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这里出事了\NI think we have a situation up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.81,0:12:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一遍\NI repeat--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.59,0:12:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里可能有一起狂野妈咪事故\Nwe may have a mommy-gone-wild situation up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.06,0:12:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是好事啊  对吗\NThat's good, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.18,0:12:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  好不了\NNo, it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.19,0:12:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有可能\NWell, it could be.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.87,0:12:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\NI don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.70,0:12:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我可以享受点小小的额外福利\NI guess I could go for a little extra credit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.28,0:13:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你在外面做什么\NBen, what are you doing out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.92,0:13:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了  等等  比赛怎么样\NI gotta go. Wait-- what's happening with the fight?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.82,0:13:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\NWhat?!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.77,0:13:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\NSorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.79,0:13:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些邻居在看电视\NPart of the neighborhood watch program.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.41,0:13:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到我看了\NIt was my turn to watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.70,0:13:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡肉太美味了\NThis chicken is delicious.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.91,0:13:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  这酒\NAnd the-- oh! This wine--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.75,0:13:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝了这酒\Nit tastes like...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.62,0:13:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由飞翔啊\Nfreedom.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.90,0:13:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能从家里出来简直太棒了\NIt is just so good to get out of the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.63,0:13:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个月只有五个小时的自由时间\NFive hours a month is all I have to myself
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.99,0:13:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每分每秒\Nand I am going to squeeze
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.99,0:13:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都要尽情享受\Nevery last second out of every one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.37,0:13:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  敬自由\NOkay well, here's to freedom.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.98,0:13:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许还敬  尽情享受\NAnd maybe a quick squeeze.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.17,0:13:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这意味着什么吗\NDo you have any idea what this means?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.79,0:13:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在起买零售品要付钱了\NYeah. We're paying retail from now on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.86,0:13:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒太太  你毁了我的人生\NMrs. Wheeler, you have ruined my life!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.07,0:13:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  淡定点\NOkay, let's calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.26,0:13:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能窝里斗\NWe can't turn on each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.83,0:13:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们就盼着呢  -我要举报\N- That's what they want. - Oh-ho, I'll sing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.96,0:13:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要知无不言\NI'll tell them everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.20,0:13:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明摆着嘛  艾玛抓到的\NObviously, Emma just grabbed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.85,0:13:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她正处在乱抓的阶段呢\NShe's at that stage.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.85,0:14:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  听着\NAll right, listen,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.92,0:14:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个聒噪的汤米回来后\Nwhen walkie-talkie Tommy gets back in here,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.92,0:14:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的说服力\Njust use your powers of persuasion
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.65,0:14:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们弄出去\Nand get us out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.30,0:14:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是学过几个法律招式\NWell, I have picked up a few legal moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我指用你没肉的小屁股\NI meant use your skinny little butt
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.42,0:14:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭出减肥中心那一套\Nand shake what weight watchers gave you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.32,0:14:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那叫诱捕\NThat is called entrapment.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.94,0:14:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或称教唆  或是\NOr solicitation, or something...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.94,0:14:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肋间的某物\NIntercoast--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.30,0:14:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的确很擅长嘛\NYou are good at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.98,0:14:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  抱着\NAll right, here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.98,0:14:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我来搞定  好的\NFine, I will do it. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.96,0:14:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  好的\NHuh, yeah, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.14,0:14:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NAh, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.81,0:14:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  这监狱我们是蹲定了\NOh my God, we're so going to prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.87,0:14:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么\NWhat's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.04,0:14:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十块钱和一张咖啡卡\N20 bucks and a coffee card
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.91,0:14:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附带至少五份赠品\Nwith at least five freebies still on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.93,0:14:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喝咖啡\NI don't drink coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.31,0:14:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这叫贿赂\NAnd that's bribery.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.80,0:14:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我说就是嘛\NOh! That's what it was.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.90,0:14:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道妈咪和我最糟糕的部分吗\NYou know the worst part about Mommy and Me?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.89,0:14:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪们\NThe mommies.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.12,0:14:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"伊兹  我该怎么办啊\N"Oh Izzy, what should I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.69,0:14:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹  我的宝贝儿怎么了"\NIzzy, what's wrong with my baby?"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.53,0:15:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会知道呢  那可是个小婴儿\NHow the hell should I know? It's a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.91,0:15:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是你的工作吗\NWell, isn't that kind of your job?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.33,0:15:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人洞呼叫奶爸\NMan cave to baby daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.14,0:15:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音\NWhat's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.32,0:15:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝宝监视器\NOh, it's the baby monitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.77,0:15:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录下了很多神奇的东西\NPicks up a lot of weird stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.54,0:15:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如昨天  我录下了一部电视剧\NLike yesterday, I picked up a telenovela.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.49,0:15:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉蒙纳很生气[剧中人物]\NI don't know what Ramona was saying to Jorge,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.26,0:15:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豪尔赫后果很严重[剧中人物]\Nbut she was pissed.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.58,0:15:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人洞呼叫奶爸\NMan cave to baby daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.68,0:15:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该把他放起来\NI should它just put it away.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.12,0:15:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去梳洗一番\NAnd I am gonna go freshen up
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我还有三个半小时值得尽情挥洒\Nbecause I still have three and a half hours worth of living to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.91,0:15:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请讲  男人洞  什么情况\NCome in, man cave. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.76,0:15:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  发生什么了\NWhat? What just happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.19,0:15:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他倒下了  -天啊\N- Oh! And he's down! - Oh my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.76,0:15:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁倒下了\NWho's down?!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.01,0:15:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹  我马上回来  我得去邻居家借\NIzzy, I'll be right back! I just need run next door to borrow...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.97,0:15:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里没有的东西\NSomething I don't have here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.94,0:15:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去跳舞怎么样\NHey! What do you say we go out dancing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.74,0:15:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.49,0:15:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不不  站起来\NNo no no no, get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.39,0:15:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  站起来\NCome on. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.30,0:15:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错过了什么\NWhat did I miss?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.76,0:16:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被铃声救了一把\NTruly saved by the bell!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.50,0:16:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错过了最精彩的一轮\NYou just missed the most incredible round.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.42,0:16:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  看到的都记着\NOkay well, remember everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.21,0:16:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我还能不能下来了\NI don't know if I can get back down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.47,0:16:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这门怎么了\NWhat's with the door?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.39,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要关上\NDon't close it all the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.70,0:16:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会从外面上锁的\NIt'll lock from the outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.01,0:16:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到男-托邦\NWelcome to Mantopia.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.62,0:16:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  我以为我们定的是兄弟镇\NDude, I thought we settled on Brotown.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.16,0:16:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊  有人吗\NHelp! Anyone...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.92,0:16:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊\NWhat are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.95,0:16:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么出去啊\NHow are we gonna get out of here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.13,0:16:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管  但是你唧唧歪歪的娘娘腔\NI don't care, but your girly whining
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.07,0:16:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扰乱了这里的男人味水平\Nis upsetting the level of manhood in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.52,0:16:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甘愿在这儿度过后半生\NI could spend the rest of my life in this room.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.84,0:16:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没信号了\NUh-oh, cable's out.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.08,0:16:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我们会死在这儿的\NOh my God! We're gonna die in here!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.26,0:16:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他们永远找不着我们\NOh no! They will never find us!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.95,0:16:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能先吃我\NYou cannot eat me first.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.00,0:16:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且根据第189条法规\NAnd according to statute 189
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.34,0:16:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是237条\Nor perhaps 237
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.39,0:16:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本州法律规定\Nof the bylaws of this state,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.92,0:16:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能关闭我们超过四十八小时\Nyou are prohibited from holding us for more than 48 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.27,0:16:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  那么\NOh great, so that's...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.70,0:17:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有四十六小时二十分钟\N46 hours and 20 minutes to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.98,0:17:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有其他安排\NAnd I've got no plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.43,0:17:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很震惊\NWell, color me shocked.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.43,0:17:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把生命献给了这座购物中心\NHey! I have dedicated my life to protecting this mall.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.89,0:17:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我选择了这份工作\NI did not pick this job.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.65,0:17:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是工作选择了我\NThe job picked me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.85,0:17:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么罚款  要么放人\NLook, charge us or let us go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.87,0:17:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  我都得去处理停车超时的事儿了\NEither way, I'm gonna need to get my parking validated.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.46,0:17:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是呼叫警察吧\NI'll just walkie the cops, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.30,0:17:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会逼问出你们的真名  齐格弗里德\NThey'll get your real name, Siegfried.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.11,0:17:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我的呼叫机\NWait, my walkie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.56,0:17:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跑哪儿去了  -别慌\N- Where is it? - Don't panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.99,0:17:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你冲向员工会议的时候还带着\NYou had it with you when you ran out to that staff meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.14,0:17:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀  男厕\NRight! The men's room.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.94,0:17:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩不许动\NYou two don't move!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.31,0:17:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锁好门  我的呼叫机不见了\NLock it down, people! I'm off walkie!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.97,0:17:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再说一遍  我的呼叫机不见了\NI repeat, I am off walkie!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.14,0:17:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  我们被锁起来了\NNo no no. We're locked in.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.85,0:17:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊\NWhat are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.70,0:17:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧  齐格弗里德\NLet's go, Siegfried.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.40,0:17:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我替你掩护  -好棒\N- I'm springing you. - Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.27,0:17:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进来了\NI'm in!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.29,0:17:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始爬吧\NNow go!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.64,0:18:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬向救援  小矮人\NCrawl for help, little buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.87,0:18:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难以置信我跟个白痴似的\NI can't believe what an idiot I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.46,0:18:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我信  -我也信\N- I can. - Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.27,0:18:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我毁了艾玛的机会\NI ruined Emma's chances.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.44,0:18:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想为她做件了不起的事\NI just wanted to do something great for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.01,0:18:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你已经做到了\NBen, you do something great for Emma
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.56,0:18:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是每次你看着她说\Nevery time you look at her and say,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.97,0:18:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嗨  宝贝儿  我是爹地"的时候\N"Hi, baby. It's me, Daddy."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.17,0:18:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真这么想吗  -真的\N- You really think so? - I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.98,0:18:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起我说你自私\NI'm sorry I called you selfish.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.69,0:18:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我无视你了\NIt's cool. I ignored you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.14,0:18:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢  塔克  你原谅我吗\NWhat about you, Tuck? Will you forgive me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.13,0:18:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会动摇的[也有"动不了"的意思]\NI'm not budging.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.16,0:18:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你这么难搞呢  塔克尔\NWhy do you have to be so difficult, Tucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.26,0:18:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我都道歉了  -不是\N- I just apologized. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.06,0:18:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我动不了了\NI'm not moving.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.89,0:18:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我卡住了\NI am stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.59,0:18:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把我弄出来\NGet me out of here!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.44,0:18:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本还真的知道该怎么待客啊  是吧\NBen really knows how to show 'em a good time, doesn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.40,0:18:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我起来了  乔丹  没事  妈咪来了\NI'm up! Jordan, it's ok! Mommy's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.97,0:18:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歇着吧  超级妈妈\NOh, give it a rest, super mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.64,0:19:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  邦妮·维勒\NHi, Bonnie Wheeler,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.57,0:19:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的妈妈\Nreal mom,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.60,0:19:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我无与伦比的小跟班\Nand my nondescript sidekick.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.82,0:19:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我睡着了\NI'm sorry. I guess I fell asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.65,0:19:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么回事啊\NWhat's the dealio with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.38,0:19:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你想让我们看起来很坏呢\NWhy are you trying to make the rest of us look bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.53,0:19:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有  我只是想让一切都完美\NI'm not. I'm just trying to make everything perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.22,0:19:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你做得如何呢\NHow's that working for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.38,0:19:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我养活了两个男孩\NLook, I've raised two boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.92,0:19:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说\Nand I'm here to tell you that
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.02,0:19:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有完美这回事\Nthere is no such thing as perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.42,0:19:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婴儿虽小\NThey might be small,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.95,0:19:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可整疯你绝对不是问题\Nbut a baby can take you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.73,0:19:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫发无损的过一天\NGetting through the day in one piece--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.71,0:19:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  就大功告成了\Nthat, my friend, is job done.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.08,0:19:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\NI know.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.73,0:19:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不知道我在干什么\NI'm sorry. I don't know what I'm doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.75,0:19:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不断努力  但就是想  打个盹\NI try and I try, but all I want to do, is take a nap.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.46,0:19:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我懂\NYeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.74,0:19:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打个长长的盹\NA really really long nap.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.68,0:19:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子让我折寿\NThis kid is sucking the life out of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.05,0:19:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂你  莉兹\NOh, I feel you, Lizzy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.39,0:19:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-伊兹  -爱啥啥\N- Izzy. - Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.66,0:19:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没人在乎\NNot that anybody seems to care,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.45,0:19:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  本哪儿去了\Nbut, um, where's Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.75,0:19:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊  有人听得见吗\NHelp! Can anybody hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.71,0:19:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被困在洗衣房了\NWe're stuck in the laundry room.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.00,0:20:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得一个人去就行了\NI guess one of us should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.03,0:20:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗  我们好绝望啊\NAnyone! We're desperate!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.67,0:20:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且我真的很想上厕所\NAnd I really need to use the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.67,0:20:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得救啦\NWe're saved!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.18,0:20:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊兹  不是你看上去的那样\NIzzy, it's not how it looks.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.72,0:20:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是你朋友困在通风口\NLooks like you're hiding out in a laundry room
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.68,0:20:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们却躲在洗衣房里喝小酒\Ndrinking beer while your friend is stuck in a vent.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.46,0:20:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  塔克  -嘿  小妞\N- Hey, Tuck. - Oh hey, girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.19,0:20:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我很抱歉\NLook, I'm sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.77,0:20:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可显然我和艾玛都没准备好上你的课\Nbut clearly Emma and I aren't ready for your class.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.05,0:20:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不像你可以从从容容当奶妈\NI just don't have it together like you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.00,0:20:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她晕倒在你沙发上了\NShe passed out on your couch.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.58,0:20:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.31,0:20:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该向你道歉\NI kinda owe you an apology.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.68,0:20:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实只是想和一个有趣的人共度一晚\NI just wanted a night off with a cool guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.70,0:20:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不知道该如何得逞\NI didn't know how else to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.77,0:20:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你所谓的审批流程呢\NSo the approval process?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.55,0:20:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没这回事\NDon't really have one.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.15,0:20:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真巧啊  我也没有\NWhat a coincidence-- neither do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.50,0:20:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我们可以从头再来\NSo maybe we can start over.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.06,0:20:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这个结果\NI would like that very much.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.32,0:20:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-吃薯片吗  -吃  饿死我了\N- Chip? - Aw yes. Starving.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.02,0:20:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁赢了  我能喝瓶啤酒吗\NWho's winning? Hey, can I get a beer?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.64,0:21:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  来了  -谢谢\N- Yeah, here. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.38,0:21:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NMm, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.05,0:21:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在这儿呢\NStill here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.45,0:21:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托帮点小忙  好吧\NA little help here, please. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.39,0:21:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  别装作听不见\NOkay. Don't act like y'all can't hear me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.57,0:21:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  那蘸酱还是我做的呢\NHey, I made that dip!
