[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.05,0:00:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你吧  艾玛\NI'm telling you, Emma. 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.77,0:00:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晒下太阳  冲会儿浪  再喝点冷饮\NA little sun, a little surf, a little cold one--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.23,0:00:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再没比这更美好的生活了\Nlife does not get any better than this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.11,0:00:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  抱歉我迟到了  我的人字拖\NHello? Sorry I'm late. My flip-flops
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.14,0:00:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在十四大道甩丢了\Nflopped out around 14th.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.22,0:00:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是整哪出呢  -欢迎来到维勒海滩\N- What's going on? - Welcome to Wheeler beach,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.20,0:00:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有陌生人会要你往他的背上抹润肤露\Nwhere strangers don't ask you to rub lotion on their back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.66,0:00:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来点刨冰么\NSnow cones? 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.59,0:00:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是冰箱从来不除冰的好处之一\NOne of the benefits of never de-frosting the freezer.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.93,0:00:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\NListen...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.66,0:00:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可供你选择的口味有\NYour current flavor choices include
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.91,0:00:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啤酒味\Nbeer
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.01,0:00:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者番茄酱味\Nor ketchup.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.51,0:00:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我建议你两样都加点\NI recommend the combo.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.15,0:00:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为我们要去真正的海滩呢\NOh, I thought we were going to the real beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.38,0:00:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里我可以叫人往我的背上抹润肤露\NYou know, where I get to ask strangers to rub lotion on my back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.08,0:00:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来是这样打算的\NWe were.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.78,0:00:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不幸的是  我被急召回去工作\NUnfortunately, I got called into work.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.28,0:00:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在简直是一年中最热的时候\NBut it's the hottest day of the year.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.38,0:00:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的疯子会在这种时候出门啊\NWhat kind of crazy person is even gonna be out?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.35,0:00:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐  各位\NMerry Christmas, everybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.57,0:00:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都做好准备重温下\NAre you all ready to revive
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.93,0:00:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒家族的珍贵传统了吗\Na cherished Wheeler family tradition?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.00,0:00:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  吃煎饼大赛\NAll right! Pancake-eating contest!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.07,0:01:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  而是一年一度的圣诞全家福\NNo. The annual Christmas card photo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.39,0:01:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小本的主意\NIt was Benji's idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.69,0:01:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家福哦\NWhoo! Family photo!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.01,0:01:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么听都不觉得这事有多令人兴奋哈\NThere really is just no way to make that sound exciting.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.01,0:01:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  因为老妈以前总是把我们打扮成圣诞麋鹿\NYeah. Because Mom used to dress us up like reindeer
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.34,0:01:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整得我们跟个白痴似的\Nand make us look like idiots.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.54,0:01:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但是现在有了艾玛了\NI know. But now that Emma's here,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.78,0:01:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把她打扮成麋鹿\NI wanna dress her up like a reindeer
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.02,0:01:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她看起来像个白痴似的\Nand make her look like an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最爱那个圣诞卡了\NAww, I always loved that card.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.39,0:01:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直是那一季最大的亮点\NIt was the highlight of the season.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.04,0:01:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  莱丽\NThank you, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.15,0:01:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会把卡片贴冰箱上  对着大笑...\NWe put it on our fridge, and laughed...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.35,0:01:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次看到时都会肃然起敬滴\Nin admiration whenever we saw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.90,0:01:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴你喜欢那卡片\NWell, I'm glad you liked it
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.93,0:01:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这回你也会出现在上面\Nbecause you're gonna be in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.38,0:01:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是  塔克  既然是照全家福\NYou too, Tuck. This is about family
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.09,0:01:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩现在都算是艾玛的家人了\Nand you're both part of Emma's family now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.52,0:01:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于你们的老爸中途退出\NWell, God knows she needs a new one
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.06,0:01:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是时候该给她添个新家庭成员了\Nsince your father belw up the old one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.60,0:01:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啤酒刨冰啊\NOoh, beer cone! 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.69,0:01:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上我才把他的肥头大耳从我们的\NI actually just finished cutting his fat head out
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.79,0:01:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相册集里剪光\Nof all of our albums.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.75,0:01:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你们不是三年前就离婚了吗\NBut you guys got divorced over three years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.66,0:01:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  前两年我还\NYeah, well, I spent the
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.30,0:01:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忙着让他声名尽毁呢\Nfirst two years trying to ruin his credit.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.74,0:01:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就开始干这个了\NAnd then I just kind of landed on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.64,0:01:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克\NHey, Tuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.76,0:01:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为维勒家族的最新成员\NAs the newest member of the Wheeler clan,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.32,0:02:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能明天开我老妈的车\Nany way I can talk you into taking my mom's car
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.53,0:02:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去新泽西把服装运过来\Nout to Jersey tomorrow to pick up the costumes?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.47,0:02:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不怎么会开车的\NOh, you know I don't really drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.49,0:02:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会  我来开  能让我去吗\NOh, I do! I'll drive. Can I do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.07,0:02:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是新成员\NI'm a new member too.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.69,0:02:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥我不能去  有事吗\NWell, why can't I go? What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.67,0:02:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道圣诞节肯定少不了圣诞老人的对吧\NWell, you know how it wouldn't be Christmas without Santa?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.20,0:02:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞老人一向是老爸扮来着\NBut Dad was always Santa!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.79,0:02:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的雪橇明天早上就会到达\NAnd his sleigh lands tomorrow morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.97,0:02:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你老爸要来镇里了吗\NYour father is coming to town?!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.45,0:02:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐哈\NMerry Christmas!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.98,0:02:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边 惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.09,0:02:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲 雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions*
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.98,0:02:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  老爸马上就要到了\NOkay, Mom, Dad will be here any minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.62,0:02:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算我求你了  就过这一个周末\NAnd I'm begging you-- one weekend,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.68,0:02:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍一张全家福  千万可别再吵架了\None photo, no fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.67,0:02:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要担心的可不是我\NHey, I'm not the one you need to worry about.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.14,0:02:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就已经向前看了\NI have moved on.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.88,0:02:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷·维勒只不过是我后视镜里的\NRay Wheeler is just a speed bump in
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.43,0:02:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一条远去的减速带罢了\Nmy rearview mirror.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.39,0:02:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意在倒车时猛地关上车门\NI wouldn't mind slamming the car in reverse
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.16,0:02:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后倒回去  -老妈\N- and backing up-- - Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.05,0:02:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NAll right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.35,0:02:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  你也帮忙劝劝嘛\NDanny, back me up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.82,0:03:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟  这世上有些事\NDude, there are some things in life 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.03,0:03:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是别插手的好\Nyou just don't get in between.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.52,0:03:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如熊和它的幼崽  僵尸和大脑\Na bear and its cub, a zombie and a brain,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.77,0:03:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸和老妈的大战\Nand Mom and Dad fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.35,0:03:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他来了\NThat's him!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.86,0:03:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  别忘了\NMom, remember--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.68,0:03:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是怎么在摧残我的灵魂\NHow he crushed my soul
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.74,0:03:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后任我自生自灭的\Nand left my ego for dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.91,0:03:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是过去式了  放心\NDistant memory. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.20,0:03:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  -本本\N- Dad! - Ben Ben!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.74,0:03:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来还是那么帅\NOh, you're looking good as always.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.08,0:03:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-老爸  -丹  都长成大小伙子了\N- Hey, Dad! - Dan the man!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.53,0:03:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快速思考\NThink fast!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.54,0:03:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在这儿啊\NThere she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.80,0:03:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊\NHi. Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.17,0:03:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你们都知道他的美貌是遗传谁的了吧\NI think we know where she gets her good looks from, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.37,0:03:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听到了一个从未想念过的声音\NThere's a sound I haven't missed once.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.60,0:03:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱下孩子\NGrab the baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.56,0:03:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邦妮\NBonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.48,0:03:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷\NRay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.53,0:04:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看咱们\NWow! Would you look at us?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.93,0:04:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么幸福的一大家子啊\NJust one big happy family.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.65,0:04:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  那个...你的生意怎么样\NSo Dad, how's business?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.94,0:04:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的\NGood. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.95,0:04:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手头有三家的房子要建呢\NI got three homes going up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.20,0:04:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是讽刺啊\NOh, that's ironic.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.94,0:04:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你的专长是拆房子来着\NI thought your specialty was wrecking them.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.69,0:04:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只拆那些旧"危房"而已\NJust the old broken-down ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.64,0:04:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  拜托  你说过你不会提起那些事的\NDad, come on. You said you weren't go there.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.88,0:04:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提起啥  中年危机岛么\NGo where? Mid-life crisis island?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.98,0:04:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太迟了  我听说你早就被选为那里的岛主了\NToo late! I heard you were just elected mayor!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.52,0:04:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你该尝试下啥么  瑜伽\NYou know what you should try? Yoga.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.23,0:04:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都是两个星期练一次来着\NI've been doing it twice a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.19,0:04:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都可以摸到我的脚趾了\NI can actually touch my toes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.34,0:04:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  那你就能更容易地\NOh. Well, that should make it easier
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.08,0:04:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的脑袋从你...   抽出来\Nfor you to pull your head outta your--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.36,0:04:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈\NMom!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.61,0:04:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了嘛\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.83,0:04:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都还没说到关键词呢\NYou didn't know where I was going with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.99,0:04:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你屁股里抽出来\NAss!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.52,0:04:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  也许你都做过了  算了\NOkay? Maybe you did. Just--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.86,0:04:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有搞错啊\NSeriously?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.74,0:04:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁家的圣诞服装会多到要用十四个箱子来装啊\NWho has 14 boxes of Christmas costumes?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.76,0:04:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是上帝也会觉得这有点过量了吧\NEven Jesus would call this overkill.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.92,0:04:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那你就帮帮忙\NOkay. Well, then make yourself useful
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.46,0:04:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给咱们找件最好的吧\Nand find us a good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.87,0:04:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要件看起来俏皮又可爱的\NI wanna be something naughty and nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.60,0:04:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.04,0:04:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个箱子里装满了各式各样的胡子\NWe've got a-- a box full of random beards.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.66,0:05:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及天使用具大杂烩\NSome assorted angel paraphernalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.99,0:05:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有光环哦\NHalo!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.05,0:05:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是什么\NWhat's over here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.47,0:05:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这箱子里装满了丹尼以前的家庭作业\NOh! And a box full of Danny's old schoolwork?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.86,0:05:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了莱丽\NSo Riley...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.11,0:05:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我跟你说"看看那些箱子"\NWhen I said, "Hey, check the boxes,"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.19,0:05:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是"看看箱子里都装了些什么"\NI kinda meant, "Hey, check the boxes!"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.22,0:05:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我都没空注意你\NOh, I'm sorry. I was too busy ignoring you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.15,0:05:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过等等\NOh, but wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.93,0:05:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧我发现了什么\NWhat do we have here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.82,0:05:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼尔·J·维勒先生的日记\NThe journal of one Mr. Daniel J. Wheeler
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.63,0:05:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天呐  那可是我们的高年级作业呢\NOh my God! Aww, that was our senior class project.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.58,0:05:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们要不要偷看下  会不会不太好\NShould we read it? Is that like totally wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.75,0:05:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  你说什么  我正在看呢\NOh, I'm sorry. What were you saying? I was reading.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.20,0:05:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  要是你都打算侵犯别人的隐私了\NTucker, if you're gonna invade someone's privacy,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.48,0:05:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好歹你也大声读出来啊\Nat least have the decency to read it out loud.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.44,0:05:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里还有我待的地儿吗\NHey, you got room for one more out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.16,0:05:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  雷  对不起\NLook, Ray, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.56,0:05:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我确实没法装出一副见到你很高兴的样子\NBut I just can't pretend that I'm happy to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.55,0:05:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是完全不行\NWell, I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.81,0:05:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他们得给我颁个奖\NBut then they'd have to give me an award,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.33,0:06:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还得写写获奖感言什么的\Nand I'd have to write a speech
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.27,0:06:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁有这个空啊\Nand you know, who's got the time?!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.43,0:06:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想跟你谈谈\NI just wanna have a conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.69,0:06:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论你想说啥  我都不想听\NWell, whatever it is, I don't want to hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.13,0:06:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想向你道歉\NI want to apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.29,0:06:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续\NGo on.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.07,0:06:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你理应过得更好\NYou deserved better.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.74,0:06:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时经历了太多还把一切都发泄在你身上\NI was going through a lot and I was taking it out on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.79,0:06:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此我很抱歉\NAnd I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.59,0:06:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过不得不说  看到你现在过得这么好\NBut I gotta say, seeing how good you look--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.37,0:06:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心里总算好过多了\Nit makes me feel a lot better.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.29,0:06:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我看起来很好吗\NYou think I look good?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.72,0:06:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我觉得你看起来美极了\NYeah, I think you look fantastic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.60,0:06:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然我离你远点对你有好处\NApparently having me a thousand miles away is good for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.88,0:06:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道是不是因为那个\NI don't know if it's that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.83,0:06:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或说是我喝了很多水变得水嫩了\NOr just that I've been drinking more water.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.36,0:06:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得咱们\NHey, what do you say you
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.18,0:06:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽个时间好好聚聚怎么样\Nand I spend a little quality time together?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.68,0:06:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的  没孩子们在场的时候\NYou know, without the K-I-Ds.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.75,0:06:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还庆幸我们只生了两个吗\NYou still happy we stopped at two?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.24,0:06:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然\NEcstatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.17,0:06:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是新来的那位倒是挺有希望\NBut the new one shows promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.38,0:06:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是我照看她\NI'm babysitting her tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.57,0:06:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他们也没说\NAnd they didn't tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.54,0:06:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能带男人过来\Nthat I couldn't invite any boys over.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.46,0:06:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要不要加入\NSo do you want to join?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.90,0:07:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那就这么约定了\NYeah. Yeah, it's a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.87,0:07:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺想你的  邦妮\NI've missed you, Bonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.92,0:07:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  好像  有情况哦\NSo? Huh? Well? See?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.19,0:07:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\NI don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.80,0:07:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当我是发疯吧  不过我真觉得你老爸\NCall me crazy, but I think that your father
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.18,0:07:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似有想和我复合的意思呢\Nis looking to move back to Bonnie town!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.38,0:07:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NOh, wait wait wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.43,0:07:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算找到点猛料了\NI think we might finally have something.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.44,0:07:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一部分都是讲暗恋的呢\NOh, there's a whole section about a secret crush.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.79,0:07:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来那个大块头当时还真是堕入情网了呢\NIt looks like the big guy was in love.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.78,0:07:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\NOh yeah-- no.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.41,0:07:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我对丹尼最了解的一点就是 \NTrust me, if there's anything I know about Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.20,0:07:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从没有真正喜欢过谁\Nit's that he was never in love.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.44,0:07:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话你就留着跟"X"女孩说吧\NYeah, tell that to girl "X."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.54,0:07:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"X"女孩  谁是"X"女孩\NGirl "X"? Who's girl "X"?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.53,0:07:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉着这可能是个代号\NOh, I'm sensing that might be a code.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.94,0:07:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 \NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.93,0:07:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜他每天都去看那个女孩的\NYeah, I guess he checked her out every day 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.51,0:07:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陆上曲棍球训练\Nat field hockey practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.35,0:07:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能  我那时就在打陆上曲棍球\NThere is no way! I played field hockey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.65,0:07:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们常拿那支队里的女生开玩笑\NWe made fun of every girl on that team.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.05,0:07:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\NWait.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.48,0:07:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前在陆上曲棍球队吗\NYou were on the field hockey team?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.73,0:07:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.26,0:08:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续念啊  咱们一定要搞清楚是谁\NOkay, keep reading. We gotta figure this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.10,0:08:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  就这么多  完了\NOh no, that's it. The end.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.88,0:08:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说一部分的时候  我指的是那两行\NWhen I said section I just meant those two lines.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.42,0:08:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我\NOh, give it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.06,0:08:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你做的好事\NNow look what you have done.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.74,0:08:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下我们永远都不知道是谁了\NNow we'll never know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.32,0:08:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和老妈  咋样\NYou and Mom... so?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.52,0:08:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  你们  有情况吗\NHuh? Well? See?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.17,0:08:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我不想撒谎\NLook, I'm not gonna lie,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.96,0:08:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实很高兴见到她\Nit was really good to see her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.41,0:08:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我也不是那类指望\NLook, I don't wanna be one of those
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.73,0:08:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"老爸老妈还能复合"的孩子\N"Maybe mommy and daddy are getting back together" kids, 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.19,0:08:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是呢\Nbut...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.57,0:08:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指不定老爸你和老妈还真能复合呢\NMaybe mommy and daddy are getting back together?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.61,0:08:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你们的想法\NIs that what you were thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.43,0:08:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  那是不可能的\NI'm sorry, that is not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.87,0:08:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经在和别人交往了\NI'm actually seeing someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.23,0:08:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  就在你和老妈就快要\NNow? Just when you and Mom are about
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.16,0:08:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复合的时候\Nto get back together?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.33,0:08:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想她会明白的\NI'm sure she'll understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.40,0:08:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  不要\NDad, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.97,0:08:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你千万别告诉老妈你已经在和人交往了\NYou cannot tell Mom you're in a relationship!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.68,0:08:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好歹也等到圣诞全家福照了后再说吧  拜托\NAt least not until after the Christmas photo. Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.38,0:08:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你幸福她可就不高兴了\NShe will not be happy about your happiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.09,0:08:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像我  可是很替你开心呢\NYou know, unlike me, who's very happy for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.59,0:08:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\NI'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.13,0:09:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫什么\NWhat's her name?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.22,0:09:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫史蒂夫\NHis name is Steve.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.24,0:09:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是...奇怪呢\NThat's... weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.26,0:09:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你说的是史蒂夫\N'Cause you said Steve
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.36,0:09:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这通常是男人的名字\Nand that's usually a boy's name.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.16,0:09:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你还说的是"他"\NAnd then you said "His."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.40,0:09:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我是同志\NBen, I'm gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.07,0:09:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOkay...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.05,0:09:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当真\NWow! Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.31,0:09:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你可以挑个更好的时机吧\NProbably could have eased into that a little more.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.27,0:09:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我看到个机会就顺势说出来了\NI'm sorry. I saw an opening and I just kind of went for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.77,0:09:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定你是同志吗\NAre you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.16,0:09:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都确定到跟一个叫史蒂夫的男人同居了\NSure enough that I'm living with a guy named Steve.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.87,0:09:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你和老妈是怎么回事\NBut what about you and Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.11,0:09:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我爱过你妈妈\NBen, I loved your Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.86,0:09:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她在一起就好像是开了一辆好车\NBeing with her was like driving a great car.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.05,0:09:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是有天那辆车\NAnd then one day that car
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.33,0:09:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的手提箱甩到前面的草坪上去了\Nthrows your suitcase out on the front lawn,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.88,0:09:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是你就上了飞机  然后你就意识到\Nso you get on a plane, and you realize...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.12,0:09:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我滴个神呐\NHoly cow!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.05,0:09:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来我是个飞行员\NI'm a pilot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.18,0:09:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你这个表达能力\NAlong with your delivery,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.12,0:10:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您真该再琢磨琢磨你刚才的那个类比\Nyou might wanna work on your analogies.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.22,0:10:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们常说跟第一次跟人出柜是最难的\NThey say the first time you talk to someone is the hardest,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.07,0:10:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以等到我和你妈和你哥出柜的时候  我肯定\Nso when I talk to your mother and your brother, i'm sure--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.68,0:10:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不要\NOh, no no no no no!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.98,0:10:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你千万不能告诉老妈或丹尼\NYou cannot tell Mom or Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.70,0:10:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少不是现在\NAt least not now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.63,0:10:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们还要照张快乐的全家福呢\NI've got a happy family photo to take,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.96,0:10:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然"同志"这个词也有快乐的意思\Nand just because gay means happy,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.39,0:10:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这并不意味着他们会快乐\Nit doesn't mean they will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.71,0:10:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我向来不喜欢撒谎\NI just hate to be dishonest.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.27,0:10:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  只有当别人问起而你又不说实话才叫撒谎\NDad, it's only dishonest if someone asks.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.51,0:10:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  没人会问的\NAnd trust me, no one is gonna ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.67,0:10:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问什么\NAsk what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.79,0:10:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以多快地转移话题\NHow quickly we can change the subject?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.24,0:10:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个朋友正在考虑出去\NI have a friend who's thinking about coming out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.59,0:10:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去拜访吗\NTo visit?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.80,0:10:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出柜\NOf the closet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.29,0:10:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥他会在\NWhy is he in--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.86,0:10:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个"柜子"啊  明白了\NOh... that closet. Got it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.29,0:10:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他还没做好出柜的准备\NBut he's not ready to come out yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.14,0:10:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我想他做好准备了\NActually, I think he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.47,0:10:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么大不了的嘛\NWhat's the big deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.21,0:10:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是他是同志  那他就是呗\NIf he's gay, he's gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.44,0:10:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留给我的女人更多了而已\NIt just means more ladies for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.01,0:10:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没  绝对没问题\NSee? Totally on board.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.89,0:10:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可如果你朋友今天是同志的话\NBut if your friend's gay today,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.08,0:10:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天仍然还是啊\Nhe'll probably still be gay tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.91,0:10:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,譬如  五点以后\NSay, after 5:00?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.22,0:10:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道具体是什么意思\NI'm not exactly sure how that works,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.04,0:10:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但觉得他说的很对\Nbut I think he's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.27,0:10:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  可以  他都等了这么久了\NAll right, it's cool. He's waited this long,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.69,0:10:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等一天也无妨\NI'm sure he can wait another day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.57,0:11:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.29,0:11:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定知道你说的朋友是谁了\NI'm pretty sure I know who your friend is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.38,0:11:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\NYou do?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.76,0:11:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你能接受吗\NAnd you're okay with that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.54,0:11:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  能接受\NYeah, I'm okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.70,0:11:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就太好了\NOh, that's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.56,0:11:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是太好了\NThat is so great.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.61,0:11:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我得接这个电话\NOh, you know what? I'm gonna take this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.92,0:11:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这个秘密目前就你知我知\NLet's just keep this between us for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.08,0:11:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本担心你母亲知道了的话会吓坏的\NBen's worried if your mother finds out she's gonna freak.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.52,0:11:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然  这是你我的秘密  -谢谢\N- Totally. It's our secret. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.78,0:11:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  老弟  你要知道\NHey, bro, just know...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.56,0:11:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会永远爱你的\NI'll always love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.41,0:11:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\NThanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.50,0:11:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是喝酒还是得付钱的\NBut you're still gonna have to pay for this beer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.87,0:11:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  维勒  在家吗\NHey, Wheeler! You home?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.31,0:11:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有几个小问题哦\NI got a couple of questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.28,0:11:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我知道答案\NOh, and I've got some answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.54,0:11:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盒子放到后面  然后莱丽走人\NBoxes in the back. Riley out the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.02,0:12:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我真的不习惯\NWow, don't think I'm gonna make a habit of this,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.71,0:12:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你很漂亮\Nbut you look beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.81,0:12:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你满身是汗\NThanks. You look sweaty.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.85,0:12:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  莱丽\NListen, Riley,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.84,0:12:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要女性朋友的建议\NI need the advice of a girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.71,0:12:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你来了\NAnd, well, you're here,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.85,0:12:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...\Nso...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.88,0:12:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我和雷复合的话你怎么看\NWhat would you say if Ray and I got back together?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.18,0:12:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你真的想知道我的建议的话...\NWell, if you're really asking my advice...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.66,0:12:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这个想法太可怕了\NI think it's a truly horrible idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.02,0:12:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说你的意思是\NSo what you're saying is
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.49,0:12:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该把他灌醉  然后使出\NI should liquor him up, and then break out
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.57,0:12:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几招性感诱惑杀手锏\Na few of my seductive charms.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.19,0:12:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我说的和这个恰好相反\NYeah, that's actually the opposite of what I was saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.50,0:12:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但是我不喜欢你说的\NI know, but I didn't like what you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.08,0:12:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷来报到啦\NGrandpa reporting for duty.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.53,0:12:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\NHi.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.80,0:12:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这不是大裤衩吗  -对啊\N- Fatpants?! - Right?!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.86,0:12:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝  女大十八变啊\NOh my God! Look at you!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.23,0:12:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会想到那样的身躯里藏着这么个你\NWho knew that this was hidden inside all that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.48,0:12:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次见到你很高兴  维勒先生\NReally nice to see you again, Mr. Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.78,0:12:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们今晚过得愉快哦\NYou guys have a good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.69,0:12:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘭  嘭  嘭  嘭  嘭\NBoom boom boom boom boom.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.15,0:12:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是天生一对啊\NOddly made for each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.51,0:13:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你读了我的日记\NWait! You read my journal?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.14,0:13:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有毛病吗你\NWhat's wrong with you?!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.29,0:13:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  先别抽风行吗\NWhat? Stay with me. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.14,0:13:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽知道X女孩的事了\NRiley knows about girl "X."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.23,0:13:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你破解了我的密码\NYou broke my code?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.28,0:13:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我叫了我三岁的侄子\NNo, I called up my three-year-old nephew
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.37,0:13:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他破解的\Nand he broke it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.66,0:13:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是莱丽还不知道\NBut Riley has not, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.15,0:13:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在你有两个选择\NSo you've got yourself two options:
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.09,0:13:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一  男人一点勇敢承认\NOne, finally man up and admit that 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.18,0:13:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经喜欢她很多年了\Nyou've been in love with her after all these years.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.38,0:13:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者  你可以...\NOr, you can--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.96,0:13:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你可以躲起来\Nor you can just hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.05,0:13:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里...嗷\NWhere did you g-- oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.91,0:13:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨\NHi.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.25,0:13:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道高中的时候你哥哥喜欢谁吗\NDo you who your brother was in love with in high school?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.66,0:13:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道  他自己\NYeah. Himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.20,0:13:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且现在他们还在一起\NI think they're still together.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.48,0:13:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道他现在在哪里吗\NWell, do you know where he is?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.60,0:13:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟他说个天大的坏消息\NI'm gonna give him such grief.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.74,0:13:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该在那边和我的...\NYeah, I think he's over there with my--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.03,0:13:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸哪儿去了\NWhere's my dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.80,0:13:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道一些你不知道的事\NI know something you don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.81,0:13:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定比你知道的多\NGuarantee I know a whole lot more.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.97,0:13:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你父母要复合了吗\NDo you know your folks might be getting back together?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.23,0:13:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个已经试过了\NAlready been down that path,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.55,0:14:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果没有出现传说中的幸福和彩虹\Nand it does not lead to happiness and rainbows.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.08,0:14:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  也可能出现彩虹[同性恋]了\NWell, maybe a rainbow.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.99,0:14:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那应该有人去告诉你妈一声\NWell, then someone should probably tell your mom
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.40,0:14:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在正准备发起猛烈进攻呢\Nbecause she is about to launch a full-on assault.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.62,0:14:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在吗  -对\N- Right now? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.99,0:14:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了  帮我招呼一下\NI gotta go! Hey, cover for me!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.02,0:14:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等等  你还记得我们偷了\NWait wait wait wait. You remember when we stole
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.13,0:14:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邻居花园里所有的精灵玩具吗\Nall the neighbors' garden gnomes?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.91,0:14:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后对面街上那个神经病\NAnd then that crazy Johnnie Haskell
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.56,0:14:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约翰尼·哈斯克尔\Nfrom across the street
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.67,0:14:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要求搜查我们家车库\Ndemanded to search our garage.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.25,0:14:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊\NThat's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.23,0:14:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  当时我们是怎么躲过去的来着\NOh my gosh, how did we get ourselves out of that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.21,0:14:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们让孩子当了替罪羊  把他们禁足了一周\NWe blamed the boys and grounded them for a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.89,0:14:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候养孩子还是有点用的\NThose kids do come in handy sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.07,0:14:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你还记得\NOh, and do you remember
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.22,0:14:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约翰尼总是在自己家院子里光着膀子干活吗\Nhow Johnnie always used to work out in his yard shirtless?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.32,0:14:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.58,0:14:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我当然难忘啦\NYeah, I remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.50,0:14:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧\NAre you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.24,0:14:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我很好  我只是觉得\NYeah, I'm great. I just feel
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.57,0:14:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该跟你说件事\Nlike I need to talk to you about something.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.50,0:14:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷  你的小甜心就在这里\NRay, it's your bonbon.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.82,0:14:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说什么尽管说\NYou can tell me anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.68,0:14:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来想等到明天拍完照之后说的\NI was gonna wait until after the picture tomorrow
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.60,0:14:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不想让大家太尴尬  但是...\N'cause I didn't want it to get too awkward, but--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.43,0:15:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会发现我现在...\NWell, I think you'll find that I am...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.74,0:15:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般都能接受\Nfairly receptive.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.77,0:15:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邦妮\NBonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.29,0:15:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我说不出口\NI'm sorry. I just can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.96,0:15:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能你只是需要点灵感\NWell, maybe you just need a little inspiration.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.50,0:15:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惹火邦妮欢迎你哦\NWelcome to Bonnie town!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.74,0:15:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邦妮\NBonnie!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.36,0:15:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊\NOh God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.18,0:15:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这得造成多大的精神创伤啊\NThis is gonna cost so much in therapy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.66,0:15:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的上帝啊\NOh God!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.20,0:15:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是夏天最好的\NAnd that is how you cool off
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.61,0:15:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解暑方法啦\Nduring a heat wave.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.93,0:15:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  本啊  你不会敲门吗\NHonestly, Ben, don't you ever knock?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.82,0:15:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我老忘记这原来是我的公寓\NSorry I keep forgetting it's my apartment!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.77,0:15:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你需要什么\NWell, okay, but if you could
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.84,0:15:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓紧拿上  然后...\Njust grab whatever it is you needed, and--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.57,0:15:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你要怎么办  一辈子\NSo what's the plan? Hide from her
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.34,0:15:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-都躲着她吗  -那有何难\N- for the rest of your life? - Well, how hard can it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.28,0:15:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她又不经常过来\NIt's not like she comes over that much.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.74,0:15:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莱丽要过来了  -快点  回酒吧\N- Riley's coming over. - Quick! Back to the bar!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.82,0:15:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个主意太好了\NHey, that's a great idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.71,0:15:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒家的男人在酒吧联络感情\NWheeler men bonding at the bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.00,0:15:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维勒家的女人在公寓交流秘密  我们走  老爸\NWheeler women bonding at the apartment-- let's go, Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.05,0:15:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上和男孩子出去最爽了\NNothing like a night out with the boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.54,0:16:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说男孩子的意思是...  -她知道了  老爸\N- And by boys, I mean-- - She's got it, Dad, yep!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.41,0:16:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道你扮演的哪只\NI don't know which one you are,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.78,0:16:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你绝对是最可爱的驯鹿哦\Nbut you're definitely the cutest reindeer of them all.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.12,0:16:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么时候变得跟传说中的父母一样了\NWhen did I become one of those parents?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.21,0:16:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能就是看到你穿着小鹿角衣服之后吧\NProbably two seconds after I saw you in those little antlers.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.86,0:16:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  圣诞宝宝  我们开始吧\NOkay, Santa baby, let's move it along.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.47,0:16:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快到了\NChristmas is just around the corner
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.98,0:16:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于可以休息了\Nand so is my next break.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.90,0:16:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我们一会儿就好了\NYeah, we'll just be another minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.53,0:16:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得怎么样\NWell, what do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.16,0:16:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸我像不像睿智之人\NDoes your dad look like a wise man?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.22,0:16:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最起码比你昨晚睿智多了\NWiser than you did last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.47,0:16:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你妈来说  昨晚跟她出柜可能\NYeah, that probably wasn't the best time
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.87,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不是好点子\Nto come out to your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.09,0:16:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  我觉得我应该按照传统\NYou know what? I think I'll do it the old-fashioned way
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.52,0:16:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在感恩节的时候昭告天下\Nand just blurt it out at Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.89,0:16:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞天使来到了人间哦\NAnd the Christmas angel is upon us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.04,0:16:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿我们可以开溜\NHey, maybe later we can ditch the fat man
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.50,0:16:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就能蹂躏一下我的天使光环了\Nand you can try to tarnish my halo.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.77,0:16:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  妈\NOkay, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.74,0:16:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你应该站在这里  -我知道  但是我...\N- You'll be standing over here. - I know, but I was--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.97,0:16:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是这里  这里  -好  好了\N- W-way-- way over here. - Okay, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.42,0:16:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  这不是什么联谊会\NOkay, this isn't a social, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.50,0:17:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以大家就不用装矜持了\NLet's shake our tinsel makers
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.27,0:17:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓紧准备好开拍\Nand get a move on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.54,0:17:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  大家快点  准备拍了\NOkay, guys, come on! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.02,0:17:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再穿件格子裙的话\NWell, put a plaid skirt on this
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是毕业照上的样子了\Nand it's my senior class picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.01,0:17:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  快点\NDanny, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.58,0:17:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就告诉我你秘密暗恋的人是谁嘛\NWhy won't you tell me who your secret crush was?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.76,0:17:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你好像没理解\NI think you're kinda missing the point
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.30,0:17:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"秘密"的意思\Nof it being a secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.18,0:17:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是莱丽啊  你对我无话不说的\NIt's me, Riley. You tell me everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.77,0:17:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个又有什么好害羞的呢\NWhat do you have to be embarrassed about?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.67,0:17:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有什么好害羞的\NI don't have anything to be embarrassed about.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.74,0:17:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是事情过去很久了\NIt was just a long time ago
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.77,0:17:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再提\Nand I don't want to talk about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.27,0:17:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右脚上那个是我的礼物吗\NAre my presents on the right feet?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.21,0:17:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看看\NLet me see.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.93,0:17:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\NDamn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.37,0:17:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像弄破了一块软皮糖\NI think I just popped a gumdrop.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.17,0:17:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  说真的\NOkay. It's official.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.04,0:17:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能再丢脸一点吗\NI can't possibly be more humiliated.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.37,0:17:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了戴帽子\NDon't forget your hat!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.99,0:17:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我表示无话可说\NOh, and I stand corrected.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.62,0:18:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼以前的精灵服装\NDanny's old elf costume.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.90,0:18:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自打四岁起他就穿不上了\NAww, he hasn't fit into that since he was four.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.93,0:18:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到铃声了吗\NHear those bells?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.64,0:18:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你被糖果手杖打死之前\NYeah, that's the last sound you'll hear
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.85,0:18:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到的最后的声音了\Nbefore you're clubbed to death by a candy cane.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.17,0:18:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就不能算了吗\NCan we please just let it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.43,0:18:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会自己想出来的\NYou know I'll figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.15,0:18:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}电影"音乐之声"的主人公一家人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.15,0:18:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  冯·崔普一家\NOkay, Von Trapps.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.37,0:18:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-都到了吧  -对  都到了  可是...\N- Finally all here? - Uh, yeah yeah. Just, uh--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.59,0:18:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很好  -我们昨晚开始的激情\N- Great. - You know, we never got
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.25,0:18:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要用一生的时间才能结束呢\Nto finish what we started last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.96,0:18:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  本\NOh! Uh, Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.95,0:18:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈  手规矩点好吗  -好吧\N- Mom, hands to yourself, okay? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.61,0:18:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵要坐下哦\NIf I could just get my little elf to sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.25,0:18:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NOh, okay. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.63,0:18:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想说\NYeah, I'm just saying, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.71,0:18:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都看过150部圣诞电影了\NI have seen 150 Christmas movies,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.80,0:18:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是从没见过黑人精灵\Nand I ain't never seen a black elf!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.22,0:18:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我们准备好了\NOkay, I think we're ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.76,0:18:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我说"茄子"的时候...\NOkay. So when I yell "Vixen"...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.46,0:18:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  她参加过曲棍球队\NFine. So she was on the field hockey team,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.25,0:18:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还一起上数学课  而且...\Nwe obviously had the same math class, and--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.76,0:18:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  上帝  我知道是谁了\NOh my God. I know who it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:18:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NDanny...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.02,0:18:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二\NOne, two--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.53,0:18:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本是同性恋\NBen's gay!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.30,0:19:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -本\N- What?! - Ben?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.39,0:19:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\NSeriously?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.35,0:19:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是同性恋\NI'm not gay!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.49,0:19:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟  没关系的\NDude, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.11,0:19:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该没有很震惊哦\NI guess I'm not that surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.72,0:19:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于明白塔克尔和他算怎么回事了\NIt does explain the whole Tucker thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.26,0:19:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等一下\NWait! Hold up!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.83,0:19:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我是同性恋吗\NWait, you think I'm gay?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.60,0:19:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见过同性恋长我这德行吗\NYo, how could you look at me and say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.21,0:19:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最后说一次  我不是同性恋\NOkay, for the last time, I'm not gay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.93,0:19:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  你到底怎么回事\NDanny, what is the matter with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.42,0:19:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  "你的朋友"\NCome on! "Your friend"?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.09,0:19:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸已经告诉我了\NDad told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.25,0:19:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没告诉我就告诉你父亲了\NYou told your father before you told me?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.35,0:19:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没说啊\NI didn't tell anyone anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.53,0:19:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他害怕出柜\NBecause he's afraid to come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.94,0:19:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没有要出柜  -看见没\N- I'm not coming out! - See?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.71,0:19:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我才是同性恋  -爸\N- I'm gay! - Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.29,0:19:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-维勒先生  -雷  你不用帮他打掩护\N- Mr. Wheeler? - Ray, you don't have to cover for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.37,0:19:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是帮他打掩护\NI'm not covering for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.61,0:19:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的都是真的\NI'm telling the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.19,0:19:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说真的吗\NAre you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.29,0:19:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\NYes!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.47,0:19:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是同性恋啊...\NYou're gay?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.19,0:19:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能先拍照\NAny chance we could put a
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.22,0:19:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再谈这个\Npin in this until after we take the photo?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.92,0:19:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦\NWow!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.19,0:19:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就没想过用缓和点的方法说这事儿吗\NYou think you could have eased into that a little more?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.09,0:19:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额  的确有人说过我应该改变下表达方式了\NYeah, I have been told I need to work on my delivery.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听你这么说\NWell, hearing you say that just
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.57,0:20:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印证了...我知道的一切\Nconfirms... everything I've always known.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.24,0:20:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你早就知道爸爸是同性恋吗\NYou knew Dad was gay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.90,0:20:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.47,0:20:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说至今为止的一切都不是我的错\NNothing was my fault!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.10,0:20:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐出色的直觉真是太棒了\NIt feels so good to be right.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.84,0:20:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样是不是说我们之间没事了\NSo does this mean that we're actually okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.23,0:20:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该吧\NUh, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.48,0:20:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是希望你能在感恩节告诉我们\NI just wish you would have blurted it out at Thanksgiving
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.96,0:20:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都这么做嘛\Nlike a normal person.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.53,0:20:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  该做正事了\NOkay, and we're back.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.63,0:20:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  大家靠紧一点\NOkay, everybody together.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.55,0:20:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才很抱歉\NOkay, sorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.02,0:20:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好不是每天都发生这种事\NThough I'm guessing this doesn't happen every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.83,0:20:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世事难料啊\NYou'd be surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.30,0:20:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我数三声\NOkay, on three.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.11,0:20:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二\NOne, two...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.83,0:20:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个交换生  对吧\NIt was that exchange student, wasn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.55,0:20:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三\NThree!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.72,0:20:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的日记  我又来了\NDear Diary. It's me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.15,0:20:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真是历史性的一天\NToday was epic!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  X女孩不知道\NFirst of all, girl "X" has no idea
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.88,0:20:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己就是那个X\Nthat she's girl "X."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.32,0:20:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是以防万一  以后我们叫她Y女孩好了\NBut for safety's sake, we'll call her girl "Y."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.35,0:20:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我还没说\NOh! But I didn't tell you
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.93,0:21:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天发生的最重要的事呢\Nthe biggest thing that happened to me today.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.70,0:21:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚知道\NI just found out
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.84,0:21:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢的中餐厅可以送外卖\Nthat my favorite Chinese restaurant delivers!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.36,0:21:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我再也不用坐上两趟地铁\NI no longer have to take two subways
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.01,0:21:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能吃到美味蛋卷了\Nto get those amazing eggrolls.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.18,0:21:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爸是同性恋  本不是\NMy dad's gay and Ben isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.39,0:21:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NDanny.
