[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.28,0:00:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  艾玛宝贝\NOkay, Emma,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.10,0:00:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次来看医生了\Nfirst doctor's visit.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.80,0:00:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心  有老爸在\NBut have no fear, because daddy's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.90,0:00:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些检查都常规的很\NIt's all pretty basic.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.58,0:00:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铺着纸的桌子\NPaper covered table.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.92,0:00:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不知上一位宝宝有没有病\NWhich is good because you never know
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.65,0:00:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防传染  挺好\Nwhere the last baby has been.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.30,0:00:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看\NLook.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.64,0:00:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费用品全都摆在这了\NHere's where they keep all the free stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.50,0:00:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔\NTucker?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.61,0:00:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.51,0:00:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别辜负医院一番美意  好吗\NDon't knock the system, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.53,0:00:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你以为我们平时用的厕纸和纸巾\NWhy do you think we always have
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.68,0:00:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是从哪来的\Ntoilet paper and napkins. Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.90,0:00:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生还没来检查\NYou're gonna get us kicked out
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.92,0:00:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就得被赶出去的\Nbefore the doctor even--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.79,0:00:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦 那是压舌板\NTongue depressors.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.05,0:00:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更喜欢称它们为...\NOr as I like to call them,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.47,0:00:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-酷毙鼓槌  -没错\N- kickass drum sticks. - Yup.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.25,0:00:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛·惠勒\NEmma Wheeler?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.36,0:00:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她的亲友乐队\NAnd her backup band,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.76,0:00:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆重谢幕\Nbig finish!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.49,0:00:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是艾玛的爸爸\NHi, I'm Emma's dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.78,0:00:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都管我叫本\NFormally known as just "Ben."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.63,0:00:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是塔克尔\NAnd I'm Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.08,0:00:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可不是情侣\NWe are not together.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.85,0:00:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么总跟人说这个\NWhy do you keep telling people that?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.39,0:01:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  这可是纽约\NDude, it's New York.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.00,0:01:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们爱误会\NPeople assume.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.99,0:01:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人会误会\NNobody assumes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.37,0:01:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我误会了\NI assumed.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.80,0:01:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是情侣\NWe're not together.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.13,0:01:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是本·惠勒\NI'm Ben Wheeler,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.12,0:01:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛的直男单身老爸\NEmma's straight and very single father.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.32,0:01:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢告知\NThat's good to know,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.49,0:01:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛的单身老爸\NEmma's very single father.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.09,0:01:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*人生妙无边  惊喜无极限*\N*It's amazing how the unexpected*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.16,0:01:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*劝君莫等闲  雌雄随我愿*\N*can take your life and change directions.*
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.03,0:01:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们来给\NSo, let's take a look
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.35,0:01:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的小病人看看\Nat our little patient here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.04,0:01:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真是可爱极了\NShe really is adorable.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.20,0:01:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  这个小生命由我一手创造  \NThanks, I made her myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.31,0:01:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总爱认为她遗传了\NI like to think that she got
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.24,0:01:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的所有优点\Nall of my good parts.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.38,0:01:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是所有啦\NNot all of--
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.68,0:01:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你坐在\NSo, why don't you sit up
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.96,0:01:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张台上吧\Non this table here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.00,0:01:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\NOkay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.91,0:01:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  请问医生芳名\NI'm sorry, I didn't get your name. Doctor...?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.89,0:01:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是凯西  是名护师[也有实践者的意思]\NCassie. I'm a nurse practitioner.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.95,0:01:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们俩还真像\NThen we've got a lot in common
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.88,0:01:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是名实践者  正实践着做爸爸\Nbecause I'm practicing to be a dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.96,0:02:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  她绝对不是那意思\NThat is not what it means, Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.92,0:02:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她喜欢你\NShe likes you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.82,0:02:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来大家说的是真的\NI guess what they say is true.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.58,0:02:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是真的 \NWhat's true?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.50,0:02:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美女会互相吸引\NPretty girls like to hang out together.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.27,0:02:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你在入院表格上\NOkay, there are quite a few items
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.20,0:02:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少填了几项信息\Nyou didn't answer on the intake form.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.89,0:02:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  有几个问题挺难回答的\NYeah. Some of those questions were a little tricky.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.12,0:02:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如生日吗\NDate of birth?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.60,0:02:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问中了最难的\NStraight to the tough ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.02,0:02:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.19,0:02:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能回答其他问题吗\NWhat else you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.89,0:02:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的病史呢\NMother's history?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.82,0:02:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲喜交集\NCheckered.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.63,0:02:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个极其复杂的故事\NLet's just say it's a very complicated story.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.01,0:02:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一度春宵后就玩失踪\NShe split after a one-night stand
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.37,0:02:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后把孩子丢在门口\Nand left the baby on the doormat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.65,0:02:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实也没那么复杂\NIt's not really all that complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.66,0:02:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢  塔克尔\NThanks, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.34,0:02:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我想说的是\NLook, the point is
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.71,0:02:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我只关心我的女儿\NI've only got one girl in my life right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.78,0:02:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请务必让她\NSo, please just make sure she stays
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.56,0:02:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,健康成长\Nas perfect and healthy as she seems.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.80,0:02:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的生命中已经有了一样财富\NShe's already got one thing going for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.03,0:02:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是你\NShe's got you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.16,0:03:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么\NWhat's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.17,0:03:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的电话号码\NMy phone number.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.59,0:03:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时间给我打电话  单身的本\NGive me a call sometime, very single Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.72,0:03:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生马上就来\NThe doctor will be right in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.66,0:03:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  我刚被热辣的护师看上了\NYes! I just got hit on by a hot baby nurse.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.43,0:03:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱俩真是好搭档\NWe make a good team.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.95,0:03:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  没错\NYes, we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.10,0:03:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这些都塞进裤子里\NNow shove these down your pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.99,0:03:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太激动了\NI'm so excited.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.39,0:03:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了这么多年  我终于能去看\NI can't believe I'm finally gonna get
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.83,0:03:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的职业比赛了\Nto see you play in a pro game
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.78,0:03:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难以置信\Nafter all these years.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.98,0:03:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是一场不落\NWhereas I have never missed one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.40,0:03:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这希望你去过卡尔加里[加拿大西南部城市]\NReally wish you could have come up to Calgary.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.98,0:03:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那儿每周都有比赛\NThere every week.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.33,0:03:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你曾受过点伤害\NI know it was a little traumatic for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.28,0:03:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但能看到你重新振作  我真为你高兴\Nbut I for one am very glad you got traded.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.67,0:03:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受伤害\NTraumatic?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.71,0:03:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会啊  运动员会因为各种原因转会啦\NNo, players get traded for all kinds of reasons.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.01,0:03:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎记者怎么写\NI don't care what that reporter said.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.92,0:03:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么记者\NWhat reporter?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.68,0:03:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个记者说唯一比你溜冰还烂的\NThe one who said the only thing worse
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.07,0:03:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是...\Nthan your skating is--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.95,0:03:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别说了  -各种原因啦\N- Aah. - All kinds of reasons.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.68,0:03:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找点吃的\NI'm gonna go get something to eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.86,0:04:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们再检查一下清单吧\NCan we please go over the list now?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.56,0:04:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都要完美\NEverything's got to be perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.72,0:04:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会完美的  宝贝\NAnd it will be, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.82,0:04:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有妈妈在  放心吧\NMom's got it covered.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.78,0:04:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从戈登那里拿到我的\NYou've got my extra long laces
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.97,0:04:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长鞋带吗  我的护口器  \Nfrom Gordon's? My mouth guard
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.36,0:04:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还在包里吗  -我带了\N- still in the package? - I'm on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.68,0:04:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮我熨袜子了吗\NAnd you're gonna press my socks?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.09,0:04:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熨斗已经准备好了\NThe iron is already on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.24,0:04:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊  我已经插上熨斗了吗\NOh, my God. Did I leave the iron on?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.49,0:04:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你还这么迷信\NI can't believe you're still so superstitious.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.10,0:04:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得高中时你\NDo you remember that rank jersey
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.81,0:04:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常穿的那件臭运动衫吗\Nyou used to wear in high school--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.00,0:04:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  就是这件\NOh, my God. That's the one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.74,0:04:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没舍得洗过\NI never washed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.09,0:04:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永不会洗\NNever will.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.49,0:04:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是胜利的味道\NThat is the scent of victory.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.12,0:04:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜利看来就跟垃圾箱里面一个味\NVictory smells like the inside of a dumpster.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.43,0:04:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满汗臭味的垃圾桶让我的宝贝获胜\NA hot, sweaty dumpster that helps my baby win.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.97,0:04:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我吧\NGive me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.55,0:04:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每次比赛还都把它套在队服里面\NI still wear it under my uniform for every game.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.19,0:04:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然紧了点  但确实是我的幸运衫\NIt's tight, but it's definitely my good luck charm.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.73,0:04:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他第一次拿冠军时就穿的这件\NHe was wearing this when he won his first championship.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.39,0:04:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时他才14岁\NHe was only 14.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.49,0:04:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  熏得我都流泪了\NDear lord. My eyes are watering.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.61,0:05:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只死鸟不可能被熏活了吧\NThat bird was already dead, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.48,0:05:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了  -不\N- Yes! - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.75,0:05:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去洗衣服\NLaundry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.79,0:05:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服上滴的口水  吐的奶  沾的便便\NIf it's drool, spit-up, or doodie-related,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.02,0:05:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都归你洗啦\Nit's your responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.18,0:05:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在吗\NKnock, knock?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.35,0:05:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚在街角吃晚饭\NI was,just having dinner
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.57,0:05:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想上来看看本需不需要\Naround the corner, and I thought I would see
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.16,0:05:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮忙哄艾玛睡觉\Nif Ben needed any help getting Emma to bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.88,0:05:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你其实是想问  本独自一人\NDon't you mean see if Ben needed any help
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.96,0:05:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否孤枕难眠吧\Ngetting himself to bed?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.43,0:05:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是太幽默了\NYou're hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.70,0:05:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-疼疼疼  -他去哪儿了\N- Ow, ow, ow, ow! - Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.60,0:05:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和给艾玛看病的护师吃饭去了\NHe's on a date with Emma's nurse.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.71,0:05:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  艾玛不是唯一\NApparently, Emma's not the only one
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.82,0:05:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被她吸引的人\Nwho passed her physical.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.96,0:05:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是与他的志趣相抵触了吗\NIsn't that a conflict of interest?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.57,0:05:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的是你自己吧\NOnly yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.02,0:05:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧\NCome on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.32,0:05:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得对本断了念想\NYou gotta get over Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.90,0:05:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\NPlease,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.48,0:05:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就不喜欢他了\NI am completely over him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.23,0:05:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  你回来啦\NBen, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.26,0:05:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  你来啦\NHey, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.54,0:05:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大好消息\NGreat news,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.64,0:05:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和凯西的约会极其顺利\Nmy date with Cassie was amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.77,0:05:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是好消息\NThat is great news.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.57,0:05:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她聪颖  漂亮  \NShe's smart, pretty,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.37,0:05:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教我自测脉搏\Ntaught me how to take my own pulse,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.34,0:05:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且艾玛也喜欢她\Nand Emma loves her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.60,0:06:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  艾玛谁都喜欢\NBen, Emma loves everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.20,0:06:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就像只宠物狗\NShe's like a puppy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.50,0:06:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想莱丽阿姨了吧...\NDid you miss your Auntie Riley-- -
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.62,0:06:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  艾玛  咱们去把\NCome on, Emma, let's go finish
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.03,0:06:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《小红帽》的故事讲完\N"The Little Red Riding Hood."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.39,0:06:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的钱押大灰狼身上啦\NMy money's on the wolf.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.75,0:06:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是塔克尔洗衣服吗\NTucker's got laundry again?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.93,0:06:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\NYup.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.26,0:06:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\NSweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.62,0:06:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪\NIt's weird,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.51,0:06:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前从没和像凯西一样的女孩约会过\NI've never gone out with a girl like Cassie before.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.68,0:06:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她教养良好\NShe's educated,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.99,0:06:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,业务熟练\Nshe's a professional,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.96,0:06:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还是个...\Nshe's...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.26,0:06:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成年人\Na grown-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.86,0:06:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咋了又\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.09,0:06:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为\NLet's just say
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.96,0:06:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你识人的能力\Nthat maybe you're not exactly
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.39,0:06:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有待提高\Nthe best judge of character.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.40,0:06:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你容易受其他事情进而影响了判断\NYou can get a little distracted by other things.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.87,0:06:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说  咪咪\NLike boobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.48,0:06:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是那样\NOkay, that's not--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.62,0:06:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  也许你说得对\Nokay, maybe it's a little true.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.91,0:06:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才需要你\NWhich is why I need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.33,0:06:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\NYou do?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.37,0:06:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和凯西吃顿饭\NJust have lunch with Cassie
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.68,0:06:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我你对她的印象\Nand tell me what you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.68,0:06:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以实话实说\NYou can be totally honest.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.23,0:06:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我不愿意\NOkay, I'd rather not.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.54,0:06:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说见过她后如实告诉我\NI mean after you go out with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.62,0:06:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  现在我有艾玛了  我觉得\NPlease? I think this is the kind of girl
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.13,0:06:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种女孩就是我应该追求的对象\Nthat I should be dating now that I have Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.92,0:07:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\NFine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.54,0:07:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去\NI'll do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.91,0:07:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.86,0:07:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个好朋友\NYou're such a great friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.63,0:07:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌那个词\NI hate that word.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.28,0:07:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  我这有条毯子太臭了\NTuck, I've got a blankie
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.47,0:07:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能需要你穿防护服清洗\Nin here that might require a Hazmat suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.54,0:07:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  爱玛啊\NOh, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.43,0:07:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么小不点儿的人\NHow could someone so small
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.35,0:07:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这么臭\Nsmell so bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.59,0:07:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你点的干酪汉堡\NYour cheeseburger,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.90,0:07:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有24根炸薯条\Nand your 24 fries.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.38,0:07:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我点的是23根\NI said 23.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.81,0:07:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数目一定得和我的运动衫号码一样\NThe number has to be the same as my jersey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.63,0:07:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  兄弟\NThanks, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.62,0:07:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本\NBen.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.70,0:07:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗨  -嗨\N- Hi. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.96,0:07:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的关于莱丽的一切都是真的\NEverything you said about Riley was true.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.10,0:07:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起玩儿的非常开心\NWe had such a great time together.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.68,0:08:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能尽快再找时间一起玩儿呢\NCan we please do this again soon?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.31,0:08:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  就这么定了\NOh, it's a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.28,0:08:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  我得先走了\NOh! Okay. Gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.30,0:08:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-以后再聊  -好\N- Talk to you later. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.60,0:08:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得怎么样\NSo, what'd you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.19,0:08:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的很对\NWell, you were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.57,0:08:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的很特别\NShe's really special.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.95,0:08:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  我就知道\NYes! I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.43,0:08:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说她特别的意思是\NAnd by special, I mean
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.62,0:08:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的巨讨厌她\NI hate that girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.81,0:08:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她实在是太烦人了\NShe is so going down.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.73,0:08:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟  再给我加一根\NHey, I need another one.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.91,0:08:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家早\NMorning!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.68,0:08:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带来了...\NI brought um--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.37,0:08:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人烤了松饼吗\NDid somebody bake muffins?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.54,0:08:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们自己做的吗\NDid you make them?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.97,0:08:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁做的\NThen who did?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.39,0:08:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  莱丽\NHi, Riles.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.59,0:08:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望一切顺利\NI hope everything is okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.94,0:08:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手艺还有待提高\NI kind of had to improvise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.79,0:08:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去上班了\NI gotta get to work,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.72,0:08:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还会在丹尼的比赛上\Nbut I'll see everyone at Danny's game
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.11,0:08:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见面的是吧  -当然\N- later, right? - Most definitely.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.15,0:08:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经开始想你了\NI miss you already.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.93,0:08:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算开吃煎蛋卷了哈\NAnd here comes my omelet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.65,0:08:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信我认识了\NI can't believe I know
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.01,0:08:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个真正的职业冰球运动员\Na real professional hockey player.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.78,0:09:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带的是甜甜圈吗\NOoh. Are those donuts?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.93,0:09:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢甜甜圈了\NI love donuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.44,0:09:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是吃了容易长胖的话  我就会...\NI'd live on them if they weren't so...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.22,0:09:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠它喘气了\Nfattening.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.83,0:09:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜她该不是去上班时\NI'm guessing she didn't just stop by
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.33,0:09:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便过来的吧\Non her way into the office?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.97,0:09:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然她已经\NWell, now that she has
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.88,0:09:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到莱丽你的认可了\Nthe Riley stamp of approval.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.93,0:09:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我在走廊\NI just met
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.08,0:09:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰见了一个超级可爱的女孩\Nthe most lovely girl in the hallway.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.01,0:09:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的  莱丽\NReally, Riley.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.68,0:09:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  妈\NHi, Ma.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.49,0:09:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得准备上班了\NI gotta finish getting ready for work.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.71,0:09:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的袜子吗\NAre those my socks?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.66,0:09:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  不是  这是我的\NOh, no, honey. These are mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.16,0:09:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我难道没告诉你  我刚被交易到\NDidn't I tell you? I just got drafted
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.40,0:09:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游骑兵冰球队了吗  对  那是你的袜子\Nby the Rangers. Yes, these are your socks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.68,0:09:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样对我\NDon't do that to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.67,0:09:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经够紧张了\NI'm nervous enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.93,0:09:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  我的鸡蛋上怎么没有放番茄酱\NWait, why do I have no ketchup on my eggs?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.15,0:09:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有比赛的时候我的鸡蛋上都会有番茄酱的\NI always have ketchup on my eggs on game day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.13,0:09:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我来说可能是场灾难\NThis could have been a disaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.58,0:09:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\NAah, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.80,0:09:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那是什么玩意啊\NOh, yeah. What was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.86,0:10:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啥玩意\NWhat was what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.68,0:10:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  亲爱的  继续锻炼你的肌肉吧\NNothing, honey. Just keep building up your strength.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.28,0:10:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看就是件破抹布\NIt looked like a rag to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.91,0:10:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  任何人\NTucker, nobody knows
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.21,0:10:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对任何东西都一无所知\Nanything about anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.44,0:10:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白了吗\NDo you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.33,0:10:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是很明白  -是本叫你吗\N- Not really. - Oh, is that Ben?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.03,0:10:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫你去爱玛那里帮忙呢\NHe's calling you to come help with Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.84,0:10:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿  塔克"  他这就过去了\N"Hey, Tucker!" He's coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.16,0:10:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我什么都没听到  -快去吧\N- I don't hear anything. - Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.39,0:10:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  丹尼\NHey-- hey, Danny!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.52,0:10:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看我们现在就走怎么样\NWhat do you say we get out of here?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.78,0:10:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大赛之前\NYou know, clear your head
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.84,0:10:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清醒一下头脑\Nbefore the big game.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.66,0:10:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意  我会照顾爱玛的\NGood idea. I'll watch Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.92,0:10:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  马上  你怎么还不走\NGo. Now. Why are you still here?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没吃完呢\NI'm still eating.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.94,0:10:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面包的好处就是\NAnd that is the great thing about bread.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.02,0:10:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以把任何东西做成三明治\NMakes everything a sandwich.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.31,0:10:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶  很美味的样子\NYay. Yummy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.16,0:10:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  那我们今晚\NAll right, I will see you tonight
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.61,0:10:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体育场见  这边\Nat the arena, and there is nothing
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.97,0:10:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不用担心\Nto worry about here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.86,0:10:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不用  拜拜\NNot a thing. So bye-bye, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.46,0:10:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜\NBye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.26,0:10:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧  拜拜\NGo on, bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.23,0:10:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你确定...  -不  不  现在就拜拜  \N- You sure... - No, no, bye-bye, now!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.76,0:10:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜  拜\NBye! Bye!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.88,0:10:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  等等\NOkay, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.76,0:10:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我知道是什么事了\NI think I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.25,0:10:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\NDo you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.30,0:10:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道\NDo you got
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.37,0:10:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚终结了丹尼的职业生涯\Nthat you just ended Danny's career
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.41,0:10:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你毁了\Nbecause you destroyed
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.82,0:11:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的幸运衫吗\Nhis lucky jersey?!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.01,0:11:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我真的不知道这个\NNo, I didn't get that part.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.02,0:11:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个十足的大骗子\NShe's such a phony.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.32,0:11:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪会有人那么好\NI mean, nobody is that nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.14,0:11:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我做了早餐"\NOh, I made breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.82,0:11:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"都是我亲手做的"\NI cooked everything myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.24,0:11:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会那样\NWho does that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.71,0:11:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你同意我的观点  是吗\NYou agree with me, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.24,0:11:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"同意"是个很语气很重的词\NAgree's kind of a strong word.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.92,0:11:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  真的\NDanny, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.49,0:11:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的很会耍手段\NShe is so manipulative.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.17,0:11:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道凯西想干什么\NI know what Cassie is doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.82,0:11:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和我弟弟\NTrying to have a relationship
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.99,0:11:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展开恋情吗\Nwith my brother?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.86,0:11:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个\NExactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.77,0:11:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个和你想做的\NAnd how is that any different
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.77,0:11:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么区别吗\Nfrom what you're trying to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.31,0:11:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然有区别  因为...\NIt's different because...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.05,0:11:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她更擅长这个\NShe's better at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.20,0:11:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我承认\NOkay, I admit it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.58,0:11:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是有点嫉妒了\NMaybe I'm a little jealous,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.80,0:11:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我总是不由自主的想他\Nbut I just can't stop thinking about him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.99,0:11:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像自从他再次进入我的生活\NIt's like ever since he came back into my life,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.91,0:11:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中时的那些感觉\Nall of these old feelings from high school
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.70,0:11:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又都一一回来了\Njust came bubbling back up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.38,0:11:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不同的是  我觉得\NOnly this time I think
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.40,0:11:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次他会注意到我\Nmaybe he'll notice me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.24,0:11:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再是以前的那个庞然大物了\NYou know, I'm not Ri-gantor anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.48,0:11:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再是以前坐在他头上的那个胖子了\NI'm not the fat girl that used to sit on his head.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.08,0:11:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想象\NI just keep imagining
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.02,0:12:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后他会走向我  跟我说...\Nhe's finally gonna walk up to me and say--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.04,0:12:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别去女洗手间\NStay out of the ladies' room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.62,0:12:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才有人在那里吐了\NSomebody just puked.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.54,0:12:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟想象中的"我会永远爱你"\NNot quite the same ring
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.81,0:12:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很一样\Nas "I've always loved you."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.13,0:12:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\NTrust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.44,0:12:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他的损失\NIt's his loss.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.88,0:12:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定总有一天\NI'm sure one of these days
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.42,0:12:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能找到个块头更大点的人\Nyou'll find someone even bigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.90,0:12:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  更好的人\NI mean, better.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.62,0:12:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\NThanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.17,0:12:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你是对的\NI know you're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.27,0:12:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...\NIt's just--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.49,0:12:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到你喜欢的人在谈论其他人\Nit's really hard to listen to someone
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.84,0:12:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真的让人很难受\Nthat you like talk about someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.65,0:12:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂\NI get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.92,0:12:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\NBelieve me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.07,0:12:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的懂\NI get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.62,0:12:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么难的\NHow hard can it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.81,0:12:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就去买件运动衫\NYou know, I'll-- I'll buy a jersey,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.32,0:12:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绑在车的保险杠上\NI'll tie it to my bumper,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.69,0:12:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后开着车绕城一圈\NI'll drive it around town,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.75,0:12:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再弄块肉包在衣服里\Nand wrap it in dead meat,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.92,0:12:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后放在塑料袋里蹂躏一下\Nand then I'll just shove it in a plastic bag
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.49,0:12:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后扔到体育场  他不会发现的\Nand drop it off at the arena. He'll never know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.25,0:12:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们已经搞定了\NI think we're actually good.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.05,0:12:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好  -对\N- Okay. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.86,0:12:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个\NCheck this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.36,0:12:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会发现的  对吧\NHe'll never know, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.57,0:12:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊\NOh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.38,0:12:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  实在是太完美了\NOh, yeah, it's perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.78,0:12:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的脑子还没有被冰球打到坏掉\NHe hasn't taken that many pucks to the head.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.72,0:12:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会发现的\NHe'll know!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.67,0:12:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要保护我\NYou have to protect me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.67,0:13:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.55,0:13:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我需要做的是拿出妈妈的样子来\NNo, what I have to do is mom-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.05,0:13:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去跟我儿子聊聊\NI'm going to go talk to my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.78,0:13:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他要长大\NI'm gonna tell him to grow up,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.12,0:13:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后希望能阻止他\Nand hopefully, I'll stop him
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.56,0:13:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你撕成碎片\Nfrom shredding you
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.01,0:13:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你对他的幸运衫那样\Nlike you did his lucky jersey.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.44,0:13:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我在这里等着\NI'll wait here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.29,0:13:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  就这样吧\NYeah, I'm sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.04,0:13:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我是他母亲\NIt's okay, I'm his mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.46,0:13:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼\NOh, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.04,0:13:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得聊聊  -你怎么才来\N- We need to talk. - Where have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.27,0:13:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\NIt's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.32,0:13:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种场面我都见过\NNothing I haven't seen before.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.10,0:13:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了这个\NExcept maybe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.17,0:13:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  邦妮·惠勒\NHi, Bonnie Wheeler...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.50,0:13:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈\NMom!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.48,0:13:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了\NRight.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.45,0:13:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\NListen.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.98,0:13:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听我说  亲爱的  -我的鞋带\N- Listen, honey. - My laces,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.85,0:13:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的护口器\Nmy mouth guard,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.15,0:13:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对\Nwait.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.10,0:13:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的幸运衫哪儿去了\NWhere's my lucky jersey?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.65,0:13:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这个\NYeah, about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.87,0:13:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你...\NSweetie, do you--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.36,0:13:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得小时候\Ndo you remember when you were little
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.72,0:13:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的兔子\Nand your rabbit,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.48,0:13:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍普森先生\NMr. Hopson,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.94,0:13:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去乡下住了吗\Nwent to go live in the country?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.64,0:13:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.84,0:13:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的运动衫也发生了类似的状况\NWell, the same thing kind of happened to your jersey.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.63,0:14:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的运动衫现在在宾夕法尼亚的农场吗\NMy jersey's on a farm in Pennsylvania?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.71,0:14:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.07,0:14:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  你的运动衫\NDanny, your jersey
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.12,0:14:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了蔚蓝天空下最好的洗衣篮里\Nhas gone to the great laundry basket in the sky.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.19,0:14:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在洗衣机里洗坏了\NIt bit the dust in the washer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.40,0:14:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它和抹布一起长眠地底了\NIt's sleeping with the lint.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.04,0:14:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,支离破碎  四分五裂了\NIt's ruined, destroyed,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.07,0:14:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥都不剩了\Nnothing left!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.67,0:14:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我的球衣弄丢了吗\NYou lost my jersey?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.96,0:14:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多吧\NClose enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.34,0:14:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  亲爱的  听我说\NBut, honey, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.75,0:14:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有事的\NIt is going to be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.65,0:14:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  不\NNo. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.72,0:14:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  怎么可能没事\NNo, no, it's not going to be okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.89,0:14:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能出去比赛\NI can't go out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.75,0:14:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我的宝贝球衣  死都不出去比赛\NI've never gone out there without it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.18,0:14:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  挑断我的跟腱  \NQuick, cut my Achilles tendon.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.70,0:14:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你必须振作起来\NListen, listen. Just pull yourself together!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.30,0:14:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  听我说\NHoney, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.54,0:14:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是件球衣\NIt's just a jersey.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.11,0:14:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟好运无关\NIt's not lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.83,0:14:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白不\NOkay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.52,0:14:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西不会给你带来好运  懂吗\NNone of this stuff is lucky, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.18,0:14:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不需要这堆鞋带\NYou don't need these laces!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.27,0:14:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗  你也不需要护口器\NOkay? You don't need this mouth guard.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.19,0:14:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  护口器你还是留着吧\NOkay, maybe you need that mouth guard,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.11,0:14:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这和好运没关\Nbut it's not because it's lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.10,0:14:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为你老妈我可为你这牙齿\NIt's because I paid a lot of money
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.64,0:14:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砸了不少钱\Nfor those teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.12,0:14:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  看着我\NNow, look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.79,0:15:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个天赋异禀\NYou are an amazing,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.65,0:15:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才华横溢的运动员\Ntalented athlete.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.59,0:15:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是丹尼·维勒\NAll right, you're Danny Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.30,0:15:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个球队里舍你其谁\NYou are the best damn player on this team!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.85,0:15:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别激动  只是姐的个人观点啦\NJust trying to make a point here, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.91,0:15:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要让一件旧衣服\NSo don't let some old shirt
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.57,0:15:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主宰你的成就\Ndetermine your greatness.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.42,0:15:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\NListen.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.44,0:15:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在就走出去\NYou get out there,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.96,0:15:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你妈也骄傲一把\Nand you make your mother proud.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.33,0:15:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  老妈\NThanks, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.41,0:15:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\NYeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.38,0:15:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈  -我知道  我知道\N- Mom! - Yeah, I know, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.36,0:15:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道该往哪走\NI know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.72,0:15:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是我的好儿子\NWhoo! That's my boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.56,0:15:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊  艾玛  快看你丹尼叔叔\NOh, look, Emma. Can you see Uncle Danny?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.32,0:15:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  小艾玛\NHi, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.41,0:15:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊  维勒\NLet's go, Wheeler!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.22,0:15:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  冲啊\NCome on, Danny! 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.33,0:15:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛一直这么暴力吗\NIs it always this violent?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.52,0:15:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够幸运才看得到呢\NOnly if you're lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.53,0:15:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很棒吗\NIsn't it great?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.74,0:15:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  裁判  这是冰球比赛\NOh, it's called hockey, ref!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.39,0:15:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是拥抱比赛\NNot cuddling!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.53,0:15:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你对凯西那么友好\NHey, thanks again for being so nice to Cassie. 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.65,0:15:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我和艾玛来说\NIt really means a lot
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.27,0:15:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意义很大\Nto me and Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.24,0:16:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别客气啊\NNo problem. 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.67,0:16:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,击人犯规\NCross check?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.67,0:16:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是瞎了啊\NWhat are you, blind?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.84,0:16:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他先打的他\NHe hit him first.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.04,0:16:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有搞错\NCome on!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.67,0:16:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  因为看起来好像\NReally, 'cause it looked like
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.74,0:16:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是丹尼刚刚猛击了...\NDanny just whaled on--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.03,0:16:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我闭嘴就是了\NI'll be quiet.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.77,0:16:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼要去哪儿\NWhere's Danny going?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.85,0:16:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁闭区  我去确认下\NPenalty Box. I'm gonna go check on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.85,0:16:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}禁闭区：冰球被罚下场队员的座席
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.41,0:16:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我马上回来  -好的\N- I'll be right back. - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.35,0:16:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以\NSo.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.75,0:16:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩进展如何啦\NHow's it going so far?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.90,0:16:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该谈谈了\NWe should talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.25,0:16:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  你太厉害了\NDude! You're amazing!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.33,0:16:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中了什么邪啦\NWhat's gotten into you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.86,0:16:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\NI don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.14,0:16:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没了那件球衣的束缚\NIt's like I'm totally free
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.24,0:16:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像彻底自由了\Nwithout that jersey.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.48,0:16:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是因为我现在能随意挥手臂了\NMaybe it's because I can move my arms.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.91,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶\NYeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.61,0:16:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻子都看得出\NIt's pretty obvious
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.57,0:16:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢本\Nyou're in love with Ben.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.09,0:16:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.39,0:16:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.36,0:16:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是...\NThat is so...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.90,0:16:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太扯了\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.42,0:16:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\NIt's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.42,0:16:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并没有觉得受威胁\NIt's not like I'm threatened,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.46,0:16:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\NI just--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.57,0:16:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你感到难过\NI feel badly for you
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.89,0:16:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在他眼中\Nbecause he's never gonna see you
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.19,0:16:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不过就是\Nas anything other than...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.88,0:16:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“大裤衩”[莱利过去的绰号]\NFatpants.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.25,0:16:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你该回去了\NAll right, get back out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.64,0:16:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得克制  少扁几个人\NBut maybe try to punch out a few less people
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.53,0:17:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离禁闭区远点儿\Nand stay out of the penalty box.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.01,0:17:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你现在\NI don't think it's me
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.51,0:17:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没空担心我了\Nyou need to worry about.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.27,0:17:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱巨怪上啊\NRi-gantor!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.54,0:17:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天\NOh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.11,0:17:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是怎么了\NWhat is wrong with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.23,0:17:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很努力克制了  但是莱巨怪\NI try so hard, but Ri-gantor
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.50,0:17:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是发作了\Nstill comes roaring out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.59,0:17:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太难过\NDon't feel too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.11,0:17:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯西是个护士\NCassie's a nurse.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.42,0:17:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她知道怎么戴颈托\NShe knows how to put on a neck brace.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.85,0:17:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本现在肯定特恨我\NI'm sure Ben hates me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.03,0:17:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会的\NHe doesn't hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.73,0:17:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去和他聊聊\NJust talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.78,0:17:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能进去\NI can't go in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.20,0:17:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到\NI can't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.28,0:17:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得直面恐惧\NYou gotta face that fear.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.07,0:17:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我\NLook at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.93,0:17:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚做到了\NI faced mine tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.78,0:17:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了比赛\NAnd won.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.83,0:17:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那冰球是从你头盔反弹进去的\NThat puck bounced off your helmet.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.58,0:17:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我故意的\NOn purpose.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.08,0:17:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说\NI'm just saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.24,0:17:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告诉他\NYou gotta tell him the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.36,0:17:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和凯西之间发生的事\Nabout what happened with Cassie
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.57,0:17:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后继续好好生活\Nand then move on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.73,0:17:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么简单倒好了\NI wish it were that easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.90,0:18:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过会儿你们家见\NI'll see you guys at your place.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.43,0:18:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺你  维勒\NCongratulations, Wheeler.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.43,0:18:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟就是个傻叉\NMy brother's an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.65,0:18:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺我优秀的儿子\NTo my amazing son
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.93,0:18:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他的决胜一球\Nand his game winning goal.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.91,0:18:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗  宝贝\NSee, sweetie?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.88,0:18:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不需要那件幸运球衣\NYou never needed that lucky jersey after all.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.80,0:18:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多棒的比赛啊  老兄\NWhat a game, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.04,0:18:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  你帅呆了\NDanny, you were amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.36,0:18:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得我们还欠\NBut, I think we owe
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.71,0:18:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位小淑女  当然还有我\Nthis little lady, and me of course,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.90,0:18:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一句谢谢\Na big thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.92,0:18:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个拿掉\NPull my finger.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.61,0:18:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的幸运球衣\NMy lucky jersey?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.65,0:18:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在改成便捷可爱的迷你号了\NNow in a convenient fun size.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.19,0:18:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这对你来说多重要\NI knew how important it was to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.08,0:18:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔克尔  谢谢你\NOoh, thank you, Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.03,0:18:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太  太贴心了\NThat was so, so, thoughtful.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.15,0:18:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说它一直都在啊\NSo it was there all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.47,0:18:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我赢的原因\NThis is the reason I won.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.89,0:18:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有可能\NOr perhaps
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.60,0:18:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我绝妙的赛前鼓励起了作用\Nit was my brilliant pep talk
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.87,0:18:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说服你\Nthat convinced you
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.22,0:18:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃了信奉十几年的迷信\Nto give up a decade of silly superstitions
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.82,0:19:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后学会相信自己\Nand finally learn to believe in yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.58,0:19:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是因为塔克尔\NNo. It was Tucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.79,0:19:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛  你是我的新幸运星\NEmma, you're my new good luck charm.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.87,0:19:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  你永远是我的袜子女孩\NBut, mom, you'll always be my sock girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.57,0:19:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行吧  只要每次比赛前\NOh, fine. As long as I get to meet you
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.28,0:19:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都让我去更衣室见你一面\Nin the locker room before every game.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.01,0:19:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那个搭着毛巾的帅哥问起我\NOh, and if that hottie in the towel asks,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.43,0:19:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说我是你姐  不是你妈\NI'm your sister-- not your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.47,0:19:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  -嘿\N- Hey. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.75,0:19:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些话\NSo, uh, here's something
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.04,0:19:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高中以后没对任何人说过\NI haven't said to anyone since high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.74,0:19:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉害你女朋友\NSorry I put your girlfriend
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.73,0:19:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭伤了脖子\Nin a headlock.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.00,0:19:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得出还是你的招牌动作啊\NApparently, still your signature move.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.13,0:19:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯西怎么样了\NHow's Cassie?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.77,0:19:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们分手了\NWe broke up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.51,0:19:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我很抱歉\NBen-- I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.22,0:19:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是我的错\NIt was totally my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.47,0:19:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你希望我去找她谈谈\NIf you want me to go talk to her--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.67,0:19:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计那会越帮越忙吧...\NNot sure how helpful that would be.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.19,0:19:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是\NBut, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.42,0:19:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事她一直念念不忘\NShe was obsessed with this idea
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.15,0:19:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得你喜欢我\Nthat you have a crush on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.24,0:19:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.29,0:19:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能\NNo.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.64,0:19:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是...\NThat is so...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.98,0:19:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太扯了\NWhat?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.04,0:20:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能是我的错\NIt was probably my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.25,0:20:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是对她说起你\NI talked about you a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.46,0:20:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如告诉她\NYou mean, like telling her
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.65,0:20:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的绰号是大裤衩吗\Nmy nickname was Fatpants?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.70,0:20:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你啊\NThanks for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.41,0:20:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我只是\NNo, I just
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.49,0:20:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她说了我俩小时候的事\Ntold her what we were like as kids,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.85,0:20:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你是怎么蜕变为现在\Nand how you grew into this
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.89,0:20:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美丽动人的独立新女性\Namazing, independent woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.32,0:20:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说了我希望艾玛长大以后\NAnd how I hope Emma grows up
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.84,0:20:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能像你一样\Nto be just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.02,0:20:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真这么说吗\NYou did?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.05,0:20:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\NYeah, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.36,0:20:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们算和好了吗\NSo we're good?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.07,0:20:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\NAll good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.02,0:20:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴有你这个朋友\NI'm really glad we're friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.42,0:20:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为友谊干杯\NTo friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.90,0:20:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友啊\NFriends.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.30,0:20:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  还是不爽这词儿\NOh, nope. Still hate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.08,0:20:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体育迷们  我们来聊聊冰球和丹尼·维勒\NAll right, sports fans. Let's talk hockey and Danny Wheele
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.65,0:20:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让他加盟新球队的首场演出...\Nwho made this first game of the new... 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.77,0:20:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成了难忘的夜晚\Ntonight a memorable one.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.90,0:20:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们来看看制胜球回放\NLet's take a look at that winning goal.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.53,0:21:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太棒了  -耶\N- That was awesome. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.81,0:21:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  看台区发生激烈打斗\NOf course, the real highlight of the game
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.03,0:21:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把今晚的比赛推向真正高潮\Nwas that incredible fight in the stands.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.65,0:21:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  天...  \NRiley! Oh, my--
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.78,0:21:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  那是你耶  是你的脸\NRiley, that's you! That's your face!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.06,0:21:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼  把遥控器给我\NDanny, give me the remote!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.29,0:21:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱丽  真是你啊  莱巨怪耶\NRiley, that's you! Ri-gantor!
